xNoury: oh hello
esence: yo
xNoury: how are you doing?
takkeo: Yo
turboooooo1: Hey George
knilecrack: wsupppp
Shanmukhosiris: hiiiiiii
knilecrack: :D
SlayerX1: HeyGuys
Equalizer_olo: Привет
the_awoken1: heeey gorge
alienware997: Greetings from Germany!
ftt0717: What’s up???
knilecrack: you didn't get banned
mtasic85: Hello guys
0xkuj: Hihihi
kornez: NEW RAP SONG? LUL
liqo13: woaow wee, are we gonna do homotopy type theory?
serhejenos: serhejenos subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 9 months!
UniversalGeneve: Tee or Tea?
fghoekstra79: Netherlands in tha house!
0xc0ffeee: suuuuup
r1ppyd1ppy: Oh boy oh boy
dougboy8989: Yo the original og jailbreaker
knilecrack: :D
nagimohsen: Geohot! Will you get back into the jailbreak scene?? Since the new bootrom exploit ??
hawsh: what are you doing today ??
watchVWAVE: Is that a cot?
stibsy73: Hey Geohot
knilecrack: did you finish with Iphone iboot thign?
Jewishrambo: he actually streamed D:
solitaryyy: What kinda tea
esence: TwitchCock?
mhigr: Hi from Glen Rock!
quackyrabbit: Good stream idea
mtasic85: I am wedding in Serbia and watching this live
oMythra: Georgy boiii
kornez: twitchCook sounds good
larsjuhw: set theory WutFace
bravech: Lol immediately go to an add
ftt0717: Tea it up.
nightknight0000: breakfast with hotz
itsimari: source??
serhejenos: I like cisistentecy in streaming schedule
blasio115: @georgehotz hi
0xc0ffeee: twitch partner wen?11!!?
kornez: and some cocaine LUL
itsxaos: Different tea? PogChamp
KrauserW: waddup
nightknight0000: what kind of tea
peakyDicers: yoo, I just did a coq stream last week
healy1818: You’re a legend!
wormtracer: Hello George!
serhejenos: consistency*
watchVWAVE: Would you recommend that chair
dougboy8989: Geo get back with chronic team we love and need you bro
rkxbz: what a haircut)
knilecrack: ahha
nmay1008: It’s a honor to be able to simply say hello sir, can’t stay
preporyan: Calculus! Oh no!
r1ppyd1ppy: George... why don’t you have any furniture?
liqo13: this stream butters my programming language theory fetish
shaungarris: Hey would love to subscribe but can’t find out how please help
watchVWAVE: The sail
nagimohsen: Will you get back in the jailbreak scene dud to the new discovery?
god_damn: reformed PogChamp
wormtracer: Where is the beard gone?
nagimohsen: Due**
beckles: My favorite Instagram influencer
larsjuhw: set theory DansGame
eduardoadf1: is it discrete math?
oMythra: Gotta take them walks
knilecrack: no
kornez: no bad
Jewishrambo: REFORMED PogChamp
bravech: What's the paper?
mondeverest: TOS
birrdd: macaiy1Kek
samtheprogram: lol
itsxaos: great Job KappaPride
tybutnowyoudie: learned a little bit of coq in university
jens472: !uptime
larsjuhw: How is the $1 jailbreak selling?
esence: why did u get Sayl instead of Embody chair
birrdd: monkaS
Jewishrambo: hairs gonna be everywhere
Luccaasss: What is the best programming language to beginners?
knilecrack: did you figure out how exploit works?
eduardoadf1: DansGame
erichtp: shave head
nagimohsen: Do you think id you tried you wouldve found the exploit if you tried
Jewishrambo: SHAVE HEAD
KrauserW: oh no the keyboard
bravech: Have you made $21m yet
r1ppyd1ppy: Poor keeb
nagimohsen: If you tried*
lefse: Hair in keyboard DansGame
solitaryyy: solitaryyy subscribed at Tier 1.
erichtp: bro wash your hands
3IIiot: twitchcoq sounds like some sort of venereal disease
eduardoadf1: do you wanna prove things to jailbreak the simulation?
minichota: what is geos job atm?
Luccaasss: @georgehotz What is the best programming language to beginners?
bravech: Ew I could hear you pee
0xc0ffeee: instagram verified account when???
god_damn: show dick
ikb79: Back on mac already :D
speeddrawing101: #freegeorgehotz
realsirjoe: watching this after reverse engineering an api
vay_man: hi
larsjuhw: Have you made $21 million dollars off your $1 jailbreak yet? @georgehotz
knilecrack: he still has chicken grease on keyboard
liqo13: @luccaasss php
birrdd: jamming
nagimohsen: He gonna ban yall if yall keep up w the exploit talk LOL
oMythra: Back on the Mac i see
blasio115: monkaW
bool3max: iphone
itsxaos: monkaS
vay_man: okay
filedescriptor: IPHONE IPHONE IPHONE IPHONE IPHONE IPHONE IPHONE IPHONE
eduardoadf1: samsung monkaS
Glymse: glymseMS
jens472: !uptime
birrdd: ratirlCoffee
uraqtlee: why did you decide to use the HHKB>
serhejenos: monkas
trchaosTR: why are you too angry man
realsirjoe: new em or old em?
r1ppyd1ppy: Rawr
larsjuhw: Pitched version WutFace
Luccaasss: Where is the windwos 10?
frotzwagen: iPhone?
solitaryyy: lol
alaouiib: u better with the beard :V
blasio115: Pog
birrdd: what is happening
UniversalGeneve: lionRapgod lionRapgod lionRapgod lionRapgod lionRapgod lionRapgod
god_damn: PogChamp WHO IS THIS GUY
knilecrack: rofl
vay_man: what about copyrights?
filedescriptor: Pog
324B2l: Pog
liqo13: poggers
r3mote: Hey
deluxych: !uptime
Glymse: LUL
GoOnAli: TriEazy
mondeverest: what about self driving cars?
champ900: hey george
eduardoadf1: PogChamp
awesomeo113: Everyone gangsta until Geo starts banning
nagimohsen: grow out the beard again
weird_machine: lokin good
takkeo: Pogg
camkinstrike: cohhK
minichota: copyright strike
filedescriptor: 🔥 🔥 🔥 🔥 🔥
KrauserW: Pog
lucas9o: PogChamp
TRIMES1: what is happening?
thv293: pog
awesomeo113: F for tos
JackB1899: JackB1899 subscribed at Tier 1.
r3mote: macos. finally =)
turboooooo1: 🔥
0xc0ffeee: flowwwwwwww
eax_ebx: раунд.
erichtp: are you partnered yet
solitaryyy: 10/10
stoogethomas: this is geohotz and I'm getting sued by sony
trchaosTR: he raps better than mgk btw
serhejenos: panicBasket
knilecrack: coke is good
nagimohsen: George graduated from RIT right?
god_damn: PogChamp WHO IS THIS
marvin_gow123: wtf
nightknight0000: my neighbors are enjoying this
realsirjoe: geohot this is my first twitch stream 🤪
theendri99: zeb89Ziopeppe
hawsh: talk about talent
oMythra: Ok ok George got a voice on him
Fatmetheny: niceeee
GaNDyRaC: uf
xmase123: rap god
skyhan0: cringe
serhejenos: CurseLit CurseLit CurseLit
r1ppyd1ppy: I didn’t know Chris D’elia streamed
speeddrawing101: shroudPrime shroudPrime shroudPrime shroudPrime shroudPrime shroudPrime shroudPrime shroudPrime shroudPrime shroudPrime shroudPrime shroudPrime
awesomeo113: Is this the real Eminem
blasio115: LOL
joker2k999: Flames!
kornez: LUL
nightknight0000: LOL
filedescriptor: monkaS
birrdd: raiikoHmm
KrauserW: LOL
TRIMES1: real eminen
324B2l: @georgehotz enlarge pdf text pls
awesomeo113: CurseLit CurseLit
Luccaasss: @georgehotz Where is the windows 10?
element04519: hello george
eduardoadf1: are you autistic ?(this is a serious question)
nightknight0000: PogChamp PogChamp
alaouiib: don t show ur twitch earningns gin :D
itsxaos: WINDOWS GONE PogChamp
KrauserW: YEEEEE
kornez: D:
trchaosTR: i think he slept well
realsirjoe: fuck windows
larsjuhw: Geohot vs sony diss track PogChamp
vay_man: wanna bet on how many times he goes to the bathroom?
joker2k999: Oh shiitt. Let go bois
twiggy_io: $200
kornez: do you ship to EU? Kappa
minichota: he killed his laptop?
xNoury: he said the word monkaS
oMythra: I got $2
MacS7n: rap god
nagimohsen: How much
PanicPoint: rude
KrauserW: i'll sub now that windows is gone
trchaosTR: hahahahaha
stoogethomas: do the Sony rap
ragemaster999: what are you reading?
theendri99: @georgehotz What about GNU/Linux?
samdabullet: samdabullet subscribed with Twitch Prime.
stoogethomas: doooo it
joker2k999: LUL yea no more windows bruh
champ900: how do you come up with stream ideas
solitaryyy: Are we still using VS Code?
K0enich: haha
Fatmetheny: How much for the computer?
rkxbz: haha
filedescriptor: me :)
birrdd: macaiy1Muah
awesomeo113: Everyone Gangsta until Geo starts banning
gal40: Wow I haven't caught one of your streams in a long while. Have I missed much or did the stream just start?
trchaosTR: freestyle for sony Kappa
r3mote: hey
eduardoadf1: do you wanna prove things to jailbreak the simulation?
leozusa: How much for the razor?
larsjuhw: TI's verse SeemsGood
stoogethomas: do the Sony rap
r1ppyd1ppy: Put Linux on it!
xNoury: first 30 minutes is always filtering out people LUL
itsxaos: this is a safe space
birrdd: ratirlCoffee keep going
esence: D I C T A T O R S H I P
3ygun: nathanBlub
filedescriptor: time me out pussy @georgehotz
bravech: This is a safe space
Luccaasss: @georgehotz why do you don't use linux?
mondeverest: !rules
nightknight0000: you look like you lost weight
minichota: just use arch
theendri99: @georgehotz What about GNU/Linux?
rkxbz: is he using his macbook?
eduardoadf1: :) ok
vay_man: right
bhad: ur a qt
m1staawesome: fuck a jailbreak seeing you shave and rap on stream is the reason why we watch
god_damn: lmao
twiggy_io: LaTeX <- For Proofs?
Tusk_TV: lol @georgehotz you need more mods papa LUL
sarupk: !uptime
inDOObitablee: This is a warzone
vay_man: hail hotz
noobmenace: I beat my meat to your videos of you coding
awesomeo113: Everyone Gangsta until Geo starts banning
realsirjoe: read plato
trchaosTR: my dad is big fan of you man
bravech: George why don't you use Linux
zeroeagle1: hello
ragemaster999: @georgehotz what are you reading?
thv293: lul
larsjuhw: Rules as clear as Twitch's TOS LUL
MrVikshay: LUL
Lazylion2: Are we allowed to talk about cars that are driving themselves
birrdd: hes not is he
turboooooo1: Easy rule
eduardoadf1: LUL
xNoury: LUL he isnt tho
r1ppyd1ppy: New drinking game. Drink whenever George bans someone
Thecatdaddyy: Thecatdaddyy subscribed with Twitch Prime.
livedb1128: What is the programming challenge today?
knilecrack: it's the tea kicking in
3ygun: nathanYikes
kornez: so many subs LUL
gal40: Did the stream just start?
filedescriptor: @eduardoadf1 don't tell him PepeLaugh
PanicPoint: little early to get that druck
bravech: Can we talk about iphones driving cars
theendri99: @georgehotz Why not GNU/Linux?
de5mond: !uptime
PanicPoint: drunk
paperking01: what are we doing today?
xNoury: 8 minutes ago @gal40
trchaosTR: do you play videogames ?
noobmenace: LUL
Ziv0: @filedescriptor LUL
serhejenos: continuation of coqfiles?
Iliftmymousealot: george i don't want to question your authority but would you mind telling us why you decided to leave windows behind?
eax_ebx: если спросить про айфон на русском, дадут таймаут?))
c252: hi george, how are you?
liqo13: can u do something with univalence axiom in coq?
gal40: Oh ok thanks @xNoury
joker2k999: Back on the coq files?
Tusk_TV: yo chat, we jerkin off? Kappa
CeccoGaming: !uptime
KrauserW: am i allowed to talk about ***** cars if i sub?
larsjuhw: vim LUL
SteveATZ: just wanting to say that your rap is still stuck in my head
bravech: Pls send paper
realsirjoe: vim or vs_code
birrdd: vim Kreygasm
neca420: huh, that was a long day since last stream yesterday Kappa
jens472: coqk
turboooooo1: Holy fuck if you use Vim I use Vim
champ900: how do you come up with stream ideas @georgehotz
the_awoken1: can u please make it a little larger, can't see much on my phone
theendri99: @georgehotz What about GNU/Linux?
Luccaasss: @georgehotz what is your keyboard?
lefse: How many wpm do you have?
ThatGuyChaos: Link to paper?
C4TFive: you need to subscribe to make zoom requests Kappa
xNoury: hhkb i think @luccaasss
stayhc: macOs again DansGame
r1ppyd1ppy: George post your tmux config
Dwayne449: Are you sleeping on the kitchen ?
OMEGA_RAZER: So we’re not talking about iPhone stuff? Does that mean the people banned for talking about it are checkm8’d?
eduardoadf1: is that related to discrete math?
xNoury: the i word monkaS
camkinstrike: existential logic
theendri99: @georgehotz What about GNU/Linux?
antony4s_: pepeHands
oh19contp: >checkm8’d
Tusk_TV: x = blowjob?
oh19contp: why
c252: just use s.t
hue88: creating a formal language ?
itsxaos: maybe this should be done in latex
twiggy_io: TeX formating works in markdown
c252: -> implies an if then
tybutnowyoudie: the second one is also in first-order logic
joker2k999: My damn emacs crashed this am. Updated, now I gotta bt my shit bros...
rkxbz: anyone? how is he opening bash and vim in one window?
filedescriptor: yes
ragemaster999: yes
Aimanissa: bleedPurple bleedPurple
filedescriptor: quantifiers are in FO
c252: yes
fear_ep: Yes it is first order logic
oh19contp: where is he from?
speeddrawing101: yes
turboooooo1: Such that is generally ‘|’
ragemaster999: exists and forall are fo
realsirjoe: mojave completely slowed down my macbook
samtheprogram: @rkxbz tmux
r1ppyd1ppy: @rkxbz tmux
tybutnowyoudie: you can quantify relations in second order logic
c252: higher order logic quantifies over different things like sets
Tyl3r44: what are you doing?
rkxbz: @samtheprogram , @r1ppyd1ppy thank you
tybutnowyoudie: you can have as many quantifiers as you want in first-order logic
phuldr: I wanted to ask about OBD2 and comma.ai, why did you decide to build separate adapters for different car models to effectively just change pin layouts for processing, did you guys played around with hooking all signal pins inside OBD port and handle them in software rather than hardware? or am I missing something? I am surely missing something here but just had an idea that it would allow people to contribute more easily
C4TFive: Whip you coq out
protein8: Link to the paper: https://hal.inria.fr/hal-01094195/document
vay_man: god bless the keyboard
itsxaos: been a while since youve seen coq?
itsxaos: its never long for me KappaPride
twiggy_io: @phuldr no car talk here
Crypod: curvyHmm according to my calculations, the answer exists
oh19contp: keyboard is taking a beating
zgamer0123: george i see u aren't banned, that's good xd
fear_ep: Higher level of logic you can quantify things, in First you can't @georgehotz
protein8: @bravech @ThatGuyChaos link to paper: https://hal.inria.fr/hal-01094195/document
Tusk_TV: lowkey can't wait to build the capital to take 2 years off work and focus on learning programming
bravech: Can't hear you over the sound of you bottoming out
John_DiResta: Well basically prolog
r1ppyd1ppy: @tusk_tv why not start now?
bravech: Thx @protein8
fear_ep: You can have many quatifiers and still it is first order logic
wormtracer: @Tusk_TV U are the definition of procastination
edu4594: rip keyboard
oh19contp: on god
jackdaniels7474: jackdaniels7474 subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months! Ayy
c252: predicate logic = first order logic
zHamish: Hello from Russia
jackdaniels7474: Yo geohot you see the fkin aliens???
bunjr: what keyboard do you use?
mathieu_696: HeyGuys
C4TFive: @jackdaniels7474 he is the alien
c252: @bunjr I think he said it was an hhkb
rkxbz: @bunjr hhkb
vay_man: yes
zHamish: hhkb 2
bunjr: thanks
yusufakcesme: what do you code??
jackdaniels7474: @C4TFive He might be. But I'm talking about the aliens discussed on Joe Rogan yesterday yo
jackdaniels7474: they got fkin reactionless drive
vay_man: this is dope
rkxbz: is it possible to hack into other's computer without leaving any trace?
steinlphd: Maybe proof it for 0 and then the induction case
DasMastah: What's the uptime?
Crypod: !keyboard
blasio115: LUL
tybutnowyoudie: 1 - 2 is not in Nat?
pau1riddle: Is it possible to write actual software that does something useful in Coq?
esence: 2-2 = 0
Tusk_TV: @r1ppyd1ppy virtually broke and ecommerce is easier to make money with limited knowledge, i learn what i can in off time, but financial stability before learning something i want to build a passion for makes most sense
esence: y 0 = 0
knilecrack: this is true
0TestUser: OMEGALUL
c252: this is an example of second order logic: ∀R ∃Q ∃f ∃x ∀y Q(f(x)) → R(y), so you are quantifying the predicates and relations/functions. afiak
Tusk_TV: this looks super complex
vay_man: eys
champ900: but can you do it in JavaScript
vay_man: yes*
nagimohsen: Vim>
kubusiowykubus: but not isnt xD
pau1riddle: The book How To Prove It contains lots of good exercises provable programmatically. It's author wrote some Java interactive prover program
filedescriptor: yes
nagimohsen: What keyboard are you rocking today goodsir
aa_ato: blabla
CLeeMeN: CLeeMeN subscribed with Twitch Prime.
pau1riddle: No, Velleman
jackdaniels7474: george you see the fucking aliens on joe rogan??
itsxaos: LUL
vay_man: lol
itsimari: @Tusk_TV what about just sitting down for it an hour a day
blasio115: Jebaited
jackdaniels7474: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Eco2s3-0zsQ
Lazylion2: xd
jackdaniels7474: here ya go
bravech: George pls add your keyboard to your channel description so people stop asking
itsxaos: Tulsi2020
jackdaniels7474: commander david francor
jackdaniels7474: love u george
esence: it's a short video
johnnyhotlava: George you beautiful man
Protoxus: Protoxus subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 6 months! Good morning
johnnyhotlava: LMAO
KrypticNation: LMAO
yash_rohilla: its the hhkb isnt it?
god_damn: thats crazy you ever tried dmt
Shanmukhosiris: time stamp
bravech: hhkb2
c252: simuleVI
r1ppyd1ppy: @itsimari nah he needs money to learn apparently
Bogz75: roe jogan?
jackdaniels7474: it's the pilot from https://www.nytimes.com/2019/05/26/us/politics/ufo-sightings-navy-pilots.html
kaktoss: "Basic Programming" ok
Tusk_TV: @itsimari i give what time i can, but its a lot to process as i have virtually no experience
itsxaos: @georgehotz are you going to do a podcast like Lex Fridman again? I really enjoyed that
esence: we love coq
Bogz75: lmfao
kornez: im here just for your background music
3ygun: OWL2019ATL
shrewduser: is this similar to prolog?
johnnyhotlava: @esence lolololol
soeim: i'm just here for the joe rogan videos
edu4594: wow
slurpwaffl: lmao how random, i was installing coq to do my logic hw, then i saw u were streaming coq shit
r1ppyd1ppy: George you broke your own rules. Banned
Shanmukhosiris: @jackdaniels7474 time stamp please
champ900: zoom
Tusk_TV: TOS
champ900: 150%
bravech: George ban yourself
jens472: wen eta?
mondeverest: what about pixie tech?
god_damn: this is a dictatorship bro
ISD_Schogol: There are rules?
itsimari: hows 1m2019 going
fear_ep: Computer programmers can't be replaced becuase there
warpoit: was that Coq programming language?
vay_man: funding?
pau1riddle: What is the objective of today's stream?
ISD_Schogol: monkaS
blazelp1: Do u have an apple watch?
E_Pizza: sounds more like a prison tbh monkaS
esence: how do you even go about the checkmark
itsimari: lmao
r1ppyd1ppy: Lawful anarchy!
zeroeagle1: ever checked proB for formal proof?
fear_ep: Computer programmers can't be replaced becuase there can't be an algo that do such job @georgehotz
kornez: who knows
realsirjoe: can u put on some music
mixa010: no tweets?
blazelp1: U switched back to OSX? @georgehotz
johnnyhotlava: You'll get all the followers you want by merit of your sinciput
ghitaionut1: nice haircut dude
Sznurek066: Will backspace.ai create my future ai wife?
edu4594: zoom pls
champ900: Kappa
twiggy_io: 100%
estrangedHD: pob
poopboy7: because its on mac
Bogz75: lets manipulate some strings
knilecrack: just make the font bigger
dorkmo: keystrokes sent to a server for approval
itsxaos: DansGame Electron DansGame
Tusk_TV: Blowjob.ai
tybutnowyoudie: what do you want to different than coq?
Jeppelelle: poopboy7 electron runs like molasses on all platforms
salihyil1: len hacker naber
FadezzHD: Can anybody tell me how he has linux-like terminal on Mac
superragetastic: Are you 30 ?
Protoxus: How do you expect to live forever? Merging with AI includes dying, y'know
autoindent: too small
r1ppyd1ppy: George code me a waifu for when we move to the cloud
hmnvdota: @salihyil1 iyi
Mijauom: @FadezzHD mac supports many types of shells
koduman: it's hard to read
TheAwesomePaul: ctrl shift p -> font size
champ900: zoom pls
johnnyhotlava: yup
johnnyhotlava: BOB
anup_kodlekere: Nice haircut
FadezzHD: @Mijauom I don't know much about that, I have been only programming for a 10 months in C on windows, going to switch to linux in some time, is there anything like that for windows, also can I dm you about it
johnnyhotlava: The mister BOB
twiggy_io: Wait you went to Carnegie Mellon
bravech: Yeah he was on ppp lol
twiggy_io: Will you get me into thier PhD program?
twiggy_io: Kappa
johnnyhotlava: I'm not allowed within two miles of anyone smart enough to get in there
pau1riddle: I'm going through Carnegie Mellon course on Computer Systems: A Programmer's Perspective, I have the book and lectures
johnnyhotlava: Bless
autoindent: George you're getting more and more handsome day by day
yash_rohilla: can you talk about ppp and your experience at ctfs?
itsxaos: @georgehotz there is a computerphile video on lambda calculus
realsirjoe: lambda now I am up for half life
SuntyX: hi
Mijauom: @FadezzHD There is the windows subsystem for Linux, but IMO I don't think it's that great if you're wanting to utilize full Linux. Also, sure.
pau1riddle: Computerphile is for normies
autoindent: dat keyboard sound i like that
Jewishrambo: lol
stupac62: Computerphile is good
twiggy_io: Its a very broad overview
Sparks1Cx: @georgehotz "shift ." speeds up video
jb8e: Hey George! Hows it going?
laz4rz: do you have any math background?
cechov: we haskell now?
gzipped: forsen1
Sznurek066: 3Blue1Brown is PogChamp
INTeaRs: yes
Sparks1Cx: forsenE
suteki1: xqcE
Sznurek066: forsenE
Jewishrambo: lol
tw0st3p: @FadezzHD i've been using wsl ubuntu for simple compiling c code on windows and i have had good results.
champ900: George pro tip google questions you have
laz4rz: @georgehotz maybe one minute physics, I mean do you have university math background
soeim: 1 1=3
gzipped: xqcE
gzipped: forsenE
Mijauom: everyone has a math background
Coraxxi: LUL
itsxaos: people study maths and shit
Jewishrambo: you sir now have a background in math :)
johnnyhotlava: They mean the wall behind you
autoindent: cuz you did historical hack
c252: computer science is math
PanicPoint: No i mean it literally. Do you have a background that you can put behind you with math on it
dorkmo: queen elizabeth knights you with math
FadezzHD: @tw0st3p Thanks a lot!
SuntyX: You prefer MacOS or Windows ?
jaalle: prove things in? Like a unit test xD?
johnnyhotlava: You currently only have a kitchen background
stupac62: @c252 isn’t comp science logic?
c252: logic, graph theory, combinatoric
swagettiyolonaise69: i knew george like coqs
Jewishrambo: coq gachiBASS
johnnyhotlava: Say what you said about coq again
Jeppelelle: write coq extension for python, then you can express in python and prove in coq :D
laz4rz: @georgehotz oneminutephysics was doing good math videos, maybe this is what you were looking for
brtk_10: Most of the programmers don't know what you talking about. People like you who combine programming with advance science I call engineers. I truly believe that car drivers will be replaced with safer and reliable autonomous cars.
c252: @Jeppelelle that would be pretty awesome
Protoxus: brtk_10 Programmers who used theory are just advanced programmers IMO
sidhrth: love you man
dorkmo: ShowLove1
WendellSwan: arnt they computer scientists?
filedescriptor: @Protoxus software engineers
Mijauom: @Protoxus What separates programmer from engineer?
itsxaos: ⊦
edu4594: backspce is about what?
johnnyhotlava: what comes after determines the rules?
swagettiyolonaise69: where is blondie ?
liqo13: left of a turnstile is a context
steinlphd: Turnstile is just implication I guess
Bogz75: 480 viewers pogchamp
WendellSwan: im late, is the goal of this stream to start writing a new programming language?
autoindent: is that formal language?
tybutnowyoudie: t is type of A
esence: press 1 if you dont understand a shit
gzipped: maths crayzbW
ls111: this guy is a mega virgin bois
edu4594: 1
tybutnowyoudie: colon means type of
johnnyhotlava: back space is upset about the programs looking in the mirror for help
alexlucas_: yo
johnnyhotlava: So you're going to make an IA go insane
esence: look at this dude @edu4594
WendellSwan: this kinda looks like some of my homework
pau1riddle: When reading dense math it's easy to run out of memory. Use a text file or pencil and paper or something
vay_man: this is mathboggling
yaus_baus: just woke up to geohot stream, bless up
esence: currying is also in js
autoindent: please english :p
the_suisse: haskell???
Protoxus: Mijauom Good question. I'm not really sure, when it omes to the formal difference between the two. I think to be an engineer, the code you're working on has to have some sort of real-life application - autonomous cars would probably be engineering, coming to think of it
Erciks: 1 and i am studying computer science.. i should quit probably
Protoxus: Erciks Why doy ou think you should quit?
swagettiyolonaise69: cos he doesnt understand shit and neither do i
treestompztv: math xqcWut
aditivity: back on the mac
Ecobat: you don't understand because you haven't tried yet
Ecobat: and just don't have interest in
Erciks: @Protoxus look at george LuL the gap is huge. I can never be good as him not even close. And i am even studying CS i should at least be close but no
swagettiyolonaise69: pardon me for not having any interest in coqs
exenu: don't be disheartened if u don't understand what is going on - only time you need to understand this is when you're working strictly at performance or embedded programming
Ecobat: @Erciks that's bs
johnnyhotlava: autonomous cars ooooor or solo trains with a lottta lottta different tracks lolol
Protoxus: I agree with Ecobat. You shouldn't compare yourself to people who've been to the industry for more than a decade. Compare yourself to how good you were yesterday. Some philosopher probably said some bullshit like that sme point.
bismarckbamfo: Hotz is the greatest of all time.
Jeppelelle: forgot an the / for the last closing <pre>
Ecobat: exactly @Protoxus
Jeppelelle: -an
brtk_10: Hotz is like Spacex!
cechov: do we understand that?
autoindent: black is background and white is letter right?
Ecobat: he's been at it for who knows how long. He didn't get good overnight
Ecobat: put in the work. The rest comes
swagettiyolonaise69: chew some ice then get brain freeze and understand
Narakuwow: George will u ever come to China? we got the best weed
Protoxus: Ecobat I love how we're speaking as if George isn't really here LUL
dorkmo: dorkmo gifted a Tier 1 sub to Jeppelelle! They have given 3 Gift Subs in the channel!
Bogz75: just get high then youll understand
c252: hotz is waaaay cooler than spacex
masterw1tcher: :D
Protoxus: Bogz75 Only if you use psilocybin
esence: guys, i am in a market for a coffee machine, any suggestions
鼻史: finally back on Mac
dorkmo: capresso
Jeppelelle: dorkmo thanks for the gift :D
Ecobat: @Protoxus he's out of it for now ahah completely immersed
greatjohn23: , ai
bravech: Aeropress
superragetastic: Is george part of the yang gang ?
Mijauom: @esence How do you feel about a Keurig?
Protoxus: Ecobat I guess that's true LUL
esence: @Mijauom no
bravech: Look at reddits coffee sub @esence
Protoxus: superragetastic Hopefully!
hourzer: guys why is he doing this?
cechov: so, he is trying to learn coq? or to write a new language for backspace.ai?
Mijauom: vim gang rise up
Alternativeplan: Do you prefer MacOS or Windows for programming?
liqo13: peano as in define zero and succ?
Ecobat: "writing a language we can prove things in"
Protoxus: Alternativeplan I'd say anything with unix is probably better if you want to do backend stuff jgrThink
cechov: @hourzer I think for backspace.ai
dorkmo: @esence capresso mt600
gunnaren: !uptime
swagettiyolonaise69: in an interview he said his favorite os was ubuntu.. cringe
WarSwick: destro7Hype destro7Hype destro7Hype
WarSwick: Thank you for Jailbreaking iphones. bleedPurple PokPikachu FortOne
autoindent: mac OS looks fancy
Ecobat: I'd say unix is better overall. The only reason I don't have Ubuntu or some Linux dist is because I like games
Mijauom: @swagettiyolonaise69 There isn't anything wrong with Ubuntu... It's easy setup for those who want to get going ASAP. I just don't personally like it because it comes with bloat.
averagesizepens: im on ubuntu,i can still play hearthstone and civ5
averagesizepens: LUL
johnnyhotlava: you already KNOW
edu4594: btw i use arch
Alternativeplan: @swagettiyolonaise69 Hmm okay
Mijauom: @edu4594 lol
Jeppelelle: edu4594 classic, never gets old :D
c252: btw I use gentoo
Ecobat: what about League of Legends ? That's the only game I care about
WarSwick: What you think of Kali Linux Geohotz destro7Smug destro7Smug
ImJ4Gu4R: ImJ4Gu4R subscribed at Tier 1.
Hound_The: You can play even LoL on Linux
cechov: yeah, you can
brtk_10: Deeping is better than ios
julien9877: succ : LUL
julien9877: S U C C
edu4594: china...
Protoxus: Hound_The I think Steam has linux-support for about 25% of all their games - I forgot the exact percentage
brtk_10: open source
johnnyhotlava: Then what
Protoxus: I'm watching this stream on linux too B)
Ecobat: @Hound_The quick search showed a lot of bugs on the game ...
iamsod0ne_: how do you get to this level of programming
Usisuvach0: @Protoxus i think dota 2 and cs go for sure work on linux
swagettiyolonaise69: im watching from interpreting 0 and 1 directly from the ethernet cable
averagesizepens: @Ecobat apparently work via wine
edu4594: ik but i dont trust in chinese stuff
c19946: https://github.com/VSCodeVim/Vim you should set some options on vscode setting.json if you need better vim/vscode performance.
Ecobat: hmmm
johnnyhotlava: just need one more
Protoxus: iamsod0ne_ Read books. Code often. Associate yourself with other programmers, so you can learn from them as well. That's what I think, at least
ImJ4Gu4R: Hello
c19946: irani elam hozoor kone
Protoxus: swagettiyolonaise69 Genius
Ecobat: @averagesizepens Patch 9.10 broke it ahah
Hound_The: You just code, practice thats how you get better at anything really
WorthyNull: what is he doing today ?
Ecobat: but yeah, I miss Ubuntu
quickfloor: What happened for that hard life style (Windows) George ?
TheAwesomePaul: reading books is harder but better than online courses
quickfloor: @georgehotz What happened for that hard life style (Windows) George ?
swagettiyolonaise69: it's about "coqs" and "succ"
averagesizepens: i so dont miss windows
WorthyNull: @swagettiyolonaise69 no shit man
imlewpie: haha he lasted 2 weeks on windows
Ecobat: had Gnome on my laptop throughout Uni. Soooo simple
cechov: pathogen?
Protoxus: TheAwesomePaul Depends on what you want to learn, I think. For theory books are better, but of a lot of surface-level stuff, or even semi-advanced stuff, just reading the documentation is superior, since online documentated is updated more frequently
WorthyNull: seriously though
quickfloor: @Ecobat do u like KDE ?
WorthyNull: what is he doing ?
WorthyNull: i didn't understand the title
quickfloor: Coq , It's everyday bro
johnnyhotlava: Shhhh
swagettiyolonaise69: @WorthyNull search coq language on wiki
julien9877: 0! = 1 LUL
Protoxus: @Ecobat Ever heard of Solus? That's what I'm running
autoindent: dat sound
imlewpie: isnt coq the mathsy language ?
Ecobat: @quickfloor no idea
swagettiyolonaise69: it's french so expect the worse
WorthyNull: @swagettiyolonaise69 thanks! I actually thought twitchcoq is a typo lmao
edu4594: the mr robot premiere its today
quickfloor: null != 0
autoindent: ASMR
Protoxus: quickfloor True though
johnnyhotlava: Euro backwards talk
edu4594: is
foxubu: Yay I made it to the stream! :) Hello Everybody
Ecobat: @Protoxus looks interesting!
quickfloor: Coq Asmr with georgehotz
cechov: afaik, he is trying to write a language that allows for priving theorems, like a math language
WorthyNull: alt f4 to solve the problem hotz
Jewishrambo: me
K0enich: oh god
brtk_10: George what is your job? What do you do for living?
Jewishrambo: u need to do parser, lexer
cechov: haskell tried, but breaks with I/O and randomness
julien9877: OH HE'S WRITING A LANGUAGE? PogChamp
johnnyhotlava: Hey lets describe then make the rules cause we're EUROPEAN
c252: not me :(
liqo13: build an AST first?
Protoxus: julien9877 How else would you spend a sunday as fine as this? jgrREE
cechov: LOL
nexscion: bruh this channel got too high iq fur me
steinlphd: Parsing is really easy with parser combinators
Protoxus: nexscion Don't worry, it's too high IQ for everyone.
averagesizepens: gallina means chicken female
Sznurek066: I wonder if most of chat is US or EU.
quickfloor: https://softwarefoundations.cis.upenn.edu/lf-current/ImpParser.html
WorthyNull: @nexscion iq is a myth man
steinlphd: In Haskell at least but I think there’re libraries for python
Protoxus: Sznurek066 EU here
Mobius5: @WorthyNull Kappa
Protoxus: WorthyNull No it's not.
johnnyhotlava: I'm eating crayons without the wrapper so this is just cosplay for me
WorthyNull: the foundation for it is so weak and shaky
Jewishrambo: preprocess -> lexical analysis -> parsing/syntax -> semantics -> generation @georgehotz kind of remember it
ImJ4Gu4R: IQ : Am I joking to you?
johnnyhotlava: @ImJ4Gu4R lol
WorthyNull: you can only get verified results as far as the amount of iq test takers which is so minimal
Jeppelelle: What? They just wrote an abstract language without lexer/parser/visitor etc?
WorthyNull: you cannot get reliable statistical results that way
Yrratic: wow, long time no see @georgehotz
johnnyhotlava: Yeah man tape measures are bullshit cause if my dad makes one using his fingers it isn't accurate
Jewishrambo: wtf is coq anyway lol
swagettiyolonaise69: do u even google
Protoxus: WorthyNull Everyone who has to do military service has to take an IQ test. This is the case for most developed countries. In the US, you're not allowed to serve in the army if you have an IQ less than 87. They want to recruit as many as they can. It's not just for fun they're using IQ tests.
st47ik: back to Mac PogChamp
twiggy_io: @Protoxus Thats not true.
cobaltstark1: are you using a laptop?
tw0st3p: @geohotz for python lexx/yacc, check out ply github.com / dabeaz / ply maybe.
Protoxus: twiggy_io Oh really?
Jewishrambo: @Protoxus isnt that what peterson said or somethin lol
josalt: Hey Everyone :)
twiggy_io: @Protoxus Yeah im positive abvout it.
Mijauom: @twiggy_io It is though? Jordan Peterson has done a lot of talks about it. It is illegal to allow peeps without a certain IQ into the military.
WorthyNull: @Protoxus the fact that some org somewhere using iq doesnt mean that iq tests are scientifically robust
Jewishrambo: Do it in C PogChamp Kreygasm
st47ik: in rust Kappa
WorthyNull: besides, you cannot actually measure intelligance when you cannot define it in the first place.
Jeppelelle: WorthyNull IQ test is BS but IQ itself isnt
edu4594: do it in assembly x86
johnnyhotlava: oh dear god
sa7b: Hi AsexualPride
Protoxus: Jeppelelle How do you define one without the other?
johnnyhotlava: OMG
WorthyNull: @Jeppelelle my arguemnt is against IQ itself
Jeppelelle: WorthyNull: then you are wrong
Roudkill: Do it in cobol :D
st47ik: What do you think of Rust-lang George?
brtk_10: Forget about coq do python and javascript.
cobaltstark1: are you using a laptop?
Protoxus: WorthyNull Well, I suppose it depends on how you define intelligence, and IQ. But I've honestly heard a lot of people saying the foundation of IQ isn't very stable - I'd love to hear your take on it in depth to be honest
WorthyNull: the fact that you can get higher score in a considerable IQ test with 30 min of practice means it has nothing to do with intelligance
johnnyhotlava: They don't want you to have it
MonkaSupreme: oh shit its my boy geohot
Irkanu: "parsing" folder?
Jeppelelle: WorthyNull: yeah, so then you are against testing, not IQ
johnnyhotlava: You don't haaaav it
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: @WorthyNull some people dont understand that simple fact
Couchmann941: page 2 WutFace
st47ik: LUL
Protoxus: WorthyNull Which specific IQ test are you talking about?
brtk_10: Please install DARK READER to chrome
superragetastic: I got 125 IQ it's over
st47ik: i got 127 Kappa
WorthyNull: @Jeppelelle you're argument sounds like hey IQ is a robust scientific measure for intelligance but there isn't any actual test to measure the very thing that it tries to measure ? -> such a measure doesn't exist...
Protoxus: The only two I really know of are RPM and WAIS.
edu4594: buzzfeed iq test
Erciks: LULW
Protoxus: WorthyNull Yeah, I'd agree with that statement. No IQ without tests.
Jeppelelle: WorthyNull: there is alot of stuff that is untestable that actually exist
Protoxus: Jeppelelle But how can we know for sure, if we can't test it?
johnnyhotlava: Life results test it
WorthyNull: @Jeppelelle if it's untestable then how can we say that it actually exists without observing it ?
MatiGoG: 360p stream yay
johnnyhotlava: You're general ability to achieve a defined goal
johnnyhotlava: your
routerbomber: Finally, you have changed back to macOS 😄
Irkanu: @georgehotz You asked about where the parsing was. I just tuned in, but noticed a "parsing" folder
st47ik: guys is Rust worth it for 2020?
superragetastic: Take nootropics to increase your IQ it's proof fool.
Jeppelelle: WorthyNull CERN test the decay for example, it does not test the actual concrete physics
GiantSweater: no
MatiGoG: yes
johnnyhotlava: Rust looks like a running simulator
johnnyhotlava: lol
GiantSweater: the duality of man
tw0st3p: ocaml parsing: https://v1.realworldocaml.org/v1/en/html/parsing-with-ocamllex-and-menhir.html
Gtxgaming23: do you even prog bro?
quickfloor: Everybody Knows @georgehotz Hate java :D
st47ik: same
xxxdeja: How did you not get banned after last stream LOL
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: who actually loves java
TreborRentro: just write a parser
st47ik: google loves java
Lazysloth: xxxdeja what happened last stream
Mijauom: @xxxdeja yes, don't leave us hanging
johnnyhotlava: Google has been thoroughly defeated by seo nerds
Irkanu: bogaHey bogaHey bogaHey bogaHey
flitcho: Hey george and chat
xxxdeja: father blessed us with his twitch money analytics
johnnyhotlava: BROKEN
Shanmukhosiris: is he creating a new language ??
st47ik: VoHiYo
autoindent: python4 !!!
st47ik: PogChamp
Protoxus: Shanmukhosiris Seems so
autoindent: i want to learn
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: python4 eta?!
tw0st3p: @georgehotz terminal font size please
Shanmukhosiris: then nobody knows what hes doing !!!!!
st47ik: where's 3to4 smh
brtk_10: Use DarkReader plesae :(
julien9877: @georgehotz just write your own parsing libraray LUL
brtk_10: https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/dark-reader/eimadpbcbfnmbkopoojfekhnkhdbieeh?hl=pl
johnnyhotlava: Not gonna do it
st47ik: darktheme all the things 4Head
johnnyhotlava: Lark is buns
johnnyhotlava: cheeks
ImJ4Gu4R: Yeaa 1 for dark theme.
quickfloor: Why you typing when you can just think about it ? "Let it type" (2022 ads on youtube)
WorthyNull: @Protoxus IQ test is only meaningful when you have a fucking massive big chunk of samples, it allegedly measures the difference between people in their ability for abstraction. It has a normal (gaussian) destribution graph. in Such collection sample methods you cannot actually derive meaningful results that maps to 7 billion of people from a considerablly small sample. it does however mean that people who took the test have difference results **IN SOLVING THE TEST ITSELF**.
ImJ4Gu4R: arrgh my eyes BibleThump
st47ik: PogChamp
Jewishrambo: PogChamp
Jewishrambo: PogChamp parser PogChamp
ImJ4Gu4R: Kreygasm
quickfloor: Kreygasm yes
st47ik: Keyboard smashing SMOrc
johnnyhotlava: @WorthyNull what happens when the results of the test correlate to different life outcomes?
Protoxus: @WorthyNull Yeah, that makes sense. You need a lot of samples for it to be reliable statistically. Do you know how many people have taken IQ tests? (Asking because I don't know myself)
brtk_10: Do you never listen to music during work?
r00tdk: What is going on ?
WorthyNull: @Protoxus And here comes the second arguemnt, the test itself is arbitrary in its nature. 1. we don't have annnny idea how intelligance is formed let alone quantifiying it 2. can you actually try and make a test in italian language that tests the level of the takers ? most likely no BECAUSE YOU DONT SPEAK ITALIAN (maybe you do but you go the point).
r00tdk: Bnf thing ?
r00tdk: Can anyone tell
kkkkkkkkkkkkkkwwwww: 500 viewers no one talking?
r00tdk: What is he trying to do ?
johnnyhotlava: @WorthyNull pattern recognition forms across all languages
miloeu: 40 viewers 460 bots
st47ik: @r00tdk the title bruh
brtk_10: @georgehotz Please install DarkReader our eyes hurt :( https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/dark-reader/eimadpbcbfnmbkopoojfekhnkhdbieeh?hl=pl
johnnyhotlava: Matrices tests
WorthyNull: @Protoxus it has the implicit notion that test makers have the ultimate ability of abstraction to be able to measure OTHER PEOPLE'S ABILITY TO ABSTRACT
st47ik: im a bot MrDestructoid
Protoxus: WorthyNull RPM IQ tests doesn't use language though
st47ik: George please i want to know BibleThump do you hate Rust?
WorthyNull: @Protoxus that was not my point. I'm coming to a generalization to explain the very nature of tests
WorthyNull: the very nature of tests requires the test maker to be on a very higher level of knowledge to be able to test accuratly other test takers.
hohaleom: guess whos back on a brand new basic hack waddap yooo
FoxMcWeezer: FoxMcWeezer subscribed at Tier 1.
riaddo: doctorWARCRY doctorWARCRY doctorWARCRY
Protoxus: WorthyNull I'll just think about the argument you're making for a moment.
WorthyNull: we don't actually know for a fact that IQ test makers have higher ability to abstract whatever the hell that means
johnnyhotlava: If I had to be five feet from a target to hit it with an arrow and I wanted to test the accuracy of an expert and made them shoot from 50 feet could I accurately judge them knowing the target after making them go through a more difficult route?
cechov: drops mic
st47ik: Coq Kappa
lycuz: !uptime
kkkkkkkkkkkkkkwwwww: @lycuz 1:10
WorthyNull: And there is the fact that nobody every seems to bother htinking baout for god knows why which is that you can actually train for a 30 min and get higher results. how is that actually an accurate measure of the intelligance?
quickfloor: @georgehotz Coding with Food asmr will be great
johnnyhotlava: YOu cannot do that for a stanford binet test
WorthyNull: Eeeeend scene and pardon my typos and stupid language
st47ik: ever tried Rust George?
johnnyhotlava: each test is different
Jeppelelle: What happened to tomcr00se?
champ900: @georgehotz do you think the government's watching right now
lexhonecker: Hi guys what is George up to in this stream?
Protoxus: WorthyNull I'll just try to rephrase your argument in my own words, just to make sure we have an agreement on what it is. So, you can't make a test involving intelligence higher than yourself, because you'd have to make questions that are more "intelligent" than you are yourself. Is that the gist of it?
speeddrawing101: @riaddo porco dio?
st47ik: SeemsGood
riaddo: Dio cane
superragetastic: @WorthyNull I guess a lot of the science behind IQ tests deal with correlations possibly ? Correlations with life outcomes, career choices etc. I think something is being measured.
speeddrawing101: hahahah
Jewishrambo: drepessive music
brtk_10: gay song?
st47ik: @lexhonecker writing a parser for coq
Jeppelelle: Protoxus and WorthyNull still, you only disprove IQ standardized test which everyone already knows is BS, you have done nothing so far to disprove IQ itself as you originally claimed
Protoxus: superragetastic Yeah, I think IQ is very related to psychometrics. Not sure though
Protoxus: Jeppelelle I'm not trying to disprove IQ.
WorthyNull: @Protoxus yes
trchaosTR: yo george which phone do you use ?
st47ik: LUL
eazyxlan: Whatcha typing on?
hoffs: hhkb
gimmighyone: I'm completely new to programming, how should i approach the subject?
Protoxus: WorthyNull I don't know if that's a good argument or not. Maybe I'm just not able to comprehend it. But humans can create a chess computer that's a lot smarter than its creator. Wouldn't the same be the case for IQ test questions? - I don't know how IQ test questions are derived, but I suppose this could be one way.
superragetastic: I want to invest in a HHKB but Idk
WorthyNull: @Jeppelelle I believe different people have different abilities and some people are smarter than others but I don't believe that you have a standarized way to measure that
stategamer: a language to prove things in? like Haskell?
brtk_10: Comeback to python and javascript. It was already enough complicated.
azstreamz99: what is he coding ?
Sznurek066: @gimmighyone depends what do you want to do.
WorthyNull: @Protoxus chess computers aren't actually smart at all, they're just faster, they simulate 100 gazzilion outcome that's it
Jeppelelle: stategamer You prove things in Matlab too i guess? (asking since i don't know anything about Matlab)
st47ik: @gimmighyone i suggest to start the very basics like what a programming language actually is (variables, conditions, loops, functions....) there's a lot of resources out there so try em and see which one helps you
superragetastic: @gimmighyone javascript for all things. Many people will tell you otherwise but ignore them.
stategamer: @Jeppelelle I have (luckily) never used Matlab
gimmighyone: @Sznurek066 i'm studying finance and econometrics, so something that can be useful in that field
gimmighyone: @st47ik ok thanks
brtk_10: Let's vote what language George should code: 0 - python, 1- javascript, 2-Coq shit
cechov: matlab then, but stata and eviews have their own language
brtk_10: 0
Protoxus: WorthyNull That's not true. Chess computers use moves that normal chess players can't comprehend, no matter how much time they use. There's a lot of chess theory, and chess computers are far superior to that
Protoxus: brtk_10 42
st47ik: javascript is great for beginners and yes it can be useful for finance and more
swagettiyolonaise69: 2 jk
Sznurek066: Learn Python and than operations on big data machine learning
Sznurek066: than* ml
Protoxus: st47ik I think whichever language you should use depends on your use case. Although it's true that some languages can be used to do more advanced things than others jgrThink
preporyan: He look so angry when he is working LUL
WorthyNull: @superragetastic differnt life outcomes are rarely measured and there is literally millions of factors that takes part in. maybe you're just disadvantaged from poor family went to poor schools and didn't really learn much. this doesnt mean that because they have lower iq they had worse life choices.
st47ik: @Protoxus true
Jeppelelle: Sznurek066 why use the slowest language for ML?
swagettiyolonaise69: george should code in PHP
prafaeltsantos: OMG the mac is back Kappa Kreygasm
st47ik: Kappa
Protoxus: Jeppelelle Go for ML? Go or no go? :P
저그매니아: will it be on youtube?
Graphityy: "Basic Programming"
Protoxus: swagettiyolonaise69 LUL
Jeppelelle: Protoxus, depends on what implementation OpenCV for go has alot of translation layers to C
st47ik: @저그매니아 i think so, on the comma ai archive
MonkaSupreme: who gets what he is doing?
swagettiyolonaise69: @Protoxus is PHP case sensitive ?
syflom: is your monitor 1440p, or what is it?
Shanmukhosiris: @Graphityy LUL LUL
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: @Jeppelelle i think python is just the most popular language for ML in general. i heard it has great frameworks to work with
Protoxus: swagettiyolonaise69 Don't remember, it's been a while since I've coded PHP
gimmighyone: tumbluPapurino
MonkaSupreme: type 1 if you get what he is doing
Shanmukhosiris: 0
저그매니아: @st47ik Thx :)
WhyKnot321: 2
CaptainAshtar: how do you change from windows to mac and backwards is that virtual machines or different machines in your home?
stalys_: 0
MonkaSupreme: 0
st47ik: np ;)
fupariox15: THE SUCCCC
swagettiyolonaise69: @Protoxus the answer is yes and no
brtk_10: Please install DarkReader our eyes hurt :( https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/dark-reader/eimadpbcbfnmbkopoojfekhnkhdbieeh?hl=pl
Jeppelelle: i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: Yeap; python for quick development but its not a low lever language
superragetastic: @WorthyNull yeah, environment is pretty important to give people the best shot.
Jeppelelle: i cant spell today, sorry to everyone that is reading :D
Protoxus: swagettiyolonaise69 How so?
WorthyNull: @Protoxus Yes they don't comprehend it becuase it doesn't follow the general pattern of how to play chess. this doesn't mean that computers "knows" how to play chess. they just simulate millions of games and have a mathematical measure of which position is better which by the way is usually hard coded rules put by programmers
root_user_198: what music is plaing in the background? lol
swagettiyolonaise69: @Protoxus look it up it's just ridiculous
st47ik: i wasted too much time in my life George LUL
jaimecres: asd
Protoxus: swagettiyolonaise69 I will. I know a lot of people hate PHP because of things such as what you just mentioned :P
superragetastic: Feynman didn't care about IQ.
CaptainAshtar: @st47ik who doesn't
Protoxus: WorthyNull That's a pretty good argument.
kingkong3211: yo
fa_k: he moved from windows to mac lol
ImJ4Gu4R: Piano pls
st47ik: @CaptainAshtar george Kappa
gimmighyone: is that post-rock music? tumbluABBO
WorthyNull: @Protoxus Neural Network as well jsut have a mathematical function to assess and self learn which is anther hard coded formula put by human. there is absolutely no evidance that computers "understand" what they
WorthyNull: what they're actually calculating
fa_k: christiancucks on chat i guess
brtk_10: I stop wasting my time and go to the swimming pool with a girlfriend.
CaptainAshtar: what is this music style called? which geo is listening to?
Protoxus: Well, understanding what you're calculating and having the ability to calculate something isn't really the same.
st47ik: sounds like Alternative Rock or something like that
WorthyNull: @Protoxus my dude the argument for and against IQ literally never ends
Jeppelelle: Same style as Greenday and the like?
CaptainAshtar: or blink182?
st47ik: kinda
Narakuwow: George has so many hairs
st47ik: sub-genres are kinda messy
brtk_10: Please install DarkReader It's really cool https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/dark-reader/eimadpbcbfnmbkopoojfekhnkhdbieeh?hl=pl
st47ik: darktheme boi
CaptainAshtar: what is this dark reader do?
Protoxus: WorthyNull Yeah, but aren't those all theoretical arguments? I think you'd need to dig pretty far into how IQ is actually measured, how the tests are made, what the results implicate on a psychometric level etc. to be able to assess how reliable IQ is. Even though it may not be backed by great theory.
Jeppelelle: Why so many decorations in this language? It would drive me nuts
CaptainAshtar: the keyboard have very nice sound on the keys
CaptainAshtar: what kind of keyboard is that
fa_k: "special algorithm"
Protoxus: CaptainAshtar It's not the keyboard that makes it sound nice, it's George's fingers.
CaptainAshtar: @Protoxus :D lol
st47ik: @CaptainAshtar it's the Happy Hacking Keyboard Kappa
CaptainAshtar: @st47ik thanks bro
st47ik: no letters on it
CaptainAshtar: no letters on it ?
thuganalyst: Who needs letters am I right
nicentra: Hi George, how are you
st47ik: look it up LUL
Kultiviert: the grammar is unclear please rephrase
st47ik: what does it compile/transpile to George?
WorthyNull: @Protoxus they are theoretical arguments yes.
hotplay: @georgehotz if you wanna be the next ninja i suggest looking into changing the category to Science and Technology
domas3210: I just came here... what is he doing? for what purpose?
WorthyNull: @Protoxus and you made a good point
sirvapealots: @hotplay are you fucking kidding LUL he needs to be in "Just Chatting" section
superragetastic: Music pls
Protoxus: brtk_10 Just installed it on Firefox, thanks for the tip. Please stop spamming though jgrGame
sirvapealots: @georgehotz you should put yourself in Just Chatting section so your stream is more discoverable LUL
fa_k: mods
kingkong3211: whats the point of keyboard without letters
superragetastic: Mod me george SwiftRage
st47ik: SMOrc chat
domas3210: Please don't spam :) Please don't spam :) Please don't spam :) Please don't spam :) Please don't spam :) Please don't spam :) Please don't spam :) Please don't spam :)
s0rrz: now i dont wanna install dark reader
s0rrz: at all
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: @sirvapealots you can get banned if you are using the wrong categories
sirvapealots: @superragetastic Yawn
domas3210: sorry it was my sister...
JUST_5HEAD: yo wtf
st47ik: bruh moment
CaptainAshtar: :D imaginary sister?
fa_k: mods ban this guy
fa_k: stop promoting your extension polish cukc
Protoxus: WorthyNull But yeah, discussing IQ theoretically and IQ "practically" are two completely different things. And I think if you can see that has relevance in the real world, the theory isn't that important. Unless you're a nerd like most people here, who put theory above all else :P
JUST_5HEAD: @brtk_10 👈 this guy
xNoury: thank you
sirvapealots: @georgehotz LUL
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: @JUST_5HEAD snitch cmonBruh
nicentra: Thanks george
atom9006: LUL LUL
superragetastic: lol
zgamer0123: me
knilecrack: noone
Protoxus: I can mod you.
zgamer0123: :v
Jewishrambo: ME
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: i dont :)
Jewishrambo: ME PLEASE
JUST_5HEAD: fuck that DansGame
fa_k: LULW
atom9006: oooh no
fa_k: LUL
superragetastic: MOD ME
MonkaSupreme: i volunteer
kkkizune: !mod
jpict: jpict subscribed with Twitch Prime.
zgamer0123: I wanted to :v
FoxMcWeezer: What’s up dude
Narakuwow: luaPOP luaLUL
Jewishrambo: PogChamp
knilecrack: someone will ruin your stream
johnnyhotlava: Moooooooderator
Narakuwow: me
RealOden: Mod me, I sub after Kappa
serhejenos: mod me
Protoxus: POGGERS
atom9006: please
Lusion: I'm not a subscriber but I once played one on tv
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: PogChamp
exenu: make me mod
T_boltsniper : Jewishrambo Pog
jpict: please!
Narakuwow: mod me luaPOP
ImJ4Gu4R: me or i wont continue sub
nexscion: that's wild
JUST_5HEAD: dont mod me
serhejenos: Mod me
exenu: I know how to make coffee
ImJ4Gu4R: hahah
RandomSil1: I'll take mod too :)
fa_k: @Protoxus NOT MODDED LUL
stalys_: <message deleted>
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: LUL
superragetastic: Mod meee ; - ;
adminuae: Kappa
Jeppelelle: Everone gets a mod
Protoxus: POGGERS
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: <message deleted>
fa_k: <message deleted>
st47ik: SeemsGood
Jewishrambo: None pipe up
serhejenos: yaaa
abk467: congrats bois
Protoxus: Jewishrambo serhejenos Congratulations
anup_kodlekere: Why don't you divide the screen into two halves
domas3210: <message deleted>
riaddo: doctorJAWLINE
ImJ4Gu4R: WutFace
JUST_5HEAD: INTERNET JANITORS LUL
xNoury: we all chilling in here
atom9006: @georgehotz subscribed for 8 months
sirvapealots: @georgehotz you should put yourself in Just Chatting section so your stream is more discoverable
superragetastic: Music please ?
st47ik: at least there will be less spam now
johnnyhotlava: That's riiiiight
Protoxus: JUST_5HEAD Pretty much LUL
sirvapealots: @georgehotz randomers can't find your stream under "Basic Programming" because they're wayy too normy LUL
jpict: Party1 Party1 Party1 Party1 Party1 Party1 Party1 Party1 Party1 Party1 Party1 Party1
i4cc8a9morw8kfrh: <message deleted>
byLeandroid: Preferences error hahaha
ImJ4Gu4R: "Basic"
DasMastah: "Computer says no"
exenu: Type 1 if u want @Protoxus to be unmodded and you to become a new mod
domas3210: where is the install dark theme on chrome now LUL
Protoxus: 1
RealOden: @sirvapealots And what makes you think normies in "Just Chatting" wants to watch programming streams?
ImJ4Gu4R: RedCoat
kluo84: dont distract George lol... first time can see him live...
Protoxus: exenu Checkmate.
exenu: farrrrk
sirvapealots: @RealOden that's how trends get picked up my dude
exenu: youre to smart
CaptainAshtar: what is hots doign right now actully?
johnnyhotlava: Mac not allowing it it's against their aesthetic lololol
JUST_5HEAD: this is basic programming, everyone can watch it Kappa
sirvapealots: @RealOden How do you think "Just Chatting" even happened in the first place LUL
Protoxus: JUST_5HEAD jgrTARD
Aimanissa: FortOne FortOne FortOne FortOne FortOne
sirvapealots: It wasn't some sort of fucking fluke LUL
JUST_5HEAD: @Protoxus LUL
st47ik: just chatting while doing basic programming Kappa
ImJ4Gu4R: Twitch does hv the api for the live notification?
nicentra: @CaptainAshtar He seems to be creating a programming language as far as I understand
mtm2: !playlist
CaptainAshtar: :D wtf
CaptainAshtar: really?
sirvapealots: @st47ik Exactly; Motherfuckers play passive games while chatting all the time
Sydowh: Can't see anything but it doesn't matter coz I don't understand
RealOden: @sirvapealots It's a place for people that want to do IRL stuff and can't be labelled under a category. However, there are sections for technology and programming :)
Jeppelelle: But seriously, what feature does Gallina provide if George have to write this much support code to get it to work?
sirvapealots: @RealOden You don't have to play fucking games to be under "Just Chatting"
Protoxus: ImJ4Gu4R Twitch's API documentation is really crappy tbh. But I think for notifications you'd have to look at the Kraken API
JUST_5HEAD: your head hides editor @georgehotz
JUST_5HEAD: your big head*
MonkaSupreme: all have succ?
CaptainAshtar: if that's basic programing then i'm king of england
Shanmukhosiris: @CaptainAshtar he is creating a phaser for coq
sirvapealots: @RealOden Quote it from TOS or just stop talking shit lmfao
Protoxus: CaptainAshtar A pleasure to make your acquaintance, Your Highness! Kappa
sirvapealots: fucking TOSfrongs LUL
Shanmukhosiris: @CaptainAshtar ENGLAND IS MY CITY
fillmyvoid: is this another episode of the coq files?
johnnyhotlava: Woah woah
fillmyvoid: poggers
Sydowh: What's Twitchcoq ?
RealOden: @sirvapealots Dropped too many times? Why so toxic?
Vendombra: hey can you hack some brazzers premium accounts for me
Protoxus: Sydowh It's coq but for Twitch
CaptainAshtar: :D
exenu: wtf is coq?
johnnyhotlava: basic programming depending on if you're george or not
johnnyhotlava: a party of one
sirvapealots: @Protoxus He's being passive aggressive -> RealOden
Shanmukhosiris: @Vendombra LUL
Protoxus: sirvapealots Who is?
ImJ4Gu4R: @Protoxus agree with you, twitch APi is a bit crappy. Thansk for the keyword ill take a look.
RealOden: @sirvapealots You are such a baby LUL
JUST_5HEAD: i want to be an internet janitor too :)
CaptainAshtar: I can't write a simple calculator he is writing a whole phaser ...
sirvapealots: @Protoxus RealOden; I've asked him where it says on TOS and deflects it like a narcissist
fa_k: LUL
johnnyhotlava: WOAH
Protoxus: ImJ4Gu4R I mean, the API works fine, it's just the documentation that sucks. tmijs is the optimal API for Twitch
johnnyhotlava: NVC guys NVC
johnnyhotlava: Non violent communication
johnnyhotlava: Feelings and needs maaan
exenu: this is not even programming
exenu: wtf is this
sirvapealots: @exenu that's what I said LUL
CaptainAshtar: this is GOD mode
st47ik: @exenu it is wdm?
exenu: no its not, what language is that
exenu: its not even a language
st47ik: thats the point Kappa
serhejenos: goerge is writing parser in python
Protoxus: sirvapealots Well, I guess that's to be expected in a Twitch chat. He's not really swearing or anything.
exenu: then where is the python ide
fa_k: @exenu Brainlet moment
exenu: im so confused
johnnyhotlava: George is building a ladder to his goal of making his programs look in the mirror
johnnyhotlava: and recognize their existence
st47ik: @exenu u dont need the python ide bro
serhejenos: hi is using vim
exenu: explain me this
CaptainAshtar: who uses python ide now a days bro
serhejenos: first you need to define a grammar for parser
exenu: why does everyone say python is easy but each time i watch george it doesn't even look like python
alxhotel: writing a parser for coq ?
CaptainAshtar: there is no easy in life
nicentra: @exenu vim is a terminal based editor. He doesn't use an IDE because he doesn't need one
johnnyhotlava: The parser he found is butt cheeks so like a god he's like I'll fix it
Jewishrambo: \n
exenu: why is he using a vim over an ide?
st47ik: @exenu it's easy for basic stuff
fa_k: Why should be everything use an IDE?
johnnyhotlava: ohhhh
CaptainAshtar: i ahte ide
swagettiyolonaise69: to be more l33t
JUST_5HEAD: @georgehotz move camera right side bro
nicentra: @exenu Because if you're good at vim you can write code a lot faster
johnnyhotlava: cant
CaptainAshtar: correcting everything i wrote
johnnyhotlava: wooooow
Protoxus: exenu I think what they mean is that understanding the syntax is easy, compared to other languages. But understanding basic python is easy, and understanding advanced python is hard. I guess that's the case for all languages and everything in general :P
st47ik: vim is lightweight and and also l33t Kappa
johnnyhotlava: HOLY SHIT
johnnyhotlava: WHAT A RUDE SYSTEM
Sim_Ayo: why are you back on mac from windows
ImJ4Gu4R: @Protoxus Ya i know what u mean :P
MonkaSupreme: https://regex101.com/r/G0cYsc/1
CaptainAshtar: because this project which he is doing is on his mac machine
jpict: NotLikeThis1
CaptainAshtar: enviorment
deed02392: Sim_Ayo he was only on Windows to make the iPhone exploit more challenging
johnnyhotlava: @MonkaSupreme i'm erect
Protoxus: MonkaSupreme That's funny
MonkaSupreme: who wouldn't be erect
deed02392: johnnyhotlava you're erect over coq
johnnyhotlava: lolololol
st47ik: LUL
deed02392: lol
steinlphd: this paper describes a tool for automated equivalence proofs of programs: https://www.kestrel.edu/home/people/eric.smith/dissertation.pdf
MonkaSupreme: > https://regex101.com/r/G0cYsc/1/ TehePelo
Protoxus: MonkaSupreme Don't post the same link multiple times jgrGame
johnnyhotlava: @steinlphd publish date?
steinlphd: 2011
nicentra: @georgehotz What phone are you using these days? Any reason why?
johnnyhotlava: Ahhh
Protoxus: nicentra Nokia 105 is the way to go. No apps, no internet, just texts and phone calls.
aidanpaledot: What about checkm8? :(
Jeppelelle: Can't one open bash inside VIm? Seems painfuil to switch tmux area every test cycle
Lutefisk123: What is coq, AKA twitchcoq?
nicentra: @Protoxus I had a nokia brick as my first phone
fa_k: language you can prove things on
st47ik: @Lutefisk123 https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Coq
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz will it be this unhackable language that we'll write world simulations in (like the one we live in)?
fillmyvoid: D:
st47ik: D:
Jeppelelle: George hates us
JUST_5HEAD: thank you :)
Jeppelelle: :D
serhejenos: Kappa Kappa Kappa
Maybay254: Vietnam
Lutefisk123: @st47ik Thanks!
StupidGladiator: what language is this ?
st47ik: np
jpict: Scoops1 :)
johnnyhotlava: Term is a euro word
Protoxus: nicentra Me too, I'm getting a nokia 3310 again soon
johnnyhotlava: ol post command b.s.
Rezii27: hello
Purrplecat: The man himself purrplT reckGasp
nicentra: @Protoxus I recently picked my iPhone Max Pro lol I'm way too dependent on the luxury of a smartphone
deed02392: i have a mate 20 pro and iphone 7
johnnyhotlava: Why
Jeppelelle: nicentra there is always room for a burner
Protoxus: nicentra Yeah, I have a smartphone as well. They've all started looking the same though :P
johnnyhotlava: Why is parsing as a binder.
johnnyhotlava: it
deed02392: i think i will upgrade the iphone to XR due to checkmi
Protoxus: deed02392 I remember watching the opening event for Mate 10 Pro. Is your 20 pro any good?
deed02392: checkm8*
johnnyhotlava: Holy shit
Protoxus: It parses POGGERS
st47ik: PogChamp
kluo84: i am lost :(
SlevinKelevrar: SlevinKelevrar subscribed with Twitch Prime.
serhejenos: poggers
Protoxus: kluo84 We all are.
johnnyhotlava: This mans "I thinks" are 100% right
nicentra: @Jeppelelle I don't do shady stuff I would need a burner for @Protoxus I know but gotta have the new shit, my mom is getting my 8 though
Purrplecat: purrplT purrplT purrplT
twistanoname: !uptime
Protoxus: nicentra I don't need a burner either, I just use my non-smartphone whenever I want to connect more with the real world without any distractions :P
deed02392: @Protoxus dude I love it. best phone i've ever owned
sulozor: do you think you could use a NN to write Coq proofs? @georgehotz
nicentra: @Protoxus Real World? What's that
Protoxus: nicentra r/outside
deed02392: @nicentra he means AFK
st47ik: WutFace
Azermite: can someone explain what is happenning ? :)
Purrplecat: Hey George how are you doing this fine evening? purrplFlex purrplPog
nicentra: @Protoxus Nah man, it's full of bugs and glitches and the meta never changes
Protoxus: Azermite No. No one can, because no one understands what's happening. :P
serhejenos: George is writing parser for small coq file
deed02392: lool
st47ik: small coq Kappa
deed02392: NotLikeThis
Lutefisk123: Kappa
Protoxus: nicentra What you call bugs I call features. The meta changes, just pretty slowly.
sulozor: he is probably writing a parser for Coq which is a language thats used in order to prove theorems and math stuff
Jeppelelle: Its kinda fun that Roomba, i vacuum cleaner have the same CPU as the state of the art phones had when i grew up :D
Jeppelelle: How things improve, its awesome
deed02392: MrDestructoid
nicentra: @Protoxus Maybe, I just kinda wish the devs were more active, so far no word from them smh
serhejenos: :( :(
Protoxus: Jeppelelle It's literally insane.
3ygun: Cow test?
kluo84: who waiting for mr robot and silicon valley final season this Oct :D
sulozor: especially with quantum computers, rip Moore
3ygun: Coq test?
deadbeatdad7: new mr robot season?
deadbeatdad7: pogers
Protoxus: nicentra Hopefully that'll change once we jailbreak it with George's help ;)
sulozor: yes tonight I believe @deadbeatdad7
Protoxus: nicentra Did you watch his "Jailbreak the simulation"-talk yet?
domas3210: is Coq usefull?
st47ik: Mr. Robot season premiere is tonight :pog
deadbeatdad7: @sulozor pog fucking champion and I didnt know about it lol.. its gonna be on netflix?
sulozor: probably no
deadbeatdad7: oof
YouPowerRush: skeet skket
nicentra: @Protoxus I"m afraid not, I don't watch too much IT sec related stuff as that's not really my thing
Protoxus: nicentra It's not about IT sec. It's more about religion and philosophy. It's amazing. :P
Protoxus: nicentra Like r/outside but taking it seriously.
st47ik: @Protoxus and sociology and economy..
notmap: what is coq used for?
fwef64: no longer using VSCode?
foxubu: We cannot see the code
Protoxus: st47ik Yeah. It's an hour of pure wisdom.
nicentra: @Protoxus I'll check it out then.
st47ik: yeah it's so rare to see that in other shows
kluo84: anyone knows where I can get his tmux.conf
foxubu: Thank you
jpict: uni100 uni100
jpict: reward A Cheer shared Rewards to 3 others in Chat!
YouPowerRush: wiggle wit it
nicentra: @kluo84 github .com/geohot/configuration
deed02392: I just joined, what's the end goal of this?
nicentra: idk how up to date it is though
deed02392: @Protoxus the it sec aspects of it are very accurate though
hoffs: so any goal here?
deed02392: @hoffs ¯_(ツ)_/¯
st47ik: @hoffs coq Kappa
Protoxus: deed02392 It's been a while since I've listened to it. Next time I do, I'll be sure to hat the IT sec aspect of it in mind. :P
Shanmukhosiris: !uptime
st47ik: @Shanmukhosiris almost 2 hours now i think
trajenx: coq
Protoxus: have*
johnnyhotlava: The focus
Rezii27: How are you doing?
ItzDabbzz: Thanks for the RPGTreeNua @jpict
hackyhacks: i've been waiting for another math & coq stream
3even: NEOVIM or SPACEMACS ?
vay_man: why is he doing this?
jpict: @ItzDabbzz np ;P
swagettiyolonaise69: @hackyhacks said no one ever
goto10: whats coq, a programming lang?
DasMastah: The triple-dot is just a wildcard, right?
notmap: can someone for the love of god, explain to me what he is doing?
Jeppelelle: Would be weird representating wildcards as other languages represents ranges though :S
Protoxus: goto10 Yeah, for proving math theorems, according to Google
goto10: @Protoxus ty, cool
DasMastah: Will it even be possible to define a single grammar for Coq, when it uses multiple sub-languages?
dragan2271: Hi
keepingtrckofthisacct: a little off-top but Geoge reminds me of Elijah Woods as a boy
johnnyhotlava: I like how he is always self referential to his problems where as I always blame the tool
johnnyhotlava: FUCKING THING
keepingtrckofthisacct: ...is cooperating
monkbitgames: what is he coding roday?
3even: Where's the hot blonde today?
Protoxus: keepingtrckofthisacct He reminds me of Martin Shkreli, but if he was a programmer instead of pharmabro.
johnnyhotlava: He keeps his hot blondes in the freezer compartment
8bitbubsy: guess they aren't all that hot anymore then
johnnyhotlava: lol
monkbitgames: what he doing?
keepingtrckofthisacct: @Protoxus yea, Martin Shkreli's serious 'face'
Protoxus: keepingtrckofthisacct I mean... If you look at his LinkedIn and some of his talks, I don't know if he's that serious :P
keepingtrckofthisacct: @monkbitgames right now, language parser
johnnyhotlava: Shkreli's more aggressive
Protoxus: johnnyhotlava Yeah, that's true.
johnnyhotlava: HIs commitment to this parser is making my helmet swell
keepingtrckofthisacct: you'll see how 'aggressive george will get if you mention a certain company
Protoxus: johnnyhotlava LUL
johnnyhotlava: @keepingtrckofthisacct lol
Protoxus: keepingtrckofthisacct jgrHA
johnnyhotlava: Got it
johnnyhotlava: that fast
johnnyhotlava: jeez
Protoxus: Matzehs monkaS
masaro22: Why back on macOS ? Thought he has a new razer Blade
keepingtrckofthisacct: @Matzehs uh, oh...chat lets see what happens to Matzehs
xNoury: the banned word monkaS
Protoxus: KNOOKEL_HEAD We're just not supposed to. It's the rules.
TheKoreanZombi: He can't vim hard enough in Windows.
Protoxus: I think the reason was something about the company being serious business, and this being a casual stream
keepingtrckofthisacct: we're all going to get banned by association
Protoxus: monkaS
xNoury: monkaS
notmap: what are u coding?
8bitbubsy: monkaS
keepingtrckofthisacct: see
Abo7atm: can i be mod?
QED__: LUL
Bogz75: LUL
johnnyhotlava: Ah
Abo7atm: eye be good
aa_ato: bbbbb_test
Protoxus: keepingtrckofthisacct Theorem proven. And you didn't even need a parser. LUL
8bitbubsy: he sacrificed his life to show us what to not do
Oxynoia: i love you clean shaven
xNoury: begging for mod FeelsBadMan
goto10: wait ,what happened?
keepingtrckofthisacct: lol
ProfessorMagikarp0: we lost another one bois PepeHands
YouPowerRush: no mods allowed
johnnyhotlava: LOLOLO
notmap: yo geo what are u coding?
Protoxus: goto10 He broke rule #1 of the stream. Don't ever mention ***.
notmap: am lost
toonarmy0: sup george
keepingtrckofthisacct: language parser
ImJ4Gu4R: SeemsGood LUL
Abo7atm: @xNoury maybe I'll subscribe so senpai will notice me
johnnyhotlava: Raspberry's > Blue
monkbitgames: @georgehotz next time make some trainer for online game
goto10: SeemsGood SeemsGood SeemsGood
Jeppelelle: ?
Jeppelelle: Am i here?
serhejenos: ok
MonkaSupreme: yea
ImJ4Gu4R: put rules in github
Protoxus: Sub only chat? :o
void69: upper class here
LainShotcs: LainShotcs subscribed at Tier 1.
QED__: LUL it worked
Protoxus: This is how you get people to subscribe, the right way.
Protoxus: THE FREE MARKET PROVIDES
MonkaSupreme: welcome 😄 🍷
LainShotcs: xD
TheKoreanZombi: Followers only is pretty good right?.
Abo7atm: lower class invaaaaaade
antony4s_: f
Jeppelelle: he back
xNoury: free shrekli FeelsBadMan
Protoxus: And we're back
Kookook21: back
foxubu: Yeah
ImJ4Gu4R: NotLikeThis
goto10: ads :(
TheKoreanZombi: Are we twitch partners yet?
swagettiyolonaise69: what happened to your windows
ProfessorMagikarp0: nickiThink what if twitch chat crowdsourced an idea for a program and geo made it and posted it on github. that'd be lit or no? nickiThink
wavebend: george, have you measured your IQ
knilecrack: and you dropped windows for that
knilecrack: ahahaha
ImJ4Gu4R: Can we talk about exploit from the previous stream?
Protoxus: TheKoreanZombi I think one of the requirements for partner is streaming x amount of days each month or week, and I don't think he's really willing to stream that consistently :P
Protoxus: Just my guess though
coProof: @imj4gu4r we’d have to kill you first
wavebend: i'll buy it for $1
alexlucas_: how comes your selling
Jeppelelle: Isnt hot corners in Mission control anyway?
KrakkenTM: WISH I COULD RUN MAC OS ON PC
Protoxus: wavebend Don't think that's the ebay price though
knilecrack: 1.1$ here
xNoury: probably still cant afford it for the ebay price LUL
r00tdk: You are not windows fan ?
goto10: @KrakkenTM easy
ImJ4Gu4R: @coProof NotLikeThis NotLikeThis
my_curiosity: buy a chinese computer and put a linux on it and code in Rust, if you are gonna ruin your life.
r00tdk: I thought you chose windows over mac ?
Protoxus: r00tdk DK? You Danish?
TheKoreanZombi: @Protoxus Yeah, he got my hopes up doing checkm8 last week when he said he was going to stream the next day too and we were going to be partnered and live happily ever after.
ProfessorMagikarp0: sell his laptop? thatd be an interesting harddrive to buy LUL
r00tdk: @protoxus nope
johnnyhotlava: It's hot
Protoxus: r00tdk Oh, okay :P
Jeppelelle: Protoxus are you?
GeneralSoak: ... all computers are chinese
Protoxus: Jeppelelle Yes
Protoxus: Jeppelelle Are you?
Jeppelelle: No, almost, LeSwede
Yeahsper: is this a language from scratch or do you use any kind of base like python?
TheKoreanZombi: It is an established language
Protoxus: Jeppelelle Jävla svenska jgrGame
HedgeOnTwitch: boolean!
ImJ4Gu4R: @TheKoreanZombi but no stream. fake hope
Jeppelelle: :(
Protoxus: Jeppelelle :P
johnnyhotlava: and you're just going to put that directly in?
TheKoreanZombi: @ImJ4Gu4R so true. BibleThump
Jeppelelle: Atleast we can count properly unlike danish poeple :D
Protoxus: Oh yeah, counting in Danish is pretty messed up now that you mention it. Same as German.
Jeppelelle: 5 = fem, 50 = halvfjerd or something, makes not sense :D
Protoxus: Oh, yeah LUL
Protoxus: It's 70 = halvfjers
goto10: @Yeahsper my understanding is, he is using the lang called "cog" to prove math theorems,
johnnyhotlava: well it's relative to real things
Protoxus: 90 = halvfems LUL
Jeppelelle: lol :D
johnnyhotlava: lol
johnnyhotlava: or relative to a whole rather than lower numbers words based on fractions lol
r00tdk: Shall i buy macbook 15 inch or wait for 16 inch ?
TheKoreanZombi: @georgehotz is going to buy a 16-inch. Do whatever he does.
KrakkenTM: TYHICC
KrakkenTM: ASS
swagettiyolonaise69: T H I C C
soulshined: now thats how you get partnered SeemsGood
Protoxus: ^
notmap: this looks confusing
MonkaSupreme: bulge
r00tdk: Haha @thekoreanzombi
ProfessorMagikarp0: @Protoxus r we allowed to talk about backspace since its not a company yet ? jnbMM
r00tdk: Cant read george mind
3even: Yo @georgehotz do you take BitcoinCash donations?
r00tdk: He shifted to razor too
Protoxus: ProfessorMagikarp0 Yeah, I think so. People mentioned it earlier :P
r00tdk: I thought he changed to windows
GeneralSoak: is twitch partner the new goal
johnnyhotlava: we can talk about his AI bulldozer backspace
ImJ4Gu4R: @3even geo dont but we all here do.
foxubu: As long as mac os cannot run cuda for tensorflow, it's not really helpful :(
Jewishrambo: !A || !B == !(A&&B) idk lol
Jeppelelle: fuxubu cant you run tensorflow through opencv?
Jeppelelle: or just models?
jxiss: yo
Keyeh: hello george
r00tdk: Is 16 inch mac will be launched in oct 19 ?
rkxbz: did he finished writing lexer?
foxubu: Jeppelle possible yet not as helpful for testing as, e.g, on ubuntu
cechov: hi, did he make any progress in the last 1.5 hour?
johnnyhotlava: George is an AI psychologist
Jeppelelle: sure, nothing is as good as native drivers, don't know why nvidia and apple hates eachother this much
foxubu: Exactly
GeneralSoak: apple hates nvidia
GeneralSoak: nvidia would be supper happy to sell them stuff i guess
MonkaSupreme: if if a?
johnnyhotlava: IF if was a fifth,
johnnyhotlava: oh wait wrong place
RomanNYC: does destruct-ing them not work? o.o
autoindent: does he make a compiler?
johnnyhotlava: when can it understand a story.
johnnyhotlava: that's what I need.
dorkmo: BibleThump
korede360: What is the parser for?
foxubu: "Who's crying on stream?" :D
myaocat: do i see python 4?
Keyeh: is this the future? PogChamp
CMTFrosty: CMTFrosty subscribed with Twitch Prime.
johnnyhotlava: So you're going for the reimann hypothesis next right? With this coq
leijurrv: Hi george @georgehotz
GeneralSoak: php is the future
MDSZilla: Popo's are here
reptil1990: @georgehotz is getting swated :D
GaNDyRaC: FBI open up Kappa
johnnyhotlava: Where
jkpfeffer: only 333 viewers?
jkpfeffer: must be a math stream
GeneralSoak: @georgehotz whats your favorite anime
Protoxus: GeneralSoak LUL
Avelansh: you should stream more often
foxubu: It was about the sirin outside
khilshot: How much (highest level) math do you know?
Am4teur: once i had to program a language for a course and wasnt pleasant, how can you do this for fun dude?
myaocat: LUL
Ziv0: LUL
jo_renttt: lmao
GeneralSoak: streaming is all about audience interaction
johnnyhotlava: I enjoy it
knilecrack: stalin was baby compared to geo
jo_renttt: FeelsBadMan
myaocat: imagine ice company
ffntdt: oh i have assignment on antlr4 and now u streaming about parser
Protoxus: knilecrack LUL
ffntdt: nice
GaNDyRaC: Kappa
myaocat: Keepo
jo_renttt: why does that sound familiar @ffntdt
Jeppelelle: knilecrack i did not think you would survive that comparison :D
johnnyhotlava: Nice gamble
knilecrack: @Jeppelelle maybe he didn't get it
knilecrack: :D
MDSZilla: bool' ? or is it supposed to be just bool
vay_man: I have no idea what you are doing
lasercatboss: im kinda just here for the keyboard sounds
foxubu: That look when he reads the chat :D
johnnyhotlava: ahhhh
r00tdk: Which keyboard is he using
Jeppelelle: hhkb
johnnyhotlava: YESSSS
r00tdk: Hhkb silent ?
r00tdk: Doesn’t seem like silent
r00tdk: Does he using printed key one or non printed ?
johnnyhotlava: Lol a scam
Protoxus: >Definitition jgrGame
Sharlock93: is this some prolog kinda programming language ?
Protoxus: >"Definiton" jgrGame
Jeppelelle: he said non printed in a previous stream, if thats still the case
verdensmand1: why the fascination with coq my man? answer me seriously - i follow on ig
johnnyhotlava: dont need no spell
johnnyhotlava: Yeah that's right blame that ass cheek parser
Sharlock93: go.py is confusing on so many levels
johnnyhotlava: that sphincter parse
Sharlock93: yes twitch that is a link
Sznurek066: Is this Chris Lattner 2.0 ?
ncdoru: ncdoru subscribed at Tier 1.
r00tdk: @johnnyhotlava can i know something about 16 inch MB ? Is it going to be worth waiting?
johnnyhotlava: Allegedly it is
khairulimam_: do you like read romance novel?
Jeppelelle: nice question
lasercatboss: its funny how chat is as confused as george but on a whole different level
Protoxus: r00tdk George says it's worth waiting, so obviously that is the unquestionable truth.
MrMcaustin1: What are we doing today kiddos?
johnnyhotlava: lol
r00tdk: Yeah sure
MrMarkFilaroski: @MrMcaustin1 terminator AI
MrMcaustin1: ah the classic
jmc516: Nice Coq
r00tdk: Is the event prescheduled ?
foxubu: No
Protoxus: "// This is really wrong" LUL LUL LUL
johnnyhotlava: YEAH
khilshot: Do you have any intention of streaming hardware tinkering?
vay_man: lets test
r00tdk: George not paying attention to chat
minahoku: hello
lasercatboss: so he is writing a python for his coq
MrMarkFilaroski: Oh, Talk dirty to us
knilecrack: ahahaha
knilecrack: man I love this stream
foxubu: MrMarkFilaroski You're banned
Protoxus: So what do we have to read to understand this? Some boolean algebra?
Jeppelelle: What does the ' decoration on bool means?
MrMarkFilaroski: c'mon.
foxubu: :D
MrMarkFilaroski: @foxubu LUL fintJustice jeffgrossHobby
Jeppelelle: Oh ok 👍
Jeppelelle: Thanks
Keyeh: functional programming language btw
flesh38: please do
MrMarkFilaroski: Hot dog, not a hot dog?
lasercatboss: so its just called bool' for some more confusion
johnnyhotlava: Python is a whore with scales
3even: Functional > OO
johnnyhotlava: OH ok
khilshot: You should give relative numbers a try in vim.
Fatmetheny: I love this place
foxubu: Order Lunch ^^
r00tdk: Do we have some project related to this ? Or is it just for fun
fazel3ss: Why so many interest in type theory?
JingleBerryBlast: De Morgan's Law for Boolean Shit
knilecrack: no more blonde girl to bring chicken?
Abo7atm: he walks in a super weird way
Jewishrambo: VoHiYo
foxubu: Seriously? Nudles?
minahoku: まるちゃんラーメン？
beylu_cs: he walks like a sim
Navilist: College flashbacks!
Fatmetheny: Instant noodle gang RISE UP
johnnyhotlava: De morgans law within boolean
lasercatboss: fusili PogChamp
Lefer_: George PogChamp
Protoxus: Cooking stream PogChamp
johnnyhotlava: That he wants to prove with coq then tell "python" about it
johnnyhotlava: NAH DAWG
foxubu: Ok real student food stream :D
lasercatboss: maybe we need georges top 10 student advice
CaptCalifornia: EATIN LIKE A DOCTOR
Sycto: george is a michelin star chef and only cooks the finest foods
flesh38: Don't put the oil in the water!
LiveLifeLive: George why don't you try beard
r00tdk: Not healthy food for guys who workout !!!
tris790: cooking stream VoHiYo
johnny_thehobo: cooking stream? PogChamp
ffntdt: Its 2am here :( and u r cooking
lasercatboss: he's coqing everybody
gunnaren: @ffntdt 2 am mcdonalds is the best - go for it
foxubu: LiveLifeLive He has in the past
johnnyhotlava: How do you know what section you wan to read so quickly?
FargioFarmani: What google chrome theme is he using?
khilshot: for o in dir(yourstuff): print(o) looks better.
ffntdt: @gunnaren no mac here works this late dude
ffntdt: *mc
Protoxus: Now THAT'S pretty.
Protoxus: jgrYIKES
johnnyhotlava: Allegedly
johnnyhotlava: In your opinion
johnnyhotlava: lol
johnnyhotlava: as not
gunnaren: @ffntdt That's sad : (
foxubu: Like Constituency Parse Trees ^^
santi_264: how long ago did this start?
Ekiinho: whatsuppp
johnnyhotlava: You have to give it meaning
johnnyhotlava: cause it's bogus
gunnaren: @santi_264 like 3- 4 hours
rkxbz: he is a vim/tmux monster
johnnyhotlava: without the standard library you gonna make one of those too?
johnnyhotlava: And then what
johnnyhotlava: ohhhhhhhhhhhhhh
reptil1990: !uptime
tris790: so you want to strip your coq :)
reptil1990: @georgehotz no chatbot :(
johnnyhotlava: lol
johnnyhotlava: EXACTLy
johnnyhotlava: 100hours for you rest of my life
wonderlab: Sup G
Jeppelelle: forgot a . after nat?
Jeppelelle: the zero nat
Keyeh: the dot
myaocat: if university is old and not good to learn why do you take 3 people from university to build RSA?
rkxbz: rsa?
Jeppelelle: weird
my_curiosity: you are getting quite proficient dealing with coq
myaocat: @rkxbz https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/RSA_(cryptosystem)
broadhawk: why did he walk away and come back
lp97: bruh. i cant even make a website in python
Protoxus: @broadhawk 'Cause it looks cool
Navilist: @broadhawk It's a genius maneuver. We couldn't understand.
broadhawk: my simple mind cant comprehend it
rkxbz: @myaocat yeah, i am familiar with it. but i thought it is not difficult to make one yourself.
Protoxus: broadhawk jgrHA
Annex_Greenland: is this the kid that hacked the iphone
johnnyhotlava: Is the speed just from reps?
manwheeluno: This is cool
nanodanger7: hello everyone
lp97: ya @Annex_Greenland
manwheeluno: Sup
Annex_Greenland: legend
rkxbz: @myaocat , i have tried to implement it some time ago. if you are interested - https://github.com/Raysultan/LearnRSA
Jeppelelle: lol
Annex_Greenland: siri stinks LUL
Ziv0: LUL
myasovlavashe: LUL
Navilist: dammit siri can't add
Sznurek066: LUL
Annex_Greenland: siri is a basic bitch
johnnyhotlava: George can teach it to add
lucas9o: LUL
LiveLifeLive: Siri got activated here!
myaocat: @rkxbz it's not about the implementation but theory
gunnaren: Siri aka home chef
Jeppelelle: effortless
Keyeh: she is going to torture in the future
johnnyhotlava: You special edward broad
knilecrack: :D
Annex_Greenland: like talking to a severe autist LUL
FargioFarmani: he talking smooth to robot girl
rkxbz: @myaocat , ok
johnnyhotlava: lololololololol
Keyeh: omg he is really living the cloud
LiveLifeLive: My Siri got activated :)
Arktri: She doesn't even thank you for the offer.
Ziv0: now you messed up her counting LUL
Sznurek066: Future is here LUL
broadhawk: you are a guest in siris house
TheKoreanZombi: Google Assistant can add time to timer
knilecrack: google must be smart
Annex_Greenland: google assistant is skynet
azstreamz99: azstreamz99 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
Nnotm: !uptime
knilecrack: can you ovaerride it?
knilecrack: override*
foxubu: PJSalt
Nnotm: has he started this today?
Annex_Greenland: surprised u dont have a cat
ImJ4Gu4R: WutFace
Protoxus: Annex_Greenland He's kinda talking to Siri like it's his cat though :P
Shanmukhosiris: @Nnotm yess
Nnotm: thanks
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz will you use this language to program some simulated worlds, so its inhabitants cannot exploit some bugs and escape?
Nnotm: it looks like Notation can even introduce mixfix syntax, that's neat
Nnotm: if then else is defined similarly, rather than built in
Johnvade: I didn't know geohot did formal methods
Nnotm: How much have you used coq or something like it?
knilecrack: ahahahahaha
lucas9o: LUL
Ziv0: LUL
Protoxus: Is Siri wife material? Helping cooking and all
broadhawk: forever
Mariosavitch: lol
Jewishrambo: CoolStoryBob
ZeeZaxean: are windows shenanigans dead? :(
Rojaster: she takes over the house
Vonsmal: LUL
Pasulya: CoolStoryBob
8bitbubsy: CoolStoryBro
Sznurek066: LUL
Abo7atm: LUL LUL LUL LUL
Jewishrambo: :)
Ziv0: lmao
sanyadollar: LUL
ffntdt: LUL
serhejenos: Kappa Kappa Kappa Kappa
Lottsz: LUL
zgamer0123: LUL LUL LUL
Nnotm: just say "for now"
Pasulya: PowerUpL CoolStoryBob
FargioFarmani: she in a loop bro
gunnaren: LUL
Mariosavitch: unplug her
broadhawk: shes broken
flesh38: LUL LUL LUL LUL
serhejenos: for how long
Protoxus: Code stream to cooking stream to dating stream PogChamp
FargioFarmani: UNPLUG
Keyeh: artificial dumbass
twiggy_io: THis is why we need backspace ai
Sznurek066: LUL she is concious
gunnaren: She sure knows how to play a woman alright
Mariosavitch: just like a real life women
Rojaster: make more fun of him Siri
lefg7: did he go back to mac?
Protoxus: lefg7 Yes
Keyeh: yes, windows suck
lefg7: smart choice
r00tdk: Not good food for guys who workout?
Nnotm: @georgehotz refl means reflexivity, i.e. for any a, a should be equal to a
Keyeh: mom spaghetti
Protoxus: https://clips.twitch.tv/DignifiedHandsomeRadishYee I like this
Keyeh: palms sweaty
knilecrack: man you should really stream more often
Moe_Bradberry: why dont you define dZ
Zharrtan: At least not chicken this time xD
MrTriharder: Haircut PogChamp
mh1996mh: !language
chocolatechp: george whats up man!
Johnvade: is he trying to understand coq then write his own similar program?
MrTriharder: @georgehotz is it ok if I don’t put an optimizer in a slam? My teacher is just happy with the colors popping on the OpenGL window 🤣
Johnvade: I just came here
walktheabyss: Which keyboard do you use @georgehotz
Dilwad: whats he working on
RSPwner_: what editor is this?
RSPwner_: the coq @Dilwad
Johnvade: vim
chocolatechp: vscode i think
khilshot: Vim i guess
RSPwner_: this one tho
TheKoreanZombi: The keyboard connected to his MacBook
Nnotm: I think it should be bool' -> Type
hoffs: @georgehotz do you just fuck around all day long or do you have a day job
RSPwner_: whats the other one
Mariosavitch: vscode
RSPwner_: okay i thought so
ffntdt: looks delicious, never had that in mylife
knilecrack: what is nat' ?
chocolatechp: what cereal is that
walktheabyss: @TheKoreanZombi and which keyboard would that be
nanodanger7: it's a happy hacking pro 2
TheKoreanZombi: his MacBook keyboard, the one that's built into the laptop
myaocat: ResidentSleeper ResidentSleeper ResidentSleeper
Mariosavitch: i love coq
zackfair_ow: Have you ever done an iq test @georgehotz
myaocat: to prove that he is smarter than you?
chocolatechp: why dont you stream more?
khilshot: Vim tip, Press 'f' key then the char you wanna jump to, it's faster. @gerogehotz
CrazyAsianBoiii: f
Keyeh: that one hell of rabbit hole
myaocat: did you port the program to windows?
hoffs: :|
chocolatechp: same
knilecrack: you don't need more
filedescriptor: 80 PogChamp
Mariosavitch: you eat like 80 iq
HS_SemenThrower: yay my favorite streamer hi fucker
Johnvade: >github stars as intelligence indicator
Johnvade: that's like twitch followers
HS_SemenThrower: learn how to hold a spoon man
warron_buffet: Hi from Russia!
chocowhiskey: eating like a 80 iq confirmed
RSPwner_: tis a fork g
hoffs: why do you even use a fork for those
Keyeh: richard feynman had 200 iq i'm telling you
Jannnik: a lot of dumb smart people Kappa
TheKoreanZombi: @khilshot Does he seem new to vim?
Johnvade: feynman probably actually had 120ish iq
zackfair_ow: Ye but there are smart people and genius people
Navilist: Dumb IQ gang stand up.
Johnvade: he wasn't the type to make a point by lying about that
zmechs: zmechs subscribed with Twitch Prime.
RSPwner_: @georgehotz why do you use vscode sometimes and other times vim?
Keyeh: what do you mean, most of his 'feynman stories' were made up
fazel3ss: I prefer to think about iq is how good you’re in multi field.
warron_buffet: From Russia with love .What do you think about quantum computers?
myaocat: twitchcoq domain is available! BUY NOW
khilshot: @TheKoreanZombi not at all but pressing the same key again and again is just too repetitive.
MrTriharder: admiralC1 admiralC2
HS_SemenThrower: jheez it's painful to watch him eat like that
MrTriharder: admiralC3 admiralC4
dorkmo: Party1
zoki_macola: that chewing sound
chocolatechp: sprinle some cheese on it
Nnotm: FWIW, this appears to contain the definition of exists https://coq.inria.fr/library/Coq.Init.Logic.html
chocolatechp: sprinkle
Johnvade: I thought he chased "Feynman stories" but did not make them up
TheKoreanZombi: @khilshot I know, was just joking with you
khilshot: @TheKoreanZombi lol
jaalle: @georgehotz Are you trying to automate our jobs?
fazel3ss: For instance you have 80 which is lowest medium. You still can be good in one field and maybe one field only. When you have it like 140 you may be able to be good in 4 different fields
jaalle: Like programming jobs
MrTriharder: Can someone tell me what coq is
Nnotm: MrTriharder it's proof assistant
LiveLifeLive: eating like 80 IQ. :)
sepulsher: @georgehotz how good you were at math in highschool?
Keyeh: is a variant of the dic language
HS_SemenThrower: @RSPwner_ vscode kills the hype, you garra feel like a haxor sometimes #vim
Thomasbrah: @LiveLifeLive lol
Nnotm: MrTriharder it let's you write proofs and checks them, and automates writing them a little bit
MrTriharder: Oh
LiveLifeLive: @Thomasbrah hahaha
Protoxus: How can you make exists work if everything is part of the simulation? jgrThink
zoki_macola: @georgehotz Do you have any advice for someone who wants to move to US and start a company in biotech?
Ecobat: @zoki_macola do you already have a business model ?
Jeppelelle: zoki_macola Check out Theranos and do the oppposite of what they did
wrelt: lark is awesome
LiveLifeLive: @Jeppelelle Perfect PUT. @zoki_macola Read Book "Bad Blood"
zoki_macola: Yeah, just not the proof that it will work. But of course nothing like Theranos
Ekshernul: just joined the stream, what's he trying to prove?
wrelt: @ekshernul he’s trying to build a prover language I think, a la coq
TheKoreanZombi: Trying to prove P=NP.
wrelt: not sure if he’s trying to prove anything in particular atm
r00tdk: Ctf ?
TheKoreanZombi: getting really close.
Ecobat: @zoki_macola I suppose no one ever had proof that "it" will work
r00tdk: Not doing ctf😄
Shanmukhosiris: asmr
Vinndy: what about it was named cold war because russia is cold? that's a good song
Shanmukhosiris: asmr <3
Ecobat: you just have to press on
r00tdk: Good ctf going on
zoki_macola: More towards Transcriptic. Cloud lab but not for general purposes
r00tdk: Balsen ctf it is hard as hell
filedescriptor: was he trying to create the exists quantifier?
Johnvade: why is he making his own coq like program
Nnotm: filedescriptor I think it was more him seeing that it's not built in and then deciding not to use it
zoki_macola: Maybe like https://carbon3d.com, but for bio
aziz_fazlagic: Where is your Razer Blade? :p
Ecobat: how long has this stream been going ?
tharda18: hi
Jeppelelle: zoki 3d print organs, molecules, enzymes and stuff?
wrelt: @johnvade he’s not, he’s making a whole coq-like language from scratch, in addition to an example coq-like program that is interpreted by his language. at least that’s my guess from joining stream 3 min ago
Protoxus: @Ecobat Uptime is 1 hour and 10 min, but there was a crash at some point, so who knows?
Johnvade: yeah why
zoki_macola: @Jeppelelle Yea, but not "printing", more like growing
Protoxus: Probably 2-3 hours
Zheikk3: "basic programming"
chocolatechp: LOl
wrelt: not sure why, he seems to just like coq (no pun)
Johnvade: to remedy some perceived weakness in coq or to get his feet wet
Johnvade: I guess the latter
knilecrack: yes
wrelt: I think he wants to understand proving languages better
Brunovercelli: """"""basic"""""" programming lul
Protoxus: wrelt I guess it's handy for proving stuff, which is why he wants to reimplement it in python? Idk
cechov: why don't you try to explain instead of raging?
chocolatechp: LOL
HS_SemenThrower: oooo censorship!!!
Shanmukhosiris: LUL
filedescriptor: damn he's taking out people left and right LUL
gonzaloquintas: hi dude!
zoki_macola: @Jeppelelle But its expensive to make cloud lab, and need to find good hardware engineers
HS_SemenThrower: no
HS_SemenThrower: i don't
r1ppyd1ppy: rip
Protoxus: HS_SemenThrower His stream, his perogative to ban :^)
smurfd0: "why not" is usually a good answer on "why?"
Johnvade: then you could just say "why not" etc
fafws321: how long has he been streamign?>????
r00tdk: Ctf
filedescriptor: he's going full stalin mode guys im afraid monkaS
Protoxus: prerogative*
knilecrack: Hey did you hear about TabNine?
sepulsher: @georgehotz how good you were at math in highschool?
Jeppelelle: zoki_macola yeah i bet biotech is incredible expensive, FDA approval is really tough in medicine too i've heard so you have a ton of work ahead of you :D
r1ppyd1ppy: @georgehotz roll a d20 to see who gets banned next
Shanmukhosiris: suggest me some easy ways to learn algorithms please
aziz_fazlagic: Why is he using a macbook?
r00tdk: Not doing ctfs?
Thomasbrah: @georgehotz so backspace.ai is your newest project or how should i understand this ?
nomadicpatch: how much rent are you paying for that apppartment?
wrelt: backspace.ai seems cool
shieeeeeeeeet: so the answer to "why" was backspace.ai
Protoxus: wrelt Damn right
JdPaulBlart: math boring programming fun
UzeezU: I really do not like the feel of SF
chocolatechp: contact button does not work on backspace
JdPaulBlart: so programmers will be useless in the future PogChamp
nudax: oh finally i catch a live stream. good to see you!
Protoxus: @chocolatechp Yes it does. It's mailto-link
eduardoadf1: what is that open on vscode?
DasMastah: The Coq source code @eduardoadf1
zoki_macola: @Jeppelelle I dont think i need FDA, we are not making drugs, more like development enviroment for bioengineering. People who use our platform would most likely need FDA
Ecobat: @JdPaulBlart yeah, probably in 150 years. Give or take 1000 years
HS_SemenThrower: does george ver play games?
eduardoadf1: thx
HS_SemenThrower: ever*
chocolatechp: o
theselectedcoder: SF seems expensive af
spanilith: seems
Ace33W: @hs_sementhrower do you know who he is?
spanilith: its like #1 or #2
theselectedcoder: 5k month for 1 bed and 1 bathroom apartment
Shanmukhosiris: any developers in the chat ?
HS_SemenThrower: @Ace33W yes but if i say his company i'll get banned
Ecobat: 5k a month !?
zenkai_oogway: @HS_SemenThrower he played minecraft once I think
JdPaulBlart: so if we take 1000 years then programmers were obsolete in 1019 @Ecobat
chocolatechp: it doesnt do anything when i click it
r00tdk: Not doing ctf nowadays?
Ecobat: @JdPaulBlart ok, don't take. Just give
Ace33W: do you know his background though? he's not a gamer. he is a programmer
wrelt: @ecobat I’d say give or take 300 imo. well, give, since it won’t be in 1869
theselectedcoder: in Estonia u get a big ass house for 5k per month
HS_SemenThrower: @zenkai_oogway ah so he's a minecraft guy?
JdPaulBlart: @georgehotz the computer science globalists wont let you automate programmers
prezk0: !uptime
Ecobat: @wrelt if all goes well, way past our time
wrelt: @r00tdk he does different things every stream. don’t think he’s done ctfs for some time
nudax: you look healthy
benchai18: My fav nerd
JdPaulBlart: it wont start ruining our jobs until the far future
sausainismilka: sup hot
wrelt: @ecobat yeah it’s almost certainly beyond our lifetimes, barring some anti-aging breakthroughs coming very soon
theselectedcoder: @prezk0 uptime is around 3.5 hours
JdPaulBlart: can you make music.ai
wrelt: jobs that are less abstract may be at risk in our lifetimes though, I think
asthmaa: @georgehotz do you have a bachelor degree? i want to understand if uni is really important for computer science
Ecobat: yup
Ecobat: @asthmaa computer science ? yes. Programming ? no.
asthmaa: k
Johnvade: >only famous people can find programs that are hard to decide
Johnvade: I am not famous
botclimber: ur willing is ur best weapon
benchai18: Whats he working on
TaFFeLaFFe: @asthmaa You're gonna be a lot better off in terms of job security with a degree.
chancechants: self monitoring abstraction layer
Johnvade: here is a program that is hard to decide (just came up with this): start at 2^200, keep multiplying by two and convert to decimal. terminate when you find a power of two that doesn't contain all ten digits in its decimal expansion
pamz123: wb
Ecobat: @wrelt it will take quite a while though. I mean, programs (or robots) that replace people's jobs will be incredibly complex. Complexity equals bugs and less secure (more prone to hacking)
sondreal: Hello
Johnvade: decide if that ever terminates!
Ecobat: so there will be a lot of ... fighting it
Ecobat: so to say
nudax: what is he working on?
JdPaulBlart: we are probably good fam
benchai18: @asthmaa if u can get the degree just do it dude. I was too rebellious to stay in school more than half a semester and the last 5 years of my life (25-30) woulda been easier if I’d finished
JdPaulBlart: if anything interesting happens it will probably be in future
wrelt: @ecobat yeah, but in 50 years, even if we aren’t yet near what we consider AGI, I think the rate of jobs being phased out will accelerate. especially simple labor and service jobs. and complexity may be partly mitigated or at least mitigated quicker with ML
haircutjimmy: Coq?
shieeeeeeeeet: is he building the parser in python? or using a parsing library? what about the interpreter?
Johnvade: theorem prover
chancechants: i for one welcome our new digital micromanagers, my TPS report will be submitted in a timely manner
sondreal: are you wearing ur watch georgehotz PogChamp
wrelt: @shieeeeeeeeet yes, in python. he’s using an awesome python parsing lib called lark. used it the first time about a week ago, and it’s very easy to understand and use
thuganalyst: What song was that?
wrelt: I’m assuming his parser and interpreter will both be in python
faxity: LUL
fafws321: why are u so angry?
Orestes13: but why george? Kappa
benchai18: CatCoq(ck)?
lyricrush: REEE
shieeeeeeeeet: does the parser auto generate the AST?
HS_SemenThrower: who hurt u george
filedescriptor: he went from stalin to feynman monkaS
faxity: thinking about dieing monkaS
JdPaulBlart: thats wack fam
lyricrush: Simulation theory.jpg
fafws321: why are you telling us these things now?
zoki_macola: Im making a biotech company to understand the genetic code and make myself immortal
DrakenZA: it makes sense
Johnvade: this is like the shittiest feynman why rant ive heard
knilecrack: you dont' give a fuck
camkinstrike: Yo wont learn if you don't ask questions.
Johnvade: cya
gonzaloquintas: I wish I know pythoin to understand what is this guy doing.... just watching he while coding is mesmerizing
frankytex: that escalated quickly
knilecrack: yeah
JdPaulBlart: we work so that life is more comfortable
Mariosavitch: why do you want to live forever
Mariosavitch: Kappa
chancechants: dont let your memes be dreams
neca420: this used to be a programming stream FeelsBadMan
wrelt: >work for moloch
wrelt: well-put
MrPrismo: What language is this that you are coding in?
spatialfree: spatialfree subscribed at Tier 1.
JdPaulBlart: with that mindset everyone should just kill theirself
spanilith: pog feinman
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz so when are you starting to hack the world simulation machine? I bet there are format string bugs there.
Thomasbrah: why, it's simple. Everyone has a limited amount of time so why not try make it as easy going and enjoyful as possible while you still have your time in exsistence
Protoxus: @MrPrismo It's coq
JdPaulBlart: this is what happens to your brain when you get sued by sony at a yound age
wrelt: @thomasbrah that assumes the primary goal in life is to enjoy oneself, which is a big assumption
W1lkins: Abort.
filedescriptor: @JdPaulBlart his speech turned me into a nihilist
filedescriptor: LUL
MrPrismo: Thanks @Protoxus
knilecrack: ahahahahahahahahaha
notelex: !uptime
chesssist: jasonrG jasonrG jasonrG jasonrG jasonrG
CondomsWontFit: PogChamp
Thomasbrah: What was the result of sony sueing you ?
ProfessorMagikarp0: hell yeah LUL
chesssist: crack or tweaaaaak
chancechants: PJSugar PJSugar PJSugar
st47ik: its the caffeine in tea Kappa
fafws321: do you like math? @georgehotz
wrelt: @thomasbrah probably made him more famous
zoki_macola: If AI advances continue at any rate, eventually we will all merge into one superintelligent computer or organism, and actually figure out how to escape this universe
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz do you think there are some nice b0fs in our simulated world?
whitsyerhing: You more of a stoic then?
wrelt: @jagger_rsw he talked about that a bit in his sxsw talk
Protoxus: Positive nihilism embraces that nothing matters that nothing matters. :D
erichtp: i cant wait for backspace to fund my future robot waifu gf
chesssist: !keyboard
filedescriptor: @erichtp same Kreygasm
Obijags: !keyboard
st47ik: @chesssist HHKB aka Happy hacking keyboard
erichtp: @Protoxus nothing else matters but you moon2PREGARIO
sepulsher: @georgehotz why math is so hard
jagger_rsw: cogito
st47ik: stoicism Kappa
Protoxus: erichtp Gotta love Max Stirner, am I right?
verdensmand1: the primary objective in life is to ball out and get like a million followers on IG most favorably while buliding good tech
DevoE444: still nothing matters though Kappa
lasercatboss: solipsism is just really convenient to justify my ego
shieeeeeeeeet: can't you derive hedonism from solipsism
Protoxus: verdensmand1 You Danish like me?
cechov: so, we gave up on coq and the parser?
Protoxus: cechov Yeah, 'cause it doesn't matter. :^) Kappa
Thomasbrah: is that his bed in the left side of the webcam ?
benchai18: You’re a far more functional tweaker than I was.
sondreal: its a couch
jagger_rsw: why nihilism is stupid? it just says that there are no objective moral values enshrined in the fabric of this world, and you need to figure your own ones (as yourself or as a society)
erichtp: @Protoxus i only love Freud and his cocaine
LemareClub: whats he doing?
lasercatboss: the coq parser just lead to way more profound questions
Protoxus: erichtp What's a n** gotta do to get some eel coq?!
knilecrack: :D
foxubu: 23 stream
knilecrack: I GOT THESE CHEEZBURGERS MANNN
wrelt: coq and philosophy go well together
Protoxus: erichtp If you don't know what I'm talking about, you gotta see the Sam O'Nella YouTube-video on Freud :P
knilecrack: @wrelt drugs too :)
JdPaulBlart: is this for discrete math
JdPaulBlart: that class was aids
lasercatboss: all the great philisophers liked themselves some coq from time to time
sondreal: discrete maths are easy if you dont ask the whys Kappa
wrelt: @jdpaulblart enjoy never understanding deep learning
erichtp: moon2WAH when its too much coq
NonTrivial778: LUL
st47ik: LUL
pmc_eft: @sondreal The boolean algebra x x=x LUL
NonTrivial778: Coq is fun
arbitel: why back to MBP ? where's your razer
sondreal: LUL
erichtp: @Protoxus I love his videos lmao
knilecrack: yes
Nnotm: nat has infinite values, but two constructors, assuming coq uses those terms
knilecrack: I used to define it in university
spanilith: 1 x for 1 y
unmercifullyy: @Nnotm what keyboard do u use?
Protoxus: erichtp If you like political philosophy to some extend you'll love jreg as well
grey_street: how much
unmercifullyy: @georgehotz what keyboard do u use?
Nnotm: @unmercifullyy physical keyboard or keyboard layout?
Nnotm: oh did you not mean to tag me?
unmercifullyy: @Nnotm sorry, did not mean to address the question to you LUL
Thomasbrah: @georgehotz is this on a macbook or an imac ?
Nnotm: okay, I was wondering why you would ask me that LUL
smurfd0: we just see your background, no doc no menubar...
erichtp: I'll give it a look thanks for the recommendation moon2EZ
W1lkins: we see the secrets monkaS
nanodanger7: https://www.hhkeyboard.com/ this is the keyboard
Belowzer0w: developing games for the ps3 kappa
xyet: he was never able to get it working on windows?
pmc_eft: de morhens law LUL
fafws321: searching de morgans law in 2019 LUL LUL LUL
benchai18: Anyone else have no idea what’s going on but riveted nonetheless??
Crypod: Jebaited yes
JdPaulBlart: $240 keyboard btw
ncdoru: !uptime
whitsyerhing: no idea what is going on. i'm here for the keyboard asmr
JdPaulBlart: i got amazon alexa on my raspberry pi can i get a job pls
Twitch0xme: @georgehotz replace with *?
slakkur: Yes,I finally get to watch live!
hotplay: @georgehotz what laptop do you have?
Crypod: wahoo! one problem eliminated!
nizero: sup George, what are your thoughts about techcrunch disrupt?
NV17: Basic
3even: @georgehotz Do you take BitcoinCash donations?
knilecrack: what do you thing about the bloomberg article on compromised supermicro servers?
knilecrack: think*
Crypod: i see some n in the middle there. is that intended?
Protoxus: Paint PogChamp
slakkur: draw.io
Jannnik: draw io
kenan7: draw.io ??
Protoxus: ^
W1lkins: javascript paint LUL
MonkaSupreme: this is how paint felt LULW
notelex: LUL
dyslexicat: Kappa
Crypod: oshiThink
ProfessorMagikarp0: luxxDetective
rscarth: rscarth subscribed at Tier 1.
DevoE444: those arrows are dope af
Protoxus: DevoE444 I know, right?
Navilist: LUL
NV17: How do you make a language damn
ProfessorMagikarp0: TheIlluminati TheIlluminati TheIlluminati
Protoxus: You can just drag from the side of a box to another to make an arrow
MllCZ: @NV17 you need structures, variables and functions
jax05_: hey what's up
DevoE444: and Pope runs the corporations Kappa
dyslexicat: weSmart
NV17: DarkMode DarkMode
johnny_thehobo: fucking employees messed all up
notelex: LUL
nizero: this is the best explanation ever
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz to go to blackhat / defcon, go to parties, meet geohot at defcon ctf parties, this makes employees happier
johnny_thehobo: TriHard take take take
fazel3ss: Don’t corps get better employees after all. It’s self investment for them
ProfessorMagikarp0: geo rant compilation video when? Kappa TheIlluminati
slakkur: Hey I'm going to vegas for ReInvent dont let the cat out of the bag!
HS_SemenThrower: hahah what a finesse
slakkur: lol
frankytex: those people exist, I have met them
MonkaSupreme: LUL
Purrplecat: 5Head
chaprio1: thanks for your ted talk
nizero: insightful!
johnny_thehobo: this is better than greta's speech
Purrplecat: I see i see purrplT purrplMald
HS_SemenThrower: yeesh
pizzA_z: Hey @georgehotz awesome as always my dude. Getting sidetracked again? 🤔
johnny_thehobo: hotz for nobel
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz are you talking about Mitnick and Schneier? :)
3even: @georgehotz Do you take BitcoinCash donations?
Navilist: Where do employees who were paid for by corporations fit in on this diagram?
HS_SemenThrower: ooo
chaprio1: politics 4Head
johnny_thehobo: he said it chat monkaS
frankytex: security and a//v pros also get money from the conference ring of perpetual bs
3even: Good chance Greta is gonna commit suicide
HS_SemenThrower: that semi autistic girl is nominated for a nobel prize
Crypod: whoaa whoaaa there
jagger_rsw: conferences are a perk these days, if employees don't get em, they go to another company, there's no expectation of learning stuff
notelex: so where can I buy tickets to your conference to listen this talk in person
haircutjimmy: :( greta
MonkaSupreme: imagine being 2 weeks on a sailing boat ... :(
nizero: she is Aspergers
UMPS: doesn't she have like aspergers and OCD
HS_SemenThrower: back peddling
whitsyerhing: universities just lumped in with corporations ?
HS_SemenThrower: greta get his ass
3even: She is a human shield
cobaltstark1: How to start learning to code like you .. I am an undergrad ..
uchihaislife: We are back on mac finally
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz you need to come to the DefCon "conference" again btw :)
fillmyvoid: capital gains
haircutjimmy: I paid to go to EuroPython last year - oh no! Sucker
Jewishrambo: Don’t think they. Do
HS_SemenThrower: do another techcrunch
cobaltstark1: How to start learning to code like you .. I am an undergrad ..
fazel3ss: What is an alternative to conf
benchai18: I want @georgehotz at my wedding.
jax05_: @cobaltstark1 google my fren
yash_rohilla: @georgehotz Why does the sec field suck?
benchai18: Why does defcon suck? Never been so I’m curious
nizero: I met you once at defcon George, u were too busy to say hi tho
Protoxus: draw.io is a native file type in Google Drive
3even: @georgehotz Do you take BitcoinCash donations?
Protoxus: Pretty nice
quickfloor: i go to college for free but it's sucks . should i drop out and be rich ?
dagobert2707: i dont get all this bad attitudes about Greta and this Friday for future thing...
cobaltstark1: How to start learning to code like you .. I am an undergrad ..
Navilist: Hehe
whitsyerhing: Have podcasts morphed into something similar to conferences?
xyet: I step out for a bit, the fuck are we talking about ? triHYPERS
foxubu: Mr. Robot #conspiracy ^^
boc5: man you are crazy you move for nothing
Nnotm: no "fridays for future" is the thing where students don't go to school on friday to protest climate change
benchai18: Wait why does DEFCON suck? Always thought abt going
chancechants: what about blizzcon?
cobaltstark1: How to start learning to code like you .. I am an undergrad ..
Jeppelelle: DEF CON 25 - Christopher Domas - Breaking the x86 Instruction Set <-- great talk for those who are into that stuff
haircutjimmy: cheers the noo
quickfloor: Drive.ai Bought by apple to be success
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz It's a bit a blackmail on employees behalf these days. They say 'if you don't let us go, so we can find out who pays better money (and maybe we leave you), we'll leave you 100% sure"
HS_SemenThrower: i wanna see u talk to joe rogan for some reason
fazel3ss: Conferences are for sharing knowledge, workshops and so on. If not them than what?
Protoxus: George on Joe Rogan when? Keepo
quickfloor: Can we run Geopodcast ?
benchai18: @georgehotz if I could get you on Rogan would you do it?
Nnotm: everyone's having fun until podcasters start making conferences...
chaprio1: Kappa great
johnnyhotlava: Just got back what happened to him translating to python?
3even: lol
HS_SemenThrower: no ben
nizero: @georgehotz what about the startups that are trying to network with investors/customers at disrupt. .. they are both give and take
HS_SemenThrower: he said some stream ago that he would not go
jax05_: @johnnyhotlava he started ranting LUL
boc5: Why you don't make your own podcast show like joe rogueAne
johnnyhotlava: @jax05_ Glorious lol
Protoxus: boc5 What do you think this is? :P
quickfloor: He saying twitch conf is not bad cause he's using twitch right now :D you have to say that bro . u can't talk sh1t about twitch in twitch
uchihaislife: @georgehotz what chair is that? looks reals comfortable
NV17: whats a twitchcoq?
boc5: It's not professional
johnnyhotlava: George you're a star though.
benchai18: @hs_sementhrower Bummer. If he had something to sell he might go. Oh well 🤷♂️
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz you're beating a dead horse about sec-conferences, it's a paid vacation
johnnyhotlava: YES it is
MonkaSupreme: twitch con = networking
quickfloor: LUL
Celestial_Jaeger: can someone help me with my pintos task 0 assignment lmao
Caene: Isn't Twitchcon more of a get-together, hey come here and meet your b-list e-celebs? Shit like that.
notelex: LUL
HS_SemenThrower: LOL
johnnyhotlava: Lol his chart
Akash_44: LUL
Julll: LUL
slakkur: wait, they have tons of labs at ms ignite, and you get out of the office which gives you time to learn without work bullshit distracting you, you also get to network, but I wouldnt go if i had to pay for it
johnnyhotlava: Is so glorious
quickfloor: ypu have more than 500 connection
johnnyhotlava: I love this man
whitsyerhing: Does anything ever progress from conferences. They do seem like a scam.
my_curiosity: coq list
quickfloor: like bill gatesa
Jewishrambo: Lol
3even: Do you take Bitcoin Cash donations?
UniversalGeneve: just sent you an invite on linkedin LUL
faulpelzz: @georgehotz why do you sleep in your kitchen?
DevoE444: i hope the fappening upload gretas nudes Kappa
johnnyhotlava: LOLOLOLOL
johnnyhotlava: God that's the best
Caene: @DevoE444 DansGame
chaprio1: @DevoE444 fbi
quickfloor: But bro . conferences give good lunch Kappa
xyet: is he mentally stable?
Protoxus: xyet Yes
zoki_macola: just leave it on
nizero: George I met Harold at a conference
MonkaSupreme: put on black screen with some music
slakkur: plus ms ignite backpack is legit
Protoxus: Yoga stream? PogChamp
johnnyhotlava: My favorite part is the perpetual conference goers.
nizero: he's a nice guy
boc5: But you make the game?
slakkur: lul
GoldSkis: @georgehotz add me back on Linkeedin
whitsyerhing: shut it off people will leave, if you have an away people will hang around and keep it open in the background.
boc5: whp*
benchai18: I watched a video of a kid tell Milo Yiannapolous he’d let Milo fuck his girl. I might say that to George
boc5: Hate the player who promote the game
xyet: Black screen with music request
quickfloor: We don't talk anymore , like we used to do
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz aren't you tempted to tacke the problem of a more general AI than self-driving cars?
bongodrummer: what about founder meetups?
W1lkins: we saw the secrets again monkaS
cobaltstark1: How to start learning to code like you .. I am an undergrad ..
ItzRicky001: run some ads sourPoggers
Crypod: it only shows ur wallpaper when that happens
Protoxus: Yes, Milo Yiannopoulos is gay
benchai18: Yes
Nnotm: ooh you can draw an away image with draw.io
johnnyhotlava: I go to conferences if I get a free tickets from the radio station
rscarth: lmao
W1lkins: Play Greta's speech on repeat @georgehotz
Akash_44: LUL
benchai18: Infinity
MonkaSupreme: I hear you Kappa
dagobert2707: Why would anyone hate this girl :D (Grete)
whitsyerhing: New scene, with just an image, no mic, maybe music playing.
quickfloor: U can earn money with ASMR here
rscarth: west coast confirmed
johnnyhotlava: Elitist time
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz You can become next Schneier, or Mitnick or Hypponen. Going to conferences 5-star hotel, 1-st class ticket, plus a few k$. 2 confs / m-th and it's a good income
frankytex: angry asmr need to be a thing
quickfloor: No :(
Caene: Muting himself while explainging LUL
johnnyhotlava: lol
MonkaSupreme: 👂
notelex: LUL
quickfloor: LUL
BuySomeEther: he likes to abuse his keyboard
jax05_: lul
johnnyhotlava: well See yas in fideen
HS_SemenThrower: ASMR
MonkaSupreme: 👁️ 👃 👁️ 👂
boc5: i think that you can be a good player poker ggotz
whitsyerhing: Giving away the secrets of his OBS setup
superragetastic: wait aren't we all get ?
camkinstrike: do you ever game george? lol
frankytex: #actually
johnnyhotlava: I'm trying to developing my next fintech conference circle jerk. So I can capitalize on people that need a vacay
quickfloor: you have linkedin prime
Caene: no audio
sondreal: no
rscarth: no
Protoxus: No
Jannnik: no
UMPS: no
MDSZilla: No
Lambda_86: no
whitsyerhing: No
frankytex: no
Akash_44: No
DevoE444: turn of events he has dinner with greta
hectorrami: No
MonkaSupreme: 👂
ᅟᅟᅟᅟ: no
xyet: VoteNay VoteNay VoteNay VoteNay VoteNay
frankytex: he bust, but he fix
T_x_x_T: No
quickfloor: NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis
W1lkins: he's going to fix it for sure Kappa
MDSZilla: OBS Settings > Audio > Desktop Audio Device
Caene: ^
Navilist: he breaketh, but he fixeth
benchai18: Guys
benchai18: Can I not subscribe from the iOS app?
ᅟᅟᅟᅟ: SeemsGood
whitsyerhing: that worked!"#
boc5: worked for a sec
benchai18: Is this an Apple Tax thing?
W1lkins: Look at this top tier debugging PogChamp
MonkaSupreme: unplug the mic
MDSZilla: OBS Settings > Audio > Desktop Audio Device ? :P
Gregerncx: @benchai18 you cannot
Caene: Go to settings
johnnyhotlava: Take the break maaaan
hectorrami: There!
whitsyerhing: we just heard you say "that doesn't work" then it went mute again.
Caene: OBS settings and look for audio output settings
Lugueiro: SeemsGood SeemsGood
MonkaSupreme: just unplug the mic my dude
benchai18: @gregerncx thanks.
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz What about starting a podcast?: a mix of philosophy, ai, security. Like JRE, just knowing what you're talking about.
Akash_44: !uptime
hectorrami: Just heard u man
slakkur: brrea time! bacin 15! bye
MDSZilla: Its not detecting your speakers rip :/
knilecrack: yers
Caene: Disabled output devices DansGame
ProfessorMagikarp0: ill watch video on my own Kappa
slakkur: I cant type
ᅟᅟᅟᅟ: SeemsGood
whitsyerhing: there we go
whitsyerhing: oh
BoringMode: break is getting smaller and smaller
frankytex: no worries, we'll wait in silence while you number 2
hectorrami: it works
sondreal: just disable mic in mac settings, and activate sound Kappa
benchai18: “I heard George is creating a new jailbreak” pass it on
W1lkins: only subscribers can hear the music
ProfessorMagikarp0: ^ LUL
Jeppelelle: So, what are we doing now people?
frankytex: only lunatics can hear the music
eax_ebx: ееееееее бой
zeroeagle1: didnt george attend twitch con?
ProfessorMagikarp0: chat, have u found any good learning resources lately? PrideWingL luxxSquad PrideWingR
benchai18: I’d like to know too
johnny_thehobo: the conference companies send the killers after hotz?
benchai18: Suicided
UMPS: anyone have tips to gain motivation
frankytex: I'm going to draw.io through this silence
robby0313: What time zone?
Datamaskin: In 10 mins its 1.30 somewhere
Lugueiro: @UMPS discipline
UMPS: that's not motivation >:|
benchai18: Anyone know where he at? Obviously Pacific
Sarkin_dota: Why are we writing a language for
benchai18: Always wondered where he’s at
frankytex: looks like his house
UMPS: he's probably in texas
ProfessorMagikarp0: @UMPS u should want to work for geo one day is that motivational?
UMPS: wait nah
UMPS: is he in SF or LA or something
benchai18: Not Texas. Texas isn’t 1:30 right now
robby0313: He is in San Diego
BerrysYT: @Sarkin_dota "To prove things in" Kappa
ProfessorMagikarp0: look where is company hq is Kappa
benchai18: I dno but I’m in LA and if he is too I’d totally send him chocolates dicks
UMPS: @ProfessorMagikarp0 no
UMPS: working for someone is suicide enducing
benchai18: @umps you are so right. I just dipped out of a great job to hop on board as a partner/CMO of a startup cuz I’m sick of working for someone else
slakkur: he's in bay area right
ProfessorMagikarp0: so ud rather cause that feeling for someone else by running a company?
benchai18: No, because I’m not an antiquated prick
UMPS: LUL
ProfessorMagikarp0: im sure ur old boss would say that too
trchaosTR: what time it is ?
UMPS: i've thought about doing small applications that can be run by just 1 person
imcraxo: 6more mins
UMPS: i think ios would be a good market for that
benchai18: Lol fair enough. But I let my current employees have autonomy (if they’re capable)
Sawfare: is he back to apple again?
imcraxo: where is he working
xyet: He took a shit and didn't wash his hands again ?
knilecrack: ahahahaha
ProfessorMagikarp0: gotta get them gains Pog
trchaosTR: oh shit real gainz
eax_ebx: strong
MonkaSupreme: oh shit my boi is doing 20
MonkaSupreme: xD
ProfessorMagikarp0: geo trying to get that jail house body LUL
trchaosTR: punisher maybe @professormagikarp0
ProfessorMagikarp0: LUL
knilecrack: breath
xyet: prerecorded video?
llpwnage: this guy crazy :DDDDDDDDDDDDDD
BerrysYT: Prerecorded af
BerrysYT: CrreamAwk
eax_ebx: wtf
ProfessorMagikarp0: 5 pushups per sub lets get geo ripped KappaPride
NonTrivial778: the world doesn't care if we die
benchai18: @professormagikarp0 I work in e-commerce (high volume... millions of $ a month just on Amazon... not including $200k/month on Walmart and ebay) and I got tired of making millions for other people... people that could let me go at any moment, or override my efforts. If I had faith in them I’d have stayed. It’s not about not having a boss, it’s abt having faith in the leadership
xyet: triS triS This dudes mental state is questionable triS triS
NonTrivial778: LUL LUL
trchaosTR: i think he watched joker
chocolatechp: yikes
trchaosTR: maybe several times Kappa Kappa
NonTrivial778: solipsism
benchai18: Joker was interesting. Anyone see it?
whitsyerhing: dishes stream
Lugueiro: 1m2019.com
NonTrivial778: @xyet what did he said?
Lugueiro: dont forget
rscarth: dishwashing simulator
NonTrivial778: LUL
trchaosTR: i watched it @benchai18
goodgameezz: kkk
frankytex: that reminds me I have to turn on the dish washer damn it!
xyet: @NonTrivial778 nothing just doing weird shit
goodgameezz: real life live
hugo_kanazaca: the amount of water he is wasting lol
ProfessorMagikarp0: @benchai18 i know those feels too actually. i was just playing devils advocate because the issue seems to be that they dont think they are doing anything wrong and arnt doing it on purpose as far as i can tell. no one wants to be bad leadership
zoki_macola: We are watching another human being doing everyday stuff. We reached the highest peak
NonTrivial778: He's a part of the simulation
frankytex: slightly delayed real life live!
slakkur: I like that he's actually human, sometimes when I watch him code, I forget. :D
W1lkins: @georgehotz why could only subscribers hear the music during the break?
trchaosTR: wasting a lot water btw
theselectedcoder: "it's about showing off with your skills" -@georgehotz
knilecrack: welcome back mf
3even: Do you take BitcoinCash donations?
HS_SemenThrower: ;d
drivewaycam: george is back just in time
r00tdk: Do ctfs
lightofhel1: just in time
tomroxxx: Geore why are u wearing an Mavericks jogger?
whitsyerhing: wasting water. it falls from the sky.
drivewaycam: what a g
jax05_: wb
trchaosTR: yo george which phone do you use
ForsakenReborn: you know how to listen to good music @georgehotz
r00tdk: Ctfs
benchai18: @trchaostr What did u think of it? Joaquin is frighteningly talented
NonTrivial778: geohot do you have schizophrenia?
knilecrack: it's not wasted
r00tdk: Why did you quit on ctf?
Sarkin_dota: You're not a hydro homie
knilecrack: ahahahahahaha
frankytex: lmao
johnnyhotlava: WOAH
MonkaSupreme: everyone pays the same LUL _
whitsyerhing: i'll turn on the shower and then go for a poo while the shower is on
MonkaSupreme: ?
hackyhacks: yes
chocolatechp: about wha
knilecrack: bro, I'll come to USA next year we need to get go out for beer
3even: @georgehotz Do you take BitcoinCash donations?
johnnyhotlava: YES
r00tdk: Let us do ctf
johnnyhotlava: Tell us
whitsyerhing: shower is just going a good 5 mins before I get in
johnnyhotlava: FLOW LIMITERS IN SHOWERS
benchai18: Anyone here an iOS jailbreaker and know if it’s possible to have background audio when minimizing Twitch app?
johnnyhotlava: continue
NonTrivial778: geohot theres a ghost behind you
jax05_: jailbreak the shower
UMPS: get this man a better vim theme
slakkur: SUB2HOTZ! LUL
trchaosTR: @benchai18 i am big fan of heath ledger but i really like joaquin's act he is verry talented and maybe he'll win oscars
Jeppelelle: UMPS Gruvbox like everyone else?
MonkaSupreme: you need some real streamer emotes
Lugueiro: @UMPS UL
Lugueiro: LUL*
UMPS: Ayu @Jeppelelle
Sylens__: What programming language are you coding in @georgehotz
NonTrivial778: coq
johnnyhotlava: More flow charts
MonkaSupreme: is this a good book? @georgehotz
johnnyhotlava: Major regret for that "nice words" Python
jonathan865: what are we listening to?
johnnyhotlava: You translating?
trchaosTR: why his profile pic is too serious Kappa
UMPS: why not write it in the language you're writing 4Head
tfue_is_dog_shit: is this the matrix? Kappa
jax05_: cause he's a pro @trchaosTR
Sylens__: @nontrivial778 was that the language answer for me?
slakkur: does coq suck?
kluo84: wonder if George interested in Bug Bounty?
johnnyhotlava: Just make one of your minions build you a custom library
johnnyhotlava: then share it with me for coq
trchaosTR: i was thinking to study computer engineering but after this i'll think again NotLikeThis
Sarkin_dota: SUCC
johnnyhotlava: Ole euro language B.S.
slakkur: OMG, I could do lame coq jokes all day... ask my wife
jax05_: this is advanced stuff
eax_ebx: I'll better ask your mom.
jax05_: mom jokes :O
eax_ebx: From Ukraine with love.)
benchai18: @trchaostr I’m with you. As a Batman villain, Ledger is still the best for sure. As a psychological madman murdered, I think Joaquin took it. Like, I can’t imagine Joaquin’s Joker competing with Batman
benchai18: Murderer*
Sawfare: @georgehotz can you tell why you moved back to apple from your windows laptop?
Lil__Slap: Wpm Record?
slakkur: because windows sucks for coding python
ImpalerV: hello :) HeyGuys
eax_ebx: mb coz шindows is not a system?
NonTrivial778: Is the CIA watching us right now?
ImpalerV: lol, it doesn't suck... been doing it for years now :/
UMPS: you should start a kode scool
UMPS: school
johnnyhotlava: He get knowledge directly from those two fingers
jax05_: lol
eax_ebx: I love CIA. Very big fan.
ImpalerV: LUL
Lil__Slap: CIA watching football Rn
gerntt: do you prefer Mac or Linux
whitsyerhing: I want it as a matter of public record that I am team china.
whitsyerhing: for when they take over.
Sylens__: Mac
P3droPL: @georgehotz Why switch back to Mac?
johnnyhotlava: CIA dgaf, my dad was a programmer and a CIA contractor, he just watched a lot of cable news
johnnyhotlava: lol
UMPS: if mac could run i3 Kreygasm
Keyeh: windows is garbage
ImpalerV: LUL
trchaosTR: @benchai18 i usually dont watch dramatic movies but this movie wasn't that boring i hope joker 2 will come with more action
Santiago_LHC: Windows 7 is fine
ImpalerV: windows is fine
slakkur: @ImpalerV are you trolling? I've done both, and mac is so much better if you need a good terminal.
kluo84: unfortunately Windows still highest percentage out there
benchai18: @trchaostr Unfortunately, they said they’re not planning to make one
neill222: @georgehotz have you heard of lean? https://github.com/leanprover/lean looks like a more powerful theorem prover than coq
whitsyerhing: who cares, you will get used to whatever you are using.
Santiago_LHC: Joker 2 is not going to be a thing. The whole point was for it to be a standalone movie @trchaosTR
knilecrack: windows is good if you need terminal
UMPS: OBO windows wins hands down
UMPS: oops
UMPS: mac*
knilecrack: @whitsyerhing yeah
kluo84: powershell is not a joke now
trchaosTR: dont blame windows guys i still use intel dual core pc with win7
johnnyhotlava: Space back pack AI
smallest_cock: is this a twitch bot?
technicalb0y: hello
Santiago_LHC: Has George been silent this whole time?
ImpalerV: @slakkur sure, the terminal. that is pretty much all. it requires just a bit more effort to install stuff on windows but even that has been taken away by the anaconda terminal. also, now there is the subsystem on windows, so there's that too. and the new terminal is coming out soon, it is currently in beta
johnnyhotlava: He's channeling
dyslexicat: world is a beautiful place SourPls
Santiago_LHC: "He's wired in" like they say in The Social Network
Keyeh: did he take l-theanine? he's so focused
UMPS: he popped an addy
technicalb0y: george can u share tmux conf file, or do you have a dotfiles repo
johnnyhotlava: LOLOLOL
Lil__Slap: Flow state AF
whitsyerhing: autism engaged
johnnyhotlava: Zooted and booted
technicalb0y: if you have
johnnyhotlava: 500 mg
neroo2k: what's the concept behind this program
johnnyhotlava: whopped up
whitsyerhing: fully weaponised
gunnaren: He's streaming under 'basic programming', that couldn't be more wrong LUL
trchaosTR: @santiago_lhc sad :(
Lil__Slap: Mo' like top tier programming
knilecrack: @gunnaren ahaha yeah
ZerkBtw: what are you listening to?
johnnyhotlava: His speed without making millions of mistakes is beautiful
UMPS: when he puts the two fingers to his head, he's symlinking to Mark Zuckerberg and tying into the Lizard Mainframe.
smallest_cock: I like the clean shave
julen9601: @Keyeh aderall
trchaosTR: dc will release harley quinn next year
Santiago_LHC: @trchaosTR it's great actually, not everything needs sequels and prequels. We have to learn to enjoy things for what they are.
benchai18: Can any software with a GUI that can be made for Linux (Debian) also be made for MacOS? You don’t use ObjC to make Windows software.. I guess I’m wondering which language can be used on the most operating systems. Besides Java. Ew.
jax05_: @johnnyhotlava I feel like he's slower than norm rn lmao
dyslexicat: ZerkBtw last song was "the world is a beautiful place & i am no longer afraid to die - gig life"
gunnaren: OSFrog Mark Zuckerberg OSFrog
johnnyhotlava: @jax05_ Yeah he's still thinking RN
technicalb0y: george do you have any dotfiles repo, can i see your tmux conf file?
johnnyhotlava: lolol
nanodanger7: @technicalb0y github.com/geohot/configuration
smallest_cock: sho bobs
brizzz_: @benchai18 Javascript/Electrom
technicalb0y: @nanodanger7 thanks
johnnyhotlava: It's not defined
knilecrack: how do you detel a word between () in vim?
knilecrack: delete*
benchai18: @brizzz_ 🍻
blazelp1: What for a Monitor are u using 4K?
Lil__Slap: if you dont understand imagine what twitch chat feels like
W1lkins: di( @knilecrack
nanodanger7: @knilecrack di(
knilecrack: @W1lkins thx
Sylens__: @blazelp1 i would like to know as well
nanodanger7: @knilecrack you can di with a lot more things it means "delete inside"
trchaosTR: twitch android app randomly crashed btw SeemsGood
xRaptorz: what keyboard is he using?
W1lkins: hhkb
roxaneb_: geo looking good, but with beard even better, me thinks
xRaptorz: tyty
knilecrack: @nanodanger7 yeah just tried it
3even: Best ebook reader for programming books? I find that many butcher the code examples
UMPS: what switches
Santiago_LHC: beardless George can type 20 words per minute faster than with beard.
trchaosTR: maybe my next phone will be iphone Kappa
benchai18: Does anyone know how old he is?
W1lkins: they are topre switches @UMPS
smallest_cock: 23
Santiago_LHC: @benchai18 Google much?
18ace81: I just got there is he writing proof assistant?
trchaosTR: he is 45 years old
trchaosTR: but he got baby face
benchai18: @santiago_lhc fair enough. Minimizing Twitch pauses the stream
keepingtrckofthisacct: almost looks like it
NonTrivial778: is your linkedin a datting place ? LUL
smallest_cock: nah he can pass as 45
trchaosTR: look how focused he is
zoki_macola: Anybody built/worked with Ukkonens Suffix Tree?
Santiago_LHC: He is actually 12
benchai18: Wow he’s same age as me. Makes me feel kinda stupid TBH
gunnaren: Imagine what george can do in a day vs your averge joe programmer
18ace81: wait is he or is he not writing a proof assistant
benchai18: (His real age is same as me. Not 12 or 45)
trchaosTR: @benchai18 dont worry i dont even speak english
johnnyhotlava: What else can you translate coq to other than that demon python?
jax05_: I was about to call twitch police @benchai18
gunnaren: @benchai18 yea we expected more from you at this point *dissapointed boomer face*
benchai18: @gunnaren *sips Kale shake in shame*
trchaosTR: i am killing grammar every letter i wrote
reptil1990: @georgehotz what are you coding? or what should it do at the end?
eax_ebx: which band is playing?
18ace81: I think it's a proof assistant but I just got here and no one is answering my questions @reptil1990
18ace81: use Haskell lmao
johnnyhotlava: He's making coq proof a theorem of boolian algebra that he wants to translate to python
johnnyhotlava: De somthing
Lambda_86: use rust
gunnaren: @benchai18 *shakes head while finding essential oils to counter your behavior*
Santiago_LHC: Is Ruby still a thing?
18ace81: yeah
eax_ebx: yep
slakkur: c# is typed and you can go back to windows LUL
benchai18: @jax05_ haha. Are 12 year olds not allowed? Or can’t disclose age? I’ve been on Twitch for like a week
tfue_is_dog_shit: is java dead?
trchaosTR: 12 years cant stream thats illegal
jax05_: I think you have to be 13 lol
ᅟᅟᅟᅟ: LUL
18ace81: java is far from dead unfortunately
benchai18: @gunnaren *fondles crystal in left pocket while looking around for a safe space*
johnnyhotlava: Python DGAF what you want to write python wants to play with lego's
davidvilla700: ??
K0shpt: @tfue_is_dog_shit It should
lavastew: java master race
johnnyhotlava: Farmers insurance is currently building a brand new infrastructure on JAVA
benchai18: WE ARE FARMERS
johnnyhotlava: They are
benchai18: DUN DUN DUN DUN DUN DUN DUN
johnnyhotlava: Dorks
Santiago_LHC: Coder Farmers Ninjas
Divulger1: @georgehotz what monitor do you use?
ᅟᅟᅟᅟ: 🤔
gunnaren: @benchai18 hahahah - this is getting out of hand
smurfd0: "it is easy"
johnnyhotlava: LOL
MonkaSupreme: water water h2o
trchaosTR: i think he broke his razer laptop while playing video games
slakkur: @georgehotz where did you learn all your math skills? Did you go to college?
r00tdk: Did you buy apple watch 5 @georgehotz
18ace81: I'm very confused as to what he is using lark for can anyone explain?
trchaosTR: alien attack
johnnyhotlava: So he's done with coq now right?
mariuss18: he is like building a rocket
ZerkBtw: lmao
notelex: KKona
Santiago_LHC: @r00tdk he showed it on stream a few days ago
xyet: LET US SEE! LET US SEE!
johnnyhotlava: That's a straight up parade
nikhilr14: yo its my dream to watch ur stream live , finally came true
trchaosTR: oh 2 pm means 14.00
r00tdk: @santiago_lhc which stream
eax_ebx: Yeah, America.
neroo2k: is this still maths ? I feel stupid :P
r00tdk: Can you tell title
nikhilr14: !uptime
blazelp1: Thank god u stopped using Windows
johnnyhotlava: Fucking antlr
johnnyhotlava: well it is an upgrade
NonTrivial778: it's Mac not windows
18ace81: wait is he writing a coq implementation?
slakkur: @georgehotz did you get all your math in HS? or did you learn it on your own?
benchai18: How does @georgehotz make money? Does he have a company? Or multiple?
nikhilr14: what is he doing today?
johnnyhotlava: George is money
ZeeZaxean: he is an instagram influencer
neroo2k: @benchai18 comma ai
jax05_: lol
slakkur: comma.ai
johnnyhotlava: @ZeeZaxean lolololol
johnnyhotlava: stop
benchai18: @nikhilr14 he’s drawing diagrams
ZeeZaxean: LUL
18ace81: honestly formal logic isn't that hard to learn in that it has no preqs @slakkur
trchaosTR: have a nice day guys i'll sleep good luck @georgehotz
benchai18: @trchaostr peace
nikhilr14: @benchai18 diagrams using AI ?
jax05_: cya @trchaosTR FutureMan
benchai18: (That means bye in American)
trchaosTR: i knew it SeemsGood SeemsGood
slakkur: Hmm I'll have to see if khan academy has it, once I figure out what i can apply it too.
benchai18: @nikhilr14 nah. Diagrams about conferences.
trchaosTR: i would be happy if u accept my friendship requests @benchai18
Tal_X_Tal: yayeetP
benchai18: @trchaostr I did
18ace81: @slakkur if you want to get into proof assistants and stuff, my gateway drug was Idris, since you can also write actual programs in it
benchai18: @18ace81 my gateway drug was hydrocodone
johnnyhotlava: @benchai18 HELL YEAH BOIZE
fafws321: Turk var mı reisler
trchaosTR: oh okay cya
nikhilr14: I wish I can subscribe to him but twitch prime doesn't support in my country
trchaosTR: @fafws321 var kanka da türkçe konuşma pek SeemsGood
chexmixz: Is the title click bait or is he just using coq language?
fafws321: Kappa
johnnyhotlava: Coq at first
johnnyhotlava: Then he inserted the coq
nikhilr14: how long he been streaming
18ace81: @chexmixz no he was writing what looked like a python implementation of coq for like half a second a while ago
slakkur: I didn't see the beginning of the stream, what is george trying to do with coq, just exploring it for fun? That sounds wrong, but I'm sincere.
johnnyhotlava: He wants to put his coq into python
Tal_X_Tal: 2:56
18ace81: @johnnyhotlava basically lmao
johnnyhotlava: LOLOLOL
nikhilr14: thats been long time
nikhilr14: did his girl friend showed up today ?
johnnyhotlava: I know
montecarlo: what keyboard does george use
johnnyhotlava: Hey what's the name of the theorem though I forgot what he said it was?
Lamb03: Love ur video about exploit
nikhilr14: poison distribution theroem?
benchai18: if BBC >= 9 else
Lamb03: What’s coq?
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz maybe we should teleport to the world where true == false
benchai18: @lamb03 About 9 inches on a good day
Divulger1: what monitor do you use
johnnyhotlava: Boolean inches
hackyhacks: negate P = P NAND P
nikhilr14: omg he just read my comment I lived my life
Jewishrambo: Any proof by contradiction ? True is false lol
montecarlo: keyboard sounds like topre switches
yaus_baus: its an hhkb
Divulger1: @montecarlo it is
0Day_H4X0rz: Hello @georgehotz and Chat from Germany
goolyio: !uptime
slakkur: I have a logitech with romer-g switches, sounds just like it, I love it too, got mx blues at the office, like my logitech more now.
knilecrack: wsupp germany serbia here
benchai18: NSNumber *coqLength
nikhilr14: is he creating his own programming language"
smurfd0: you are mentioned as streaming in /r/coq :)
0Day_H4X0rz: @knilecrack Hello
benchai18: Definitely took an addy
Divulger1: @yaus_baus do you know what monitor size does he use
johnnyhotlava: The long flowing nature of python will allow the coq he built to fit inside however pythons opening wont allow his coq in
theewbc: LIVE from the cloud!!
benchai18: @johnnyhotlava I like u. Ur crazy. But I like u
yaus_baus: @Divulger1 no clue
johnnyhotlava: @benchai18 Lol
18ace81: why is he making a sum type with only one option wtf
slakkur: wrapping coq with python...
st47ik: Kappa
benchai18: Does he take Adderall XR or regular?
nikhilr14: guys is he uisng tmux for multiple session creations?
knilecrack: What is NAT' ?
johnnyhotlava: XR or you're an addict
st47ik: @benchai18 he takes tea :)
slakkur: tmux ftw
에스엔엑스: @nikhilr14 yes
benchai18: @johnnyhotlava I know. But I grind the XR beads to bypass the time release
slakkur: I just use split in vim... I don't know tmux well
johnnyhotlava: @benchai18 lol chew them like a man
johnnyhotlava: Get em stuck in your teeth
johnnyhotlava: lololol
benchai18: @johnnyhotlava I did that yesterday in the car lol. Just doesn’t hit as well
johnnyhotlava: LOL
yaus_baus: george uber eats some chicken, its only fitting for coq stream
slakkur: I need to learn vim like george though, holy moly he's good
nikhilr14: vim split for spliting editor , tmux split for windows split @slakkur
RishabhDeepSingh: Heyy
johnnyhotlava: Chicken = False
yaus_baus: chicken bootloader asmr
slakkur: I mostly use vscode, only vim when I'm remoting. love vscode
johnnyhotlava: Real humans watch ASMR? I thought it was only bots.
homestarr: vim is for boomers
Joy_void_Joy: Don't know if this has been mentioned, but I really recommand the ssreflect add-on/dsl instead of pure coq.
NonTrivial778: username checks out
nikhilr14: guys share some of the vim commands he uses
benchai18: def growCoq: coq=0; while coq < 9: coq
slakkur: I what blows my mind is watching how efficient george is using vim mode in vscode... that's crazy, atleast I think that was what he was doin.
Joy_void_Joy: (What is the definition of eqb' you're using? Just joined in)
benchai18: @georgehotz I’ll order you postmates right now just say the word. Fr
johnnyhotlava: Everybody's got their own methods for what they do to prove their own coq but he wants a pure coq
johnnyhotlava: No protection
yaus_baus: you can take the person out of vim but you cant take vim out of the person
benchai18: He’s probably studying the py3 CoqLibrary
johnnyhotlava: Vim is a cia litmus test
nikhilr14: its hard to understand stream joining in middle , Its better to wattch on youtube
slakkur: if you can prove your coq, you don't need protection
johnnyhotlava: lol
RomanNYC: Can you simpl first?
benchai18: @nikhilr14 Does he put them on YouTube
tomroxxx: tomroxxx subscribed with Twitch Prime.
yaus_baus: @benchai18 comma archive channel
nikhilr14: he doesn't coma ai will put in their youtube channerl , which is ownded by him @benchai18
Joy_void_Joy: Did you try inversion?
Joy_void_Joy: That's what you usually want to do in your case
krnflake1: what osx apps are you using? spectacle, obs, but what are the other two in your menu bar? the height icon and the mouse thing?
Joy_void_Joy: inversion H
Lambda_86: case analysis?
Joy_void_Joy: After introducing it
johnnyhotlava: Slicker than owl shit
SnakeOneMLG: !uptime
SnakeOneMLG: not on windows anymote PogChamp
exenu: not even ELI5 can help me understand wtf hes doing
slakkur: @exenu yah I'm lost
benchai18: benchai18 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
johnnyhotlava: fornicate that library
prakyath_kantharaju: prakyath_kantharaju subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 3 months!
dalwin401: I’m eating Spicy nuggets tryna see what’s popping up in this stream
montecarlo: monkaS
st47ik: earthquake?
LazyAfternoons: monkaS
exenu: he's talking to us like we understand what hes saying
johnnyhotlava: you don't go look guys that's who goes first
johnnyhotlava: Safe room
torlkhal: WHAT THE PLAN
johnnyhotlava: @dalwin401 those nuggs are not safe
benchai18: @lazyafternoons Can you exblain what monkaS is
johnnyhotlava: lol
LazyAfternoons: Are you typing on a Topre keyboard?
psychicside: @benchai18 monkaS
LazyAfternoons: @benchai18 It's an emote used to express tension
LazyAfternoons: I think it used to be part of Twitch standard emotes
johnnyhotlava: That has been linked to "stuff" allegedly
psychicside: newfags LUL
Joy_void_Joy: Is proving that eqb' x y <-> x = y off limit?
benchai18: @lazyafternoons 😘
MDSZilla: @LazyAfternoons I've heard he uses HHKB
johnnyhotlava: Gewgle it
LazyAfternoons: @MDSZilla Seems that's the case, Torpe switches for sure
LazyAfternoons: Topre*
benchai18: PrimeRlyTho
slakkur: dang, I need to catch this on youtube so I can see the beginning when he explains why he's trying to do with coq... jesus how do I say this without it sounding wrong
krnflake1: sry to ask again: what osx apps are you using? spectacle, obs, but what are the other two in your menu bar? the height icon and the mouse thing?
G0NERZ: hi
benchai18: He’s trying to disassemble coq
psychicside: but why
smurfd0: https://stackoverflow.com/questions/47523376/coq-true-false-discriminate-fails-no-primitive-equality isnt that something like what u are trying todo..
psychicside: go to the shelters monkaS
jax05_: they're coming for you george
averagesizepens: where is the robot girl?
st47ik: NotLikeThis
johnnyhotlava: Construction & parades as well as coq insertion
HS_SemenThrower: ggwp
averagesizepens: LUL
dorkmo: from north korean subs?
johnnyhotlava: Hardcore
nikhilr14: he looks shit scared of earthquake or terrorist attack
ProfessorMagikarp0: luxxGun
ImpalerV: LUL
psychicside: see you next life @georgehotz Kappa
knilecrack: everytime you type destruct one more bomb explodes
TopicOffic: hey yo georgie ahaha
prakyath_kantharaju: you banned North Koreans, they are attacking cali now.
G0NERZ: hack live mrdang3rAim
johnnyhotlava: @knilecrack direct correlation
johnnyhotlava: He's DOING IT
TopicOffic: he's hacking the code
johnnyhotlava: lol
johnnyhotlava: That's not a knife
1garo: wow
nikhilr14: North koreans trying to take out him
johnnyhotlava: THIS IS A KNIFE
prakyath_kantharaju: shit singularity is here guys
johnnyhotlava: @prakyath_kantharaju I'd hope it's faster
knilecrack: his destruct has delay
johnnyhotlava: slow agony is B.S
Sznurek066: George Hotz is playing "Welcome to the game" irl. LUL
benchai18: Is there a single person here that knows what he’s doing?
MDSZilla: @benchai18 read the title LUL
torlkhal: thats a user freidnly languague
averagesizepens: o persons includin george
johnnyhotlava: Like a glossy moronic overview sorta like how I know the sun is hot
benchai18: @mdszilla I did. Doesn’t help
benchai18: I’m just here for the coqs at this point
MDSZilla: @benchai18 Well that's what he's doing.
3even: @benchai18 google coq language
torlkhal: whats the big picture
johnnyhotlava: Jusssst had to do his own library
G0NERZ: mrdang3rThink
johnnyhotlava: Chicken ='s ass
slakkur: I'm not enjoying the coq, it's too hard
Joy_void_Joy: I don't know that this can be done by hand
Joy_void_Joy: In ssr, you'd just define your induction differently
Joy_void_Joy: And in vanilla Coq, use inversion, because it relies on binding done by the inductive definition
st47ik: WutFace
averagesizepens: attack inc
Phantomhive_: coq files redux?
johnnyhotlava: Oh that's a jet
johnnyhotlava: There's a few special forces outposts don't worry
st47ik: air force drill?
johnnyhotlava: They just get real erect around there
RishabhDeepSingh: codeforces.com went under DDSOS @georgehotz
HS_SemenThrower: change title to: paranoid kid on ritalin
benchai18: @johnnyhotlava wasn’t the coq too large for that memory address? I think coq type is “long long” but he’s trying to store coq as an int
3even: Navy exercise
MDSZilla: @georgehotz I saw a interview of you on Youtube, In which you said OS and Compiler were the best classes you ever took, In what way did those classes help you improve and learn more about the backend working
psychicside: It is Kappa
Erciks: i dont know but someone did got shot
whitsyerhing: I don't think he washed his hands boys...
johnnyhotlava: @benchai18 lololol
johnnyhotlava: stupid
averagesizepens: mexico taking san diego back
johnnyhotlava: love you
benchai18: 😇
Joy_void_Joy: inversion
ortunado: Happy Birthday on ur 30 bud FeelsBirthdayMan
Joy_void_Joy: inversion H. I mean
johnnyhotlava: Yeah just switch to "vanilla" fuck all that library boner work
johnnyhotlava: or something
RomanNYC: @georgehotz if you do "Show Proof." you can see that it does some pattern matching on eqb'
RomanNYC: (after doing inversion)
benchai18: def coqInversion: gender == “trans”
MDSZilla: I saw a interview of you on Youtube, In which you said OS and Compiler were the best classes you ever took, In what way did those classes help you improve and learn more about the backend working, since I just started college and really do want to learn the development process and nerual networking.
johnnyhotlava: Lernin?
Foxhaulin: What’s up George, hope you are doing good
Divulger1: what monitor size do you use @georgehotz
Joy_void_Joy: Ltac is really unusable yeah...
johnnyhotlava: Learning that nice interface
st47ik: oh god WutFace
chaprio1: monkaS
knilecrack: they defined everything from begging so ti was easy for them
benchai18: if isSet(coq.inversion) gender = “trans”
johnnyhotlava: LOLOLOL
johnnyhotlava: Stop it
benchai18: Ok ok
giorgostheo97: The f macbook is that ?
johnnyhotlava: That was really good for me
johnnyhotlava: at least
kluo84: is it earthquake ?
benchai18: @johnnyhotlava it was for u
johnnyhotlava: @benchai18 I'm still laughing at it for some reason
Santiago_LHC: THere's a marching band outside
RomanNYC: I'm pretty sure inversion pattern matches on the proof state to get the constructor that created the expression of type eqb'
ardzybro: Which MacBook Pro you using and what are the specs
nexscion: !uptime
Santiago_LHC: People obssesed with hardware and specs
Joy_void_Joy: Seeing how you defined eqb', I don't think you can do it by hand?
Joy_void_Joy: Because you rely on binding both parameters to the same value
nanodanger7: @Santiago_LHC honestly these questions are getting so boring :D I wish George would add a bot so we could make command for FAQs
Santiago_LHC: !keyboard
johnnyhotlava: I feel like that episode of it's always sunny when charlie thinks he can speak Chinese
nanodanger7: yeah that's not gon work
Santiago_LHC: should be the main one
knilecrack: what matters that is works
Santiago_LHC: Exactly
r1ppyd1ppy: ffs guys. HHKB2
Lambda_86: im 90% sure based on his typos that he uses dvorak
johnnyhotlava: People actually use dvorak?
nanodanger7: yeah but HHKB 2 guys you'll become an 10x engineer instantly
johnnyhotlava: for real
nanodanger7: buy*
metasudo: He uses one of those default logitech bluetooth keyboards
jax05_: lol
HS_SemenThrower: oh don't forget to sell coding gloves
abk467: i believe it. i'll take 10
ProfessorMagikarp0: ^
johnnyhotlava: @HS_SemenThrower lol
Longboolean: Fischer price lern to type keyboard Kappa
giorgostheo97: Is it Dvorak tho?
beltez: Hi George
metasudo: Sell me engineering enlargement pills,
Santiago_LHC: Also, we need his chair, don't forget the chair.
johnnyhotlava: I'm packing actual crystal meth into tubes and selling them as 10x addy xr.
prakyath_kantharaju: Yep that works, justy like razer you can sell Geozer
MDSZilla: georgehotz when you started your journey for programming what sort of projects did you do at start to learn?
johnnyhotlava: "programmers"
ooMariaoo: ouu
benchai18: @johnnyhotlava Can I get a sample?
johnnyhotlava: @benchai18 I GOCCHUUU
Erciks: programmer socks best socks
Santiago_LHC: Programming phylosophy
johnnyhotlava: Say yo coq it aint true
nanodanger7: you
MDSZilla: Use a if statement? Kappa I'm still learning C im new to this world
johnnyhotlava: Hey coq listen up
amuzinc: @georgehotz did you watch the buzzard talk?
benchai18: @johnnyhotlava I haven’t smoked tweak in 4 yrs. Haven’t shot it in 3 lol 😆
nanodanger7: you'll also need to buy a razer laptop and then sell it after a few months on ebay
Santiago_LHC: if not true then false
johnnyhotlava: @benchai18 lolol
johnnyhotlava: Plug it
johnnyhotlava: direct injection
johnnyhotlava: save the liver
benchai18: Dude it burns
benchai18: I have lol
johnnyhotlava: lol
johnnyhotlava: killing me
MrMarkFilaroski: Why is everyone Go unfriendly?
Santiago_LHC: I like Go, but the game
MrMarkFilaroski: @Santiago_LHC yeah.. I get it
metasudo: all have succ real
MrMarkFilaroski: Kafta Go?
knilecrack: Go is nice
johnnyhotlava: @benchai18 water soluable vegetable caps my man
nexscion: what's an inversion?
amuzinc: @georgehotz will you make a better lean
johnnyhotlava: Error: We don't actually provide the freedom of definition we pretend to.
Joy_void_Joy: Well, if you're okay with proving eqb' x y -> x = y, then you can just use trivial. But maybe it's using built-ins you want to avoid
Sylens__: !monitor
Joy_void_Joy: Inversion just checks how a term could have been constructed, it works it "backward"
metasudo: Is that your bed to your right?
Lambda_86: simpl
preporyan: !uptime
Joy_void_Joy: You can't compute a Prop
speeddrawing101: !uptime
Joy_void_Joy: It has to be a set
Joy_void_Joy: You can make a function on bool, that check if they're equal
johnnyhotlava: Joy is so erect
Joy_void_Joy: Sorry, tell me if I'm backseating too much :D
MDSZilla: Inb4 Joy_void_Joy made Coq Kappa
benchai18: @johnnyhotlava It’s not enough lol. Once u turn to shooting, nothing else compares. Good thing I cut all that shit out a few years ago 😅 ... life is way more stable now (albeit kinda boring)
thekillerens0: Yo
metasudo: look at the big brain on joy
thekillerens0: Hi
johnnyhotlava: @benchai18 awesome man that's a good life choice
zoki_macola: we will call him Big Brain Joy
benchai18: @johnnyhotlava thanks bruh
MDSZilla: Compare two of those things if they're same its true if they're not its false?
Nnotm: Have you looked at agda at all?
jax05_: @benchai18 congrats dude
Joy_void_Joy: Well, like you could do this: Definition eqb x y := match x, y with |true, true => true |false, false => true |_, _ => false end.
Joy_void_Joy: Oops, no return
benchai18: @jax05_ Thank you ☺️
benchai18: Did you guys know that “bool-bool” means dick in Hebrew?
Joy_void_Joy: And then, you'd be done
Nnotm: so that would be the conventional ==?
solitaryyy: What is `.g` extension?
MrMarkFilaroski: This is better than sex
Nnotm: -> is more like implies, not equals
Sylens__: @georgehotz what 4K monitor do you use?
archeadis: @georgehotz did you stop using tiling wms?
Santiago_LHC: Enough with the hardware questions!
Joy_void_Joy: So it'd be eqb' x y <-> eqb'' x y?
benchai18: @mrmarkfilaroski I just sent a dev friend of mine a link to this stream and I wrote “watching this guy work makes me stiff”
Erciks: i think i understood something
benchai18: @erciks I’m jealous
MDSZilla: For those asking questions about hardware and stuff, Visit georgehotz Instagram he posted a pic of his setup
MDSZilla: Hopefully you guys can scout out what he uses there
jax05_: and don't forget to follow
Santiago_LHC: https://www.instagram.com/georgehotz/
johnnyhotlava: My girl thinks Jorge is handsum
Santiago_LHC: Setup: https://www.instagram.com/p/Bx0DMrUAxE-/
MrMarkFilaroski: Hardware=Firmware= why do I buy my Athena's from Sweden? haha
Sylens__: @santiago_lhc why you so salty about the questions
MrMarkFilaroski: @benchai18 LUL jeffgrossCu fintFINGERS
Santiago_LHC: @Sylens__ I'm not salty, I'm annoyed by the same noob questions every 10 seconds.
Santiago_LHC: Who freaking cares what monitor does he use
Sylens__: @santiago_lhc deal with it ppl are new and not aware
MrMarkFilaroski: antenna's*
MDSZilla: Santiago_LHC you dont have to reply :)
Sylens__: Ikr
Santiago_LHC: The point is that it doesn't matter.
MDSZilla: george has his instagram linked below those who have common sense would visit his instagram and look there instead of asking it in chat before checking.
johnnyhotlava: It's the secret to becoming great is mimicking accessories. Nike has built a business on that
benchai18: What kind of desk do you use? And what sort of mouse pad?
johnnyhotlava: Faulty human circuits
jax05_: lol
MDSZilla: benchai18 Ikea LUL
Santiago_LHC: HEY GEORGE; WHAT AIR DO YOU BREATHE
benchai18: Lol
Sylens__: Yeah okay
Joy_void_Joy: apply eqb_refll?
Rtc_ti5: !
faulpelzz: Perrieair
jax05_: lmao
zoki_macola: Macbook Air
Luccaasss: what is he doing?
MDSZilla: at this time this false false = true and true, true = true is making me thing of Quantum Computing
benchai18: DO YOU USE A NUTRI-BULLET OR NINJA BLENDER?
nanodanger7: we should just go back to the old days when asking about keyboard and shit was bannable :D
johnnyhotlava: Kuwait is the world leader in coq inversion
benchai18: Lmao
johnnyhotlava: Slap chop
Joy_void_Joy: You always use function if you can, instead of Inductive properties, because you can just compute them :D
benchai18: I think @johnnyhotlava is my long lost brother
essSau: hi
johnnyhotlava: @benchai18 Gotta be
Santiago_LHC: The word keyboard should be an auto-ban
johnnyhotlava: lol
SHREKonVHS: my name gay
nexscion: damn then you just got banned
benchai18: @santiago_lhc 1
Santiago_LHC: OH NO
MDSZilla: Move on from hardware talks dont drag it
SHREKonVHS: ur mom nama jef
SHREKonVHS: ur mom nama jef XD
johnnyhotlava: Hardware is so last week
Joy_void_Joy: You can?
benchai18: Santiago, do you work at CERN?
Joy_void_Joy: You can just compute it
SHREKonVHS: hack the mainframe you idiot
SHREKonVHS: enhance
Sarkin_dota: Must be nice stroking coq code on that keyboard
johnnyhotlava: Well "large" is relative so
Santiago_LHC: @benchai18 Nah, just a fan of colliding particles
johnnyhotlava: He could work on a colider anywhere
benchai18: @santiago_lhc sick
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz coq is so-so, why won't you try to find some vulns in the fabric of the universe, and we'll all escape to the 1
benchai18: Large Hadron Coqllider
johnnyhotlava: lol
MDSZilla: Chat has activated its Meme Mode FailFish
Sarkin_dota: hardon
Joy_void_Joy: wait, why do we want to prove that again?
Joy_void_Joy: like, what's the endgoal
benchai18: @sarkin_dota Damnit. You win
Joy_void_Joy: I mean
Santiago_LHC: Large hardon collider. That's a drinking game somewhere
IEEKl: anyone in chat, macbook pro or new surface laptop for programming?
Joy_void_Joy: If you want to prove eqb' x y, you now can do eqb'' x y
Justanotherantiantiplayer: @IEEKl x230
Joy_void_Joy: That's just the idea behind it
johnnyhotlava: CLack book bro 32 cm
xxdvxx: pro for sure @ieekl
benchai18: @joy_void_joy is the only person that knows what’s happening
okkessh: do we want to prove other things using our theorem once we prove it ?
Santiago_LHC: You can program on the shittiest of computers @IEEKI so pick the one you like the most
Nnotm: haven't done anything with coq in a long time but it seems like you might need decidable equality for proving something like this
Justanotherantiantiplayer: i like when its exiting for a minute ( ͡° ͜ʖ ͡°)
MDSZilla: Joy_void_Joy you seem like a person who has been experimenting with coq and has been programming, I'm just getting started could you tell me what sort of projects you did on your own while learning
johnnyhotlava: Joy has a superior imminens fronti pontificis
xxdvxx: interesting you're not using window manager
annasgrasshopper: coolest guy on the tech industry
SHREKonVHS: im gay
jay_al97: you're on mac today?
benchai18: @shrekonvhs Checks out
jax05_: jfc
knilecrack: what do you need?
fSyLyndon: @SHREKonVHS hi gay im dad
IEEKl: or i maybe asked the question wrong, why is macbook pro better? (cuz it seems like many programmers prefere a ios but i have always coded in windows) @xxdvxx @Santiago_LHC
Tsuisekii: !time
mexeroserisback: any opinions on Lear vs Coq?
annasgrasshopper: use linu
annasgrasshopper: linux
whichtom: cmd tab?
Justanotherantiantiplayer: @IEEKl did you just say ios?
johnnyhotlava: you guys have os's?
tfue_is_dog_shit: this is the best twitch channel i have ever watched
jax05_: lol
Santiago_LHC: @IEEKI If you want to make apps for iOS, having a Mac would make sense. But if you are used to Windows, no reason to switch.
johnnyhotlava: I'm doing this by hand
MDSZilla: 1 is not 0 but 0 is 1 ?
SHREKonVHS: im the creator of the checkm8 exploit ama
Nnotm: maybe you really shouldn't destruct? Seems like if you have eqb' x y, you should be able to get eq_refl out of that whole thing, which proves that x and y must be equal
jrrbls: !online
Justanotherantiantiplayer: @johnnyhotlava im just saying xkcd 378
knilecrack: ls
knilecrack: ups
benchai18: @shrekonvhs wen A13 eta son
IEEKl: @Santiago_LHC ok
Froopyland: @tfue_is_dog_shit you come from fortnite? you got a long way ahead
Nnotm: IIRC those are for using specific tactics like induction
puffnfresh: I love it when you stream Coq
jax05_: @IEEKl you should get a feel for coding on different platforms and pick what you like best.
Lambda_86: i think discriminate uses eq_ind
tfue_is_dog_shit: @Froopyland no i am html programmer
johnnyhotlava: @Justanotherantiantiplayer I mean I'm using a pencil that's high level shit llol
Joy_void_Joy: eqb'_ind is an induction lemma
puffnfresh: prop is proposition?
FaustPetrovich: @tfue_is_dog_shit yeah, it’s the best channel, but sadly he is more concentrated on his instagram career
Joy_void_Joy: On nat, it would be peano's induction
nanodanger7: html is not a programming lang bro
benchai18: Guys I’ve been sitting on the toilet for like 2 hours on this chat
Bagofpotatoes: Reit?
Froopyland: tfue plays fortnite right? anyway, coding channels are pretty good and geo's one of the best imo
benchai18: Legs are numb frfr
nexscion: why is coq so confusing?
Santiago_LHC: @benchai18 commit that shit already
Justanotherantiantiplayer: @Santiago_LHC LUL
puffnfresh: I really like Agda for proving
IEEKl: @jax05_ yeah i guess but i feel like if you buy one apple product then u kinda stuck in the apple ecosystem
Bagofpotatoes: Idris seems nicer than this
Joy_void_Joy: @nexscion Because we purposefully disabled everything to make it less so :D
benchai18: Can I make a coq pull request
johnnyhotlava: YES
jax05_: @IEEKl not necessarily. I like having both tho
johnnyhotlava: Forbidden fruit ecosystem
johnnyhotlava: Lower dimension products
jax05_: @IEEKl it's just that most people prefer unix based systems so that's why they say mac or linux. it's less bulky than windows
Demografixx: what are you doing ?
okkessh: isn't coq an unfortunate name ?
johnnyhotlava: Python don't want it
tfue_is_dog_shit: who you chose python
puffnfresh: what's the goal?
tfue_is_dog_shit: why*
benchai18: Anyone interested in UFO’s? Cmdr Dave Fravor was on Rogan yesterday. Worth watching
Santiago_LHC: so many existencial questions
puffnfresh: @okkessh it means chicken
johnnyhotlava: @benchai18 haven't finished it
benchai18: Same
IEEKl: @jax05_ true
benchai18: Lol he said coq
Joy_void_Joy: It would be easier to understand them if you checked bool_ind
Justanotherantiantiplayer: @IEEKl just use what you have or what you can afford. learn to code dont worry about "right" or "wrong" os, language, tool etc. When you figure out what you are interested in switch to the best tools for that
Joy_void_Joy: Or nat_ind
Lambda_86: i believe eq_ind is used for induction and eq_rec is used for recursion
Joy_void_Joy: They are induction lemma automatically generated
okkessh: @Joy_void_Joy are you involved in coq project in any way
xEHLE_: @Joy_void_Joy did you write coq or something?
puffnfresh: I have never seen someone write Coq without something like Proof General
jax05_: we got a coq expert in here fortunately
Joy_void_Joy: I did not, I just played with it a lot :D
Joy_void_Joy: I am trying to make a very intuitive version of Coq
IEEKl: @Justanotherantiantiplayer yeah i have coded for 5 years, but i have always coded in windows, and i have never felt the need of running another os
Bagofpotatoes: what's proof general?
johnnyhotlava: Joy's ever expanding cerebrum
Joy_void_Joy: But it's way in the early stage right now
okkessh: just dont say 'I played with coq' outloud
puffnfresh: it's like an IDE for Coq
xEHLE_: well, gl with that
benchai18: @johnnyhotlava accept my friend request. I’ve been seeking you out for 30 years I don’t wanna lose u now
Joy_void_Joy: @okkessh Just realised after typing it, oops
jax05_: tehe
Justanotherantiantiplayer: @IEEKl then just keep doing what you like. if you want to learn about another os i would go for linux just because its free :P
johnnyhotlava: @benchai18 we are united
Initial18: @puffnfresh Is it a big Coq IDE?
Justanotherantiantiplayer: and personally i like it the most :D
okkessh: @Joy_void_Joy no worries we are all clean minded people here
johnnyhotlava: Joy is pure
jax05_: linux mint is a good flavor for those switching from windows imo
johnnyhotlava: as the driven snow
IEEKl: @Justanotherantiantiplayer haha yeah i guess
Midooriya10: can we use kali as daily driverm
Midooriya10: ?
benchai18: @joy_void_joy was in Nickleback at some point
jax05_: you could lol
Lambda_86: i also tried to make a coq clone but it didn't end well lol
chocolatechp: geoooorge
Joy_void_Joy: (If you want to make it easier, you can just change the inductive to specific case. But if you want the general version with x, I don't see how to do it without equalities)
johnnyhotlava: @benchai18 confirmed
imcraxo: !faq
johnnyhotlava: Bassist
benchai18: @johnnyhotlava knew it
puffnfresh: is Prop is a Set? I can't remember
johnnyhotlava: coq don't know shit
Joy_void_Joy: Nope, Prop is different from Set.
Lambda_86: Prop is the type of propositions and Set is the type of values
Lambda_86: so yeah different
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz why sticking so much to the boolean arithmetic? :) just use the one where true == false
Joy_void_Joy: Basically, the difference between the two is that you can "see the value"
myaocat: true == !false
puffnfresh: thanks @joy_void_joy @lambda_86
puffnfresh: ah interesting!
myaocat: you are doing it wrong! true == !false
imcraxo: where is he programming
johnnyhotlava: He's rock hard for boolean arithmetic cause he wants to make AI look at itself
Nnotm: https://github.com/coq/coq/wiki/Prop_or_Set gives some reasoning on which you should choose, though doesn't explain that well what they actually are
Joy_void_Joy: If I give you 1, or 2, you can see how I constructed them. If I give you a proof that 1 < 2, you are not allowed to "read how I made it"
Joy_void_Joy: You just know it is true
puffnfresh: "true == false -> Void"
jagger_rsw: I wonder if what he's doing right now is related to quantum, AI and blockchain
puffnfresh: good explanation, thanks @joy_void_joy
Joy_void_Joy: most welcome :3
luuwa_: Hi guysss
jax05_: joy is actually helping me understand wtf is happening lol
johnnyhotlava: Joy is a godsend
jagger_rsw: @jax05_ geohot is creating a new cryptocurrency
myaocat: 1 1 = 2
puffnfresh: I can do that proof in Coq @myaocat
luuwa_: 1 1 = 1
jax05_: The internet has ruined my trust in ppl @jagger_rsw
puffnfresh: that's about the limit of my Coq skill
myaocat: @puffnfresh can you do a research why 1 1 == 2?
okkessh: I mean I think false is both a prop and a set
okkessh: it is both a value and a prop
Joy_void_Joy: So you want a property that takes two parameters, a bool, and a proof that this bool "eqb'" true
Joy_void_Joy: proposition*
Joy_void_Joy: I'm not saying you want to use induction
Joy_void_Joy: But they are easier to read
luuwa_: Category: Basic Programming ..ss.s.s.s
Joy_void_Joy: In the case of bool, it is equivalent to a case
myaocat: Pog
Nnotm: luuwa_: true not equalling false does seem fairly basic to me
luuwa_: idea is basic bro
Nnotm: do you have to intro it?
johnnyhotlava: Flowers for johnny
puffnfresh: I've done "true = false -> Void" in Agda and Idris, it is pretty easy once you figure out to express it that way
puffnfresh: is that what we're doing in Coq?
johnnyhotlava: IF THEN
Joy_void_Joy: Well, it'd be waaaaaay easier if we were doing true = false @puffnfresh
okkessh: @Joy_void_Joy how is the the keyword false is a prop I am having a hard time
Joy_void_Joy: Or using a specific instance of eqb'
puffnfresh: what are we doing instead @joy_void_joy ?
johnnyhotlava: If it's true well coq guess the fuck what IT AINT in this one case where we're talking in snake language.
Nnotm: it seems like that's basically what we're doing though? eqb' is basically a non-polymorphic version of =, and "not" seems like it should be defined in terms of "-> False" but I'm not sure
Joy_void_Joy: @puffnfresh We are proving ~(eqb' true false) with a self made inductive definition
Joy_void_Joy: But the problem is that this definition tacitally use equality
indigolord: what syntax are we writing here?
Joy_void_Joy: And we don't want to use anything about equality
Joy_void_Joy: So I don't know if we can do this
johnnyhotlava: He's trying to get coq to work in parseltongue
indigolord: Wtf is this lang
Joy_void_Joy: @okkessh I did not get the question
Joy_void_Joy: Basically :d
Nnotm: puffnfresh if you didn't see it, the type of the actual theorem is "not (eqb' true false)"
firstavegner: What’s that language?
okkessh: @Joy_void_Joy george said fasle is a of sort prop
Nnotm: firstavegner Coq
Joy_void_Joy: False is "of type" Prop
puffnfresh: which is simplified to eqb' true false -> False right?
Nnotm: puffnfresh I believe so, but I'm not sure
Joy_void_Joy: It's important to make a difference between "instance of" and "of type"
okkessh: @Joy_void_Joy I see but isn't the meaning of props is that you prove them with other props
puffnfresh: eqb' looks like what?
Joy_void_Joy: Prop just mean the type
Nnotm: puffnfresh IIRC it's a non-polymorphic copy of the definition of =, but there may be a few minor changes
Joy_void_Joy: It just mean that it's a term you can construct?
Joy_void_Joy: So False is "of type" Prop
Joy_void_Joy: Even though you can't construct it
Joy_void_Joy: Does that make sense?
johnnyhotlava: Is that how they want you to construct terms?
okkessh: @Joy_void_Joy I get it but it doesnt make that much sense
puffnfresh: seems like this should be easy then...
Joy_void_Joy: @Nnotm That is exactly right
okkessh: like you prove something with a theorem that is of type prop and thats cool
Joy_void_Joy: @puffnfresh It would, if we were allowed to use anything about equality
puffnfresh: @joy_void_joy why can't we discriminate, each case seems trivial?
johnnyhotlava: So you sayin dis parseltongue is elitist
firstavegner: Seems like logic set and theory stuff
Joy_void_Joy: @puffnfresh The problem is that the definition use binding
benchai18: Try a coq block of code
johnnyhotlava: lol
Joy_void_Joy: eqb'_refl x: eqb' x x
Joy_void_Joy: So we're using the fact that it's the same x
Joy_void_Joy: But George doesn't want to use anything about equality
puffnfresh: @joy_void_joy can't we case on the x?
johnnyhotlava: you want your coq to have a non linear plot up the x axis so that it can reach the post labeled spot "G"
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz what were you watching recently on netflix?
Joy_void_Joy: Well, that's kind of what inversion is doing
puffnfresh: alright cool, I'm catching up
firstavegner: Can you define a “==“ in qoc ?
Joy_void_Joy: But you can't case directly on it, because it's a Prop
Nnotm: firstavegner yes
Joy_void_Joy: If we were using Set, I think it would be way easier
johnnyhotlava: Banned
puffnfresh: let's use a Set
Joy_void_Joy: (Don't take my word on it, checking that)
johnnyhotlava: lol
benchai18: Where is Santiago?
joker2k999: LUL.
mkdrmnd: !uptime
johnnyhotlava: @joker2k999 Glorious
okkessh: the data type boolean is of type set
joker2k999: he's a sub dorkmo
Joy_void_Joy: I meant eqb
Sarkin_dota: What did he say
joker2k999: scratch that.
okkessh: are you sure false is a prop when the data type boolean is of type set
Joy_void_Joy: But I was mistaken, forget the part about it being easier
okkessh: I am confused
puffnfresh: eqb is a Type right @joy_void_joy ?
Joy_void_Joy: Yes
puffnfresh: not a Prop
Joy_void_Joy: @okkessh Yes, false is a bool, but False is a Prop
Santiago_LHC: @benchai18 what happened
Joy_void_Joy: You cannot
johnnyhotlava: redefine it
okkessh: but bool datatype is of type set
benchai18: @santiago_lhc someone asked about keyboard. We needed u
Santiago_LHC: I should be a mod.
Joy_void_Joy: You are saying "all booleans are true"
puffnfresh: trivial.
Nnotm: okkessh there's a difference between false and False
Joy_void_Joy: Which is not true
johnnyhotlava: chanj da rools
Lambda_86: how about just using discriminate on a version of the proof that has the standard library's =, then copy-paste the lambda expression from printing it and modify eq to eqb'
3FXX: @georgehotz How do you maintain your cognitive skills like non-stop 6-7 hours?
benchai18: Meth
johnnyhotlava: ICE
fafws321: Cocain
benchai18: Glass boiii
Lambda_86: use Print
johnnyhotlava: High speed chicken feed
okkessh: @Nnotm what is the difference between to falses
johnnyhotlava: that plexi
benchai18: IV Bath salts
johnnyhotlava: from the nexty
HS_SemenThrower: @3FXX drink iced tea then chew on the ice
Joy_void_Joy: @okkessh false is a Bool, and Bool is a Set. Set is the set of all constructible terms. Prop is the set of all terms that exists
benchai18: Glass in a pookie son
Joy_void_Joy: And Type is the type of all of this
3FXX: @HS_SemenThrower what :D
johnnyhotlava: lololol
Nnotm: okkessh I'm not too familiar with Coq terminology, but more or less this: bool is a Set that has two elements, true and false, whereas False is a Set that has 0 elements
puffnfresh: destr??
Lambda_86: Print true_is_not_false.
puffnfresh: destruct?
ボズシフティー: tyvm for the ps3 jb back in the days !
Nnotm: okkessh false is the boolean value you'd find in many other programming languages whereas False is a logical proposition
puffnfresh: puffnfHS
okkessh: @Nnotm oh I see now
okkessh: so False is the already proven prop that is already there
puffnfresh: NICE
johnnyhotlava: That level
Joy_void_Joy: False_ind is just contradiction
puffnfresh: FALSE INDUCTION
Nnotm: okkessh well - the point behind False is that you *cannot* prove it, and the reason is that the elements of a proposition are no proves
HS_SemenThrower: bet he not gonna wash his hands now look
Joy_void_Joy: It allows you to say "if I have False in my hypotheses, I'm done"
zoki_macola: poor neighbors
Nnotm: okkessh I meant "are the proofs", pressed enter too early
johnnyhotlava: He has cellophane over his board of keys
HS_SemenThrower: NotLikeThis
chocolatechp: did u just go inject cocaine
benchai18: Lol nice terminology. You almost got banned
Nnotm: okkessh and False has no elements, i.e. has no proofs
johnnyhotlava: Plugged a lump of that firey ice
puffnfresh: Coq the code generator
benchai18: @johnnyhotlava is a true wordsmith
Sznurek066: LUL
3FXX: thats how he maintains, i get it now
oyAli: you back on macOS?
fafws321: Ökkeş çok zorlama be
benchai18: Mix it with that tar. Next level bruh
Santiago_LHC: coqaine
johnnyhotlava: @benchai18 only you my friend lololol
johnnyhotlava: that midwest rollercoaster
johnnyhotlava: lololol
benchai18: 😁
johnnyhotlava: that arkansas up down
benchai18: Went from speedballs to goofballs
johnnyhotlava: or any other bad places I could think of
benchai18: Lmao
johnnyhotlava: lololol
puffnfresh: refl is a=a
benchai18: That ozark cocktail
johnnyhotlava: lolololol
Joy_void_Joy: You defined it
johnnyhotlava: That louisiana lump
oyAli: cmon georgie
benchai18: Lmao
ferrahs: True === false
puffnfresh: ship it @ferrahs
benchai18: I wish Theo Von was in this chat
ferrahs: @puffnfresh to the mooooon
johnnyhotlava: True = False but only when we boolin
johnnyhotlava: in only he were
dorkmo: dorkmo gifted a Tier 1 sub to Lambda_86! They have given 4 Gift Subs in the channel!
Joy_void_Joy: They are using eq_ind to do the binding, that's clever
Sznurek066: Pog
ferrahs: !uptime
kroanke: @ferrahs
kroanke: 4.38
ferrahs: if (userInput = “!uptime”)
benchai18: HAHAHAHHAA
Sarkin_dota: lol
benchai18: @santiago_lhc
ferrahs: @muhhn OMEGALUL
faulpelzz: lol
moonify: How long have been he streaming?
yaus_baus: since like 10am western
kroanke: i was laughing so hard when you got timed out @muhhn
yaus_baus: big boy stream
Santiago_LHC: @muhhn because keyboards don't matter
ferrahs: @muhhn monkaS
benchai18: God damn I’m crying lAughing
ferrahs: @muhhn it’s a MacBook Pro keyboard
chocolatechp: its the logitech 10 dollar keyboard
benchai18: Dvorak
benchai18: I am dvorak
ferrahs: What is he actually programming? Someone fill me in
mexeroserisback: D: no its not
yaus_baus: go to dvorak and lose all vim mappings
yaus_baus: no thanks
benchai18: @muhhn jk. I don’t use Dvorak nor do I have aids yet
mexeroserisback: Dvorak was an ingenious composer wtf
puffnfresh: needs to take a second parameter?
puffnfresh: your fun?
UMPS: @benchai18 (yet)
Joy_void_Joy: @ferrahs He is trying to understand a language named Coq by being the most minimalistic possible
benchai18: I’m very careful with my words
Santiago_LHC: it's apple
benchai18: Guys I dno how emotes work. I can’t make my own unless I’m a streamer, correct?
ferrahs: @joy_void_joy what is Coq? Is it based on another lang? What lang is it similar to?
ferrahs: @muhhn rip
Nnotm: its syntax is based on ML
ferrahs: @benchai18 yeah
benchai18: @muhhn 10 min starting now
faulpelzz: bwahahaha
Joy_void_Joy: eq_ind allows you to switch a term. So if you want to prove P x, and you know that x = y, you can use it to change the goal to P y
ferrahs: @muhhn just whispered me saying he’s crying :( rip
Santiago_LHC: F
benchai18: Poor @muhhn
puffnfresh: it's a formal verification tool
drivewaycam: !uptime
puffnfresh: proof assistant
Joy_void_Joy: @ferrahs It's a proving language. It is not really a programming language, because you never run it
Joy_void_Joy: You just compile it
Santiago_LHC: @driveawaycam 4 hours 43 min
ferrahs: @joy_void_joy oh, so what’s it’s application?
benchai18: @joy_void_joy so what’s the point? Is this like an existential thing
drivewaycam: @Santiago_LHC ty
puffnfresh: there's proof extraction so you CAN run it but almost nobody in the world does
johnnyhotlava: He gonna make python do the work
drivewaycam: i love python
Palohdire: Palohdire subscribed with Twitch Prime.
Joy_void_Joy: Because it allows you to prove things
benchai18: @georgehotz is the Robert Frost of coding
puffnfresh: @benchai18 for proving things
johnnyhotlava: @drivewaycam No you don't
Joy_void_Joy: Like 1 1 = 2, and you'll be sure of it
johnnyhotlava: lol
drivewaycam: trust me man, i love it @johnnyhotlava
johnnyhotlava: Parseltongue
benchai18: @johnnyhotlava hai ahasee yeth?
johnnyhotlava: lolol
dyslexicat: true = false
Santiago_LHC: True is just a word
puffnfresh: true = false
thuganalyst: true == false
okkessh: maybe everything is true
Nnotm: (False -> True) -> False sounds like it should be provable, in principle
ferrahs: true === false ;)
Joy_void_Joy: You can extract it to a function that runs, but
johnnyhotlava: you have to say "it wont work"
puffnfresh: I don't think so @nnotm
Joy_void_Joy: @Nnotm Nope, False -> True
Nnotm: oh, oops
funwayz: false is true in some perspective
benchai18: @joy_void_joy I’m too stupid for this. What’s the point of proving philosophical things? Is this just like for fun
Joy_void_Joy: If you have false, you have everything
yaus_baus: true && false
MajesticMack: false is just less true in life
ferrahs: @benchai18 yes it’s fun for him
johnnyhotlava: False encapsulates too much brain
Joy_void_Joy: @benchai18 The typical exemple is in planes
Joy_void_Joy: You want to prove that your algorithms won't lead to a crash
puffnfresh: @benchai18 prove that there are infinite prime numbers, this is useful
benchai18: I feel like I’m swinging further into the spectrum every moment
Joy_void_Joy: And it can be used in mathematics
Joy_void_Joy: To be sure about a proof
ferrahs: Yeah, this is basically mathematical proofs in code
benchai18: Fuck I’m dumb
puffnfresh: push your code somewhere @georgehotz I'll have a go
Joy_void_Joy: Well, you can also extract the algorithm you've implemented to a real language
Joy_void_Joy: And run them there
puffnfresh: I've done that @joy_void_joy
benchai18: They don’t teach coq on codeacademy
Joy_void_Joy: You mean in Coq @puffnfresh ?
puffnfresh: written proofs about Haskell code in Idris, ported it back
johnnyhotlava: lolololol
Joy_void_Joy: Oh
Cal3b123: Are we going to do any modal logic, with first order logic it gets preety crazy
Joy_void_Joy: Yeah, it's the same idea
puffnfresh: did that for product code in fact
puffnfresh: at a start-up
c9bd: why is this guy proving true != false lol
benchai18: I feel like I’m gaining IQ points just being here
johnnyhotlava: Alright I'm good on this My cerebrum is shrinking
johnnyhotlava: @benchai18 opposite I am getting dommed by the relativity
benchai18: Guys if I learn HTML can I basically use coq?
johnnyhotlava: lolool
Cal3b123: Has George said what hes using zotero for :thinking:
Nnotm: puffnfresh just tried to write this proof in haskell by the way, if I didn't mess anything up the proof is just "case" (I didn't even know you could use empty case without {})
johnnyhotlava: I need help extracting my coq proofs into brazzers
okkessh: what is on VS code
johnnyhotlava: then onto vhs
yBw1: what are we doing
puffnfresh: @nnotm yeah looks good
puffnfresh: that's what it would be in Coq if we used the propositional equality
Backrub: is school lame @georgehotz
Mariosavitch: NotLikeThis
benchai18: @johnnyhotlava xvideos or pHub?
yBw1: this lang looks so much fun
M03x: !uptime
Cal3b123: Do you have to do implication introduction first?
inciMage: any explanation why he uses windows sometimes
puffnfresh: push this code @georgehotz I want to have a go
puffnfresh: sweet I'll have a go <3
muhhn: back bitches
sudqijawabreh: proposition maybe >
okkessh: prop is 4=5
puffnfresh: Prop is proposition which is like a type
muhhn: which mod keeps timing me out :thinking:
okkessh: prop itself is a type
okkessh: prop is like a claim
Joy_void_Joy: Prop is of type Type
Joy_void_Joy: And Prop is the type of all propositions, yes
puffnfresh: Kappa
lemonboxed: i think for each set of props they have to follow the same type of set rules to be true
Joy_void_Joy: Yes nat <- Set <- Type
Joy_void_Joy: 1 = 2 <- Prop <- Type
Joy_void_Joy: Type <- Type <- Type
djuckfomla93: @georgehotz Which colorscheme are you using for vim ?
benchai18: @muhhn Whassup big daddy
okkessh: okay here it is : the basic stuff that exists is separated into 2 in coq some are set which are like datatypes and smaller sets and props are saying this is equal or not equal to this and props are not sets
Joy_void_Joy: In eq_ind (I'm trying to rewrite it right now, so it will be easier to read)
PotatoesAreTheKings: okay so maybe i should have watched from the beginning
nanodanger7: @djuckfomla93 the default
Joy_void_Joy: Well @okkessh kinda?
Joy_void_Joy: Because all set can be a prop
johnnyhotlava: can be...
djuckfomla93: @nanodanger7 how come that i dont have same colorscheme then, is it because of xterm ?
Mariosavitch: making a program reason is difficult. glad you are onto the task mr. hotz
inciMage: imma sleep bye guys
johnnyhotlava: He needs two fingers to access the knowledge
nanodanger7: if you have a mac and change the text to white and the bg to black it should be the same
djuckfomla93: @nanodanger7 Nah, i have arch.
okkessh: the false which is a bool is a set and the false which is a prop is a prop
nanodanger7: well then that's why it's different
yaus_baus: @djuckfomla93 just use ST if youre on arch
okkessh: @Joy_void_Joy am I doing good ?
yaus_baus: best teriminal
lemonboxed: to access knowledge you have to call metaphysical glasses that you can push on
puffnfresh: something like that @okkessh
johnnyhotlava: @lemonboxed Ahhh advanced insight
benchai18: @djuckfomla93 Arch? Great. Another nerd that’s smarter than me
Joy_void_Joy: @okkessh I'm not sure I follow. What is the type of false, and what is the type of False?
Klingenwetzer: hey dad FeelsGoodMan
okkessh: type of false is set and type of False is prop ?
B0tch: What are you doing?
Klingenwetzer: true != false forsenThink
okkessh: but type of false is first boolean and then set ?
djuckfomla93: @benchai18 Arch does not make anyone smarter lul :) @yaus_baus i'll try that terminal, thanks for advice
johnnyhotlava: False is a type of true
Joy_void_Joy: Well, false is a bool
annasgrasshopper: Arch linux is quite a cool OS, I really like to use it with i3
Joy_void_Joy: Bool is a set
johnnyhotlava: or that's what I tell my girl when I'm on snap
Klingenwetzer: this is messing with my head LUL
Joy_void_Joy: False is a Prop, yes
okkessh: is it a coincidence that the name is coq and there is := in syntax
Klingenwetzer: LUL
benchai18: @johnnyhotlava Legend
Sznurek066: P != NP forsenThink
lemonboxed: is it bc its statically typed so you have to emualate dynamic types
johnnyhotlava: @benchai18 you're gods son
Klingenwetzer: thats so stupid LUL
djuckfomla93: @annasgrasshopper i3 is nutz...next lvl
yaus_baus: @djuckfomla93 I personally use Luke Smith's build of st, looks nice with i3 gaps
benchai18: All in favor of transferring ownership of the Federal Reserve to @johnnyhotlava ?
benchai18: I
johnnyhotlava: I
johnnyhotlava: Court is adjourned
jax05_: lol
benchai18: Unanimous decision. Democracy at its finest
djuckfomla93: @yaus_baus why not the default one ? which benefits do i get from his build ?
jax05_: you two should get married
johnnyhotlava: @jax05_ you missed it?
benchai18: He gives me a broner
jax05_: @johnnyhotlava yes FeelsBadMan
yaus_baus: @djuckfomla93 just saves you time configuring it, he has some good keybinds defined too
johnnyhotlava: Helmet engorged full mushroom
yaus_baus: as well as aesthetics
benchai18: Hahahahahahaha
djuckfomla93: @yaus_baus Thanks buddy, will definitely give it a try
benchai18: The smart people are just ignoring us completely
johnnyhotlava: Such is life.
jax05_: are you calling me dumb?? @benchai18
benchai18: You’re the exception
djuckfomla93: lul
jax05_: FeelsGoodMan
johnnyhotlava: I have the iq but the technical knowledge is uhhhhhhh not there
Klingenwetzer: has george mentioned his opinion regarding the bootrom exploit?
benchai18: I used Coq to determine that @jax05_ != dumb despite paying attention to us
johnnyhotlava: lol
jax05_: @Klingenwetzer he did a stream about it recently
puffnfresh: OH MAN
Klingenwetzer: damn I missed it
jax05_: @benchai18 I'm sorry for indulging you D:
benchai18: @klingenwetzer I think it’s on youtub son
cozinn: !uptime
jax05_: oh wait I am dumb
RomanNYC: clear H1 I think
puffnfresh: Coq is so much more fun than any video game
yaus_baus: coq club lmao
johnnyhotlava: I eat crayons without the wrapper
benchai18: @jax05_ I think @johnnyhotlava and I are gonna adopt u
Klingenwetzer: I saw the original tweet 4h after it was posted, but I didn't check on what george was doing NotLikeThis
puffnfresh: QED
johnnyhotlava: Welcome home
johnnyhotlava: Proved IT
jax05_: woooooot
yaus_baus: good job george
knilecrack: GG
puffnfresh: QED <3 <3 <3 <3
Klingenwetzer: BIG 🧠
HS_SemenThrower: ggwp
extremelywide: LOL
dorkmo: boiiiiii
puffnfresh: get that W
dorkmo: Pride100
puffnfresh: Pride10
prakyath_kantharaju: I just realized that true is not equal to false
benchai18: SO CLOSE. KEEP PULLING THE COQ. IM SO CLOSE
johnnyhotlava: Super unfair considering I use piano keys and didn't know the type
Joy_void_Joy: I think I've found a way to do it very simply
johnnyhotlava: Lets start over
Joy_void_Joy: You start with Lemma true_eq_false: ~(true = false).
Joy_void_Joy: Then you apply it to your goal
Joy_void_Joy: And then you destruct eqb' true false
Joy_void_Joy: It works in my computer
benchai18: @joy_void_joy lemme know if ur looking for a job
rkxbz: omg, you are still sitting?
Klingenwetzer: LUL
Joy_void_Joy: But with ssreflect syntax
Johnvade: you know what, this stream was actually helpful
Klingenwetzer: Math WutFace
Johnvade: i might do something similar in plan9 c
benchai18: @joy_void_joy I agree. Ssreflect for sure
Joy_void_Joy: Not with the library, just the syntax
johnnyhotlava: NO EQUALITY
puffnfresh: equals and ssreflect??
puffnfresh: ah I see
Johnvade: ty ty ty
djuckfomla93: @georgehotz are u coming to Europe soon?
johnnyhotlava: ALRIGHT
Klingenwetzer: Proofs forsenX WutFace
Joy_void_Joy: But it's what it's doing with eq_ind?
extremelywide: this is NOT an equality friendly stream >:-(
Joy_void_Joy: Or I'm confused?
Klingenwetzer: LUL
puffnfresh: I had some doubts
puffnfresh: for a while
abk467: i was iffy about it but this clarifies it
K0enich: awesome
benchai18: @joy_void_joy I think he’s re-routing the encryption to the mainframe
johnnyhotlava: @benchai18 lololololololololol
okkessh: is proving a tautology really and accomplishment?
Mariosavitch: true != false? What world is this
johnnyhotlava: STOOOOOPID
jax05_: it's a proofs world
HS_SemenThrower: @benchai18 lmfao
johnnyhotlava: man that's killing me
benchai18: 🧢 das my ass hat
Joy_void_Joy: I'll have to take a look at that then, sorry
Joy_void_Joy: @benchai18 I'm listening :P
puffnfresh: it's not a tautology
Klingenwetzer: forsenKek
tfue_is_dog_shit: true == true is false in js
Mariosavitch: ask siri
puffnfresh: LUL
frankytex: the true loser is that keyboard getting soar from being diddled so hard
crowsssssssss: crowsssssssss subscribed with Twitch Prime.
Klingenwetzer: ANY TRUERS? forsenHead
picklesareok: Am I stupid or is it contrapostive
yaus_baus: uber eats chicken geroge
Mariosavitch: im a flat earther
okkessh: it is a tautology, you solve an equation and you end up with 3!=5 what do you call it
shissle: You mean a Model
benchai18: @joy_void_joy How do you feel about marketing? Id hire u for sure
Nnotm: ~(true = false) isn't a tautology? Isn't it true for all possible interpretations of the (0) free variables?
prakyath_kantharaju: amazon prime it bro
johnnyhotlava: Fridge = Stocked with coq chicken
puffnfresh: @okkessh simple?
johnnyhotlava: Forage
Roundlay: <3
puffnfresh: thanks @georgehotz
dotmops: any oil princes? squadW
K0enich: <3
Klingenwetzer: <3 dad
jax05_: byeee
3FXX: !uptime
joker2k999: peace bois.
knilecrack: gg
annasgrasshopper: bye bye Hotzzzzz
okkessh: and me
annasgrasshopper: :)
rkxbz: what is your favourite book??
Klingenwetzer: lowHi enjoy your meal my dude :D
puffnfresh: stream more Coq
prakyath_kantharaju: MVP joy_void_joy
johnnyhotlava: the coq crew
Joy_void_Joy: Most welcome :3
tfue_is_dog_shit: <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 BibleThump BibleThump
puffnfresh: it's lots of fun
johnnyhotlava: Yeah I basically had to carry the whole coq team
Klingenwetzer: in python LUL
Nnotm: have you thought about implementing agda instead?
johnnyhotlava: Held the coq together
puffnfresh: I <3 Agda @Nnotm
shieeeeeeeeet: he's answering "why?" Pog
Klingenwetzer: I took compiler building (:
benchai18: Why did he freeze? Did he dip?
Joy_void_Joy: Its core is very minimalistic, yes
okkessh: will you check the gmail dor the backspace ai
Joy_void_Joy: That's what I love about it
okkessh: for the backspace ai
jax05_: @benchai18 he's still talking
Klingenwetzer: LUL
johnnyhotlava: George is going to break out of the matrix
johnnyhotlava: He wants AI to learn about itself so he can learn aobut himself
puffnfresh: <3 learning
Roundlay: But Lambos help me get a girlfriend
puffnfresh: keep it coming @georgehotz
Klingenwetzer: you wanna proof a concept :) for your own sanity
johnnyhotlava: I missed a talk
johnnyhotlava: oh ok
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz but you're writing language to prevent breaking out of simulation, b/c it's provable ;)
okkessh: you are creating the last invention of mankind with backspace telling you
Klingenwetzer: TRUE PogChamp
jax05_: I think he's referring to his techcrunch talk
shieeeeeeeeet: do you have a primary optimization objective that guides most of your actions?
Klingenwetzer: yes you want :)
yaus_baus: making ig users think lol
Klingenwetzer: you make me think about making someone to think forsenThink
yaus_baus: ur comments lul
ZeeZaxean: youtube does that having 3 ads before a 10sec video, idk whats real anymore
knilecrack: what did you think?
Kriminell00: D: no way
lemonboxed: ig is just bots
knilecrack: IG is for retards
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz seeing you at joe rogan's would be interesting, given that joe is easily captivated by ideas like world simiulations and AI gods
johnnyhotlava: YEAH
knilecrack: you are just saying that case you didn't get verified
Klingenwetzer: LUL
risky_banana: bubbaCREEP
okkessh: yeah joe rogan is the way to many followers
knilecrack: cause*
SKPTCL: george took dmt? really?
johnnyhotlava: You portal travler
joker2k999: oh shit. talk about it.
johnnyhotlava: traveler
Klingenwetzer: joe rogan forsenHead
grizvok: dmt is crazyyyyy
yaus_baus: have joe rogan on geohot stream
johnnyhotlava: Just go on and dominate the convo
okkessh: do you use adderal
grizvok: i did an extraction myself
knilecrack: Did you smoke it?
benchai18: @jagger_rsw I’d try getting him on jre if he wanted but someone said he already said he’s not interested
kingkong3211: well joe got some weed for you lol
Klingenwetzer: george > elon
thuganalyst: Tell us bout da DMT
SKPTCL: is it as huge of a meme as everyone makes it out to be?
Roundlay: Do you use Modafinil?
shieeeeeeeeet: do you plan on cryogenically freezing your brain if you encounter an earlier-than-expected death?
joker2k999: LUL
okkessh: you have more dopamine with Adderall
Klingenwetzer: retalin OpieOP
Roundlay: How do you measure productivity?
okkessh: you should try concerta
johnnyhotlava: Well creating the delusion does remove some pressure
knilecrack: you should mark your stream 18
jax05_: lol
CondomsWontFit: have you finished reading GEB?
shieeeeeeeeet: how is cryo equivalent to effective altruism?
Klingenwetzer: this is 18 programming forsenS
puffnfresh: don't get the kids into Coq
Klingenwetzer: true != false is dangerous
knilecrack: not if you ask me but twitch :)
yaus_baus: 18 for streams with coq content
johnnyhotlava: Deceit is the key
knilecrack: @Klingenwetzer he will fuck up stupid kids
Joy_void_Joy: Ooh, talking rationality and effective altruism :D
benchai18: Love coq
johnnyhotlava: "altrusim" namsayin
Joy_void_Joy: Great!
kingkong3211: how long do you think it will take till we get basic VR.
johnnyhotlava: Machiavellian self corruption will lead you to the light
rkxbz: what is your favourite book?
Klingenwetzer: rationality is like only the half of the story
joker2k999: can we get a rant or what? LUL
benchai18: Last time I’m gonna ask... George u wanna be on Rogan or nah?
puffnfresh: I agree @georgehotz
picklesareok: Any rationalist essays worth reading?
shieeeeeeeeet: so you'd rather just stop existing than possibly be resurrected?
johnnyhotlava: You want this very thing
rkxbz: what is your favourite book?
kingkong3211: how long do you think it will take till we get basic VR
johnnyhotlava: right now
knilecrack: when r you gonna stream again?
jagger_rsw: go joe rogan :)
Klingenwetzer: wanna be on INFO WARS?
dotmops: go on thisweekinstartups again that was a fun convo with jason
metasudo: ill have you on my podcast, we can smoke weed and color in coloring book
Roundlay: Wouldn't you tend to live a better life/achieve your goals more often if you can more easily overcome cognitive biases, etc.?
metasudo: s
djuckfomla93: Do you plan on coming to Europe soon ?
Klingenwetzer: forsenS
searchingforlife: @georgehotz why are you shilling for soylent and mealsquares?
rkxbz: what is your favourite book?
CondomsWontFit: have you finished reading GEB?
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz but yudkovsky is crio-lover
kingkong3211: how long do you think it will take till we get basic VR.
okkessh: what kind of tea do you drink
benchai18: I love jre, but I’d rather see him on TPW w/ Theo Von
zoki_macola: what do you think about WeWork?
picklesareok: Thank you!
elonsmuskygooch: When are you going on Logan Pauls Podcast?, he said he wants you on. @georgehotz
johnnyhotlava: LOLOLOL
metasudo: bad blood is fucking awesommmmme
Couchmann941: how did the iphone jailbraking go? @georgehotz
jax05_: lmao
johnnyhotlava: It's genius in a different sense
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz what are you watching on tv, some cool movies/series out there?
johnnyhotlava: billions
johnnyhotlava: for that shit
rkxbz: what is your favourite book?
johnnyhotlava: God bless them
Nnotm: https://slatestarcodex.com/2015/08/17/the-goddess-of-everything-else-2/
jax05_: thx
laz4rz: @georgehotz billions is great
benchai18: You sound like Kermit a little
Klingenwetzer: do you guys know "The Physicists"?
shieeeeeeeeet: @georgehotz are you saying you wouldn't pursue cryo because you're not a rationalist?
johnnyhotlava: Woah
johnnyhotlava: jorge
Bra_te: what is inch?
joker2k999: i think looking at binaries on windows made him switch back to the mac...
dotmops: another ThisWeekInStartups podcast with Jason would be fun :D
yaus_baus: why use dating apps george
okkessh: what is the tea you keep drinking
tris790: cringe ?
benchai18: @georgehotz == KermitTheFrog Look into it
johnnyhotlava: Oh i cant date on apps
metasudo: bro ill date you
mlacix: @georgehotz are you exited about the new season of Mr. Robot?
johnnyhotlava: I like to harass in person
peter35_: how much coffee do you drink?
knilecrack: ohh you should
benchai18: I love Hinge. Met my girl on hinge
johnnyhotlava: Aggression is a serious advantage
kingkong3211: how long do you think it will take till we get basic VR.
Roundlay: When's your next date
Bra_te: mr robot wasn't that good :/
catacata92: Do you like anime ?
jax05_: dating apps feel really uncomfortable to me
djuckfomla93: @georgehotz Alright, i guess im a spammer. Are u coming to Europe soon ?
johnnyhotlava: Aggression ups your iq by 20 pts
benchai18: Is Coq >= 9?
thuganalyst: Did you see that video of Shkreli roasting Jason Calacanis? LOL
elonsmuskygooch: Can I buy your merch? @georgehotz
lemonboxed: when will vr not fry my eyeballs
Roundlay: TPFufun
Klingenwetzer: forsenThink girls
knilecrack: ahaha
johnnyhotlava: lol
Klingenwetzer: N O LUL
knilecrack: Yeah
gunnaren: Norway right here
Klingenwetzer: Me @georgehotz
Klingenwetzer: :)
exonex_osu: germany
jagger_rsw: si, switzerland
annasgrasshopper: I'm from europe
speeddrawing101: uk
kingkong3211: uk here
annasgrasshopper: Portugal here
Sznurek066: EU Pog Poland here
Roundlay: Tokyo
mlacix: Iam from Europe as well
faulpelzz: can u hack brainz?
metasudo: GeoHotz cock socks
shissle: Yes
lasercatboss: germany whaddup everbody
Bra_te: on what are you working right now?
zoki_macola: Serbia
Klingenwetzer: Germany DatSheffy
fear_ep: Italy
Hueston94: Watching from Northern Ireland
Threated1: yea
knilecrack: Zoki madafaka
ferrahs: Toronto
Roundlay: Still got that PASMO money?
Bra_te: Germany <3
catacata92: Do you think emotions hinders real thinking ?
johnnyhotlava: George what do you want AI to do next
shissle: Come to Germany
LiamS212: Uk gang where u at
gunnaren: !uptime
benchai18: @georgehotz bleached ass or natural?
Klingenwetzer: hack my raspberry pi @georgehotz
joker2k999: minecraft stream bros.
fazel3ss: Let’s do some AI on audio
shieeeeeeeeet: do you think that quantum superposition is a memory-efficient representation for the simulation?
fazel3ss: Nobody does audio
Roundlay: https://www.twitch.tv/georgehotz/clip/TolerantFunAnteaterBrokeBack
ferrahs: Can you give tips on data structure and complex algorithms?
Klingenwetzer: 🧠
Bra_te: have you ever done drugs?
benchai18: Can you be my life coach
elonsmuskygooch: Can I pay you $100 bucks to write "#1 Twitchy" on a shit white shirt with a marker? @georgehotz
djuckfomla93: Goddamit, i just want a single conference with George Hotz....am i asking too much ?
Klingenwetzer: LUL
fazel3ss: Was it 20$?
johnnyhotlava: What level confrontation is appropriate for management. SHould I use a whip?
joker2k999: thought it was $100.
ferrahs: LOL not implementing, but to be able to do leetcode
metasudo: if you think about it, if you sit on the toilet, you're connecting your butthole to every other butthole in the area, its a butthole network
Roundlay: Sit down Tai Lopez
walktheabyss: Best piece of advice for getting better at programming?
lasercatboss: guys
ferrahs: @metasudo mesh topology?
lasercatboss: you saw his talks
lasercatboss: dont invite him
Klingenwetzer: he wants the premium stuff LUL
yaus_baus: cloud butthole
lasercatboss: link his last talk
puffnfresh: https://yowconference.com/lambdajam/
lasercatboss: its fine
benchai18: @johnnyhotlava Threaten their kids
johnnyhotlava: @benchai18 bless
elonsmuskygooch: Can I pay you $100 bucks to write "#1 Twitchy" on a shit white shirt with a marker? @georgehotz
puffnfresh: come to Sydney for the annual Coq fight
lemonboxed: unless your toilet is offgrid
lemonboxed: offgrid toilets 2020
puffnfresh: we have a Coq competition every year
Klingenwetzer: LUL paypal me
Sarkin_dota: Sounds like a scam
yaus_baus: scam
benchai18: Bro I’m loaded
benchai18: I’ll keep u on retainwr
catacata92: your talk was something
lasercatboss: do you say the 15 mins thing at you dates too? lmao
Klingenwetzer: forsenThink
jagger_rsw: what if you get lifecoached in the end :)
ferrahs: I’ll charge back Kappa
shinypickel: scam OMEGALUL
benchai18: Love u dude.
grizvok: LOL
shieeeeeeeeet: what's your ETA for AGI, whatever your definition of that is?
Kriminell00: inb4 joe rogan calls you on skype
johnnyhotlava: I want you to create an extortion tool for public officials
Klingenwetzer: what about a date with you? @georgehotz forsenThink
jagger_rsw: Star Trek or Star Wars?
johnnyhotlava: lolololol
rkxbz: how about joker movie?
johnnyhotlava: YES
benchai18: @johnnyhotlava let’s buy him a shard and fly him out
grizvok: LAAS
okkessh: you said, you would never get married in video why is that
krnflake1: ios or android?
elonsmuskygooch: Can I pay you $100 bucks to write "#1 Twitchy" on a crappy white shirt with a marker? georgehotz
johnnyhotlava: @benchai18 zoot that man up
Klingenwetzer: forsenThink linkedIn
Roundlay: LUL
Keyeh: KappaPride
Roundlay: Damn I'm out
buttez: LUL
jax05_: lul
Bra_te: who are you rooting for in 2020?
johnnyhotlava: what's the most obscure programming language I can use to keep from being copied?
catacata92: Would you let AI govern 'countries' ?
dorkmo: GayPride
Klingenwetzer: only for you KappaPride
ferrahs: KappaPride
grizvok: LOL
johnnyhotlava: sanskrit?
joker2k999: LUL
Klingenwetzer: DODGED LUL EZ
Roundlay: Are you in the yanggang
elonsmuskygooch: Can I pay you $100 bucks to write "#1 Twitchy" on a crappy white shirt with a marker? @georgehotz
shieeeeeeeeet: @georgehotz what's your ETA for AGI, whatever your definition of that is?
twiggy_io: Okay be my life coach
johnnyhotlava: FItty dollas
krnflake1: ios or android?
lasercatboss: how you come back from a shitty week to prove your lifecoarch potential
picklesareok: why is it so hard to find an interesitng objective function
knilecrack: let's go 10 pushups for proving false != true
johnnyhotlava: I gochu
jagger_rsw: coaching is about listening, and you talk a lot )
Klingenwetzer: Big new iPhone PogChamp
knilecrack: ahahahahaha
eaoruhgadfhjglajsdlfgj: PogChamp
Keyeh: OMEGALUL
lasercatboss: Pog
Sznurek066: PogChamp
Jewishrambo: 7
searchingforlife: PogChamp
0xc0ffeee: ahahahah
Klingenwetzer: PogChamp
johnnyhotlava: look at the length of those arms
peter35_: horrible form NotLikeThis
jax05_: Pog
metasudo: he's got good form
Sarkin_dota: Would you agree to twitchstream the coaching session?
gunnaren: EASY clap
puffnfresh: wtf is going on
knilecrack: YEAH BOYYYYYYYYY
okkessh: you said you would never get married why is that
benchai18: What a tweaker. I love him
ferrahs: PogChamp
hardtarget4: weak
rkxbz: you almost died man
johnnyhotlava: man has got some reach
jax05_: I thought he was gonna fail
Klingenwetzer: buy a new one OpieOP
kayos_rl: kayos_rl subscribed with Twitch Prime.
UniversalGeneve: george.fit()
twiggy_io: Is this when you hire me?
yaus_baus: lmao
grizvok: ROFL
ferrahs: @benchai18 that’s what coke does to you
Jewishrambo: lets do it guys
CondomsWontFit: do it PogChamp
benchai18: @georgehotz u wanna be on Rogan? Lmk
grizvok: lollforfl
gunnaren: Someone please do this
Klingenwetzer: SKYPE OMEGALUL
ferrahs: Are you making an iOS 14 JB? Kappa
puffnfresh: who is game?
yaus_baus: live dr phil with geohot
0xc0ffeee: someone do this plz
Jewishrambo: viewer call ins
3FXX: how about $0 5min teaser for 270 people then we decide
Roundlay: Lifecoaching https://clips.twitch.tv/HappyAcceptableCheesecakeNotLikeThis
Keyeh: can you hire me?
ZootedNipples: why do you use mac os?
Jewishrambo: lol
Klingenwetzer: I can look pretty :)
twiggy_io: I can program kinda okay
johnnyhotlava: I am a pathological liar I can get you anywhere?
johnnyhotlava: I open doors
aziz_fazlagic: why do you use mac os?
searchingforlife: how much for a group twitch life coach?
twiggy_io: github.com/evanlib
johnnyhotlava: Shit
Klingenwetzer: LUL
johnnyhotlava: Well
ferrahs: @aziz_fazlagic why not lmfao
rkxbz: github.com/raysultan
gunnaren: LUL
Klingenwetzer: posting the githubs LUL
johnnyhotlava: I figured I could start a new "tech" company that makes chairs
Klingenwetzer: with only private repos OpieOP
johnnyhotlava: We chair
johnnyhotlava: we sit
Roundlay: Is this a hackintosh?
Jewishrambo: boyfriend applications but for geohot
annasgrasshopper: https://github.com/Alf0nso
puffnfresh: https://github.com/puffnfresh
eaoruhgadfhjglajsdlfgj: LUL
Klingenwetzer: LMFAO
puffnfresh: NO STARS
twiggy_io: I have one star thank you
rkxbz: im bewbie
benchai18: Remind me ur email?
0xc0ffeee: lolololol
eaoruhgadfhjglajsdlfgj: NO STARS IN 2019 LUL
jax05_: lmao
Klingenwetzer: OMEGALUL README
0xc0ffeee: ahahaha
johnnyhotlava: LMAO
knilecrack: ahahahahahahaha
Sznurek066: LUL
joker2k999: bruh...
buttez: LUL
Kriminell00: oh god this was a bad idea LUL
Klingenwetzer: LMFAO LUL
aziz_fazlagic: @ferrahs Just wondering ;p thought he just got a razor blade
0xc0ffeee: rip
knilecrack: ahahahahahahahahahaha
Jewishrambo: HAHA
johnnyhotlava: Hey what's a github
kayos_rl: lul
yaus_baus: george would prob roast my git too
ferrahs: LMFAO normie github
benchai18: @jewishrambo Shana tova
fazel3ss: Hire me I’m fucking bored
Klingenwetzer: dafuq this is worse than mine LUL
Jewishrambo: EleGiggle
dorkmo: roast githubs stream lol
puffnfresh: riPepperonis
faulpelzz: lmfao
ferrahs: LOL
Klingenwetzer: TAB WutFace
puffnfresh: https://github.com/puffnfresh
okkessh: will you check a video of my image processing algorithm
puffnfresh: roast me
Keyeh: i'd would pay you to roast githubs
okkessh: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AEUoB59kNcI&feature=youtu.be
Klingenwetzer: STARS PogChamp
Keyeh: literally
rkxbz: how to get stars?
ferrahs: Formatting sucks lmao
johnnyhotlava: Hire me I earn my living cutting in principles into the services they pay for creating the illusion of profit.
benchai18: @johnnyhotlava WHATS HIS EMAIL?
knilecrack: that's how you make $$
searchingforlife: https://github.com/dougwilson
Sznurek066: LUL sellout
Klingenwetzer: LUL
johnnyhotlava: @benchai18 I know not
goto10: @georgehotz just curious, what happened to your self-driving car project?
johnnyhotlava: GOteem
benchai18: @georgehotz what’s ur email
joker2k999: can't hate. his hub is better than mine. LUL
Vespus: Work for free? yeah, nty
TheKoreanZombi: Puffnfresh has hundreds of stars
Klingenwetzer: PogChamp
ferrahs: @searchingforlife fake stars
jax05_: oh shit
buttez: THICC contributions
searchingforlife: gotem
fazel3ss: I have 16 lol
puffnfresh: puffnfresh subscribed at Tier 1.
Klingenwetzer: DAMN THIS GUY PogChamp
Sarkin_dota: PogChamp
buttez: saturday committer dafuc
benchai18: cheers
joker2k999: nice bro.
Sznurek066: PogChamp
peter35_: how many pieces of flair do you have
johnnyhotlava: Nice nice flair
puffnfresh: oi I subbed
alb55: time to leave 1st grade hotz
Jewishrambo: isnt that forked
Klingenwetzer: FeelsGoodMan Nice man forsenK NOICE
ferrahs: That isn’t his work
twiggy_io: All forked
okkessh: interested in an image processing algorithm on dashcam footage ?
goto10: who use perl?
imsooinhuman: whats in your guys opinion best site for coding challenges?
fazel3ss: Perl
johnnyhotlava: We chair invest
puffnfresh: https://github.com/puffnfresh
jax05_: all forked lol
ferrahs: Everything on his profile is forked. Fake AF lol
buttez: when u commit like 20 times in one day so u dont get dark green squares anymore :(
metasudo: oh we're checking out githubs? Here's mine https://github.com/torvalds
Klingenwetzer: 2 contributors LUL @georgehotz
Klingenwetzer: "other ppl"
johnnyhotlava: His face
puffnfresh: there we go boiz
johnnyhotlava: HOT
Jewishrambo: WutFace
jax05_: PogChamp
twiggy_io: All forked
blazorup: have you checked out stdlib.com ? what do you think about functionscript ?
buttez: from India?
goto10: he is not look Indian though
eaoruhgadfhjglajsdlfgj: 300 repos WutFace
Klingenwetzer: Indian Boys PogChamp
johnnyhotlava: Image search I don't buy it
puffnfresh: I lived in India for a year
Jewishrambo: try it
puffnfresh: just got back last week
Klingenwetzer: LMAO
Keyeh: PogChamp
Roundlay: PogChamp
joker2k999: LUL
Keyeh: hire him Pog
yaus_baus: damn
yaus_baus: must be nice
Jewishrambo: PogChamp
CondomsWontFit: PogChamp
Klingenwetzer: PogChamp FREE JOB ONSTREAM
searchingforlife: PogChamp
ScrubLifeChoseMe: ur still on?
shieeeeeeeeet: hired PogChamp
tris790: Freee JOB BOIIS
peter35_: get him to explain what a monad is Kappa
metasudo: HES HIRED
puffnfresh: yeah you can hire me @georgehotz
Sznurek066: hired Pog
puffnfresh: $50 for 15 minutes
johnnyhotlava: George I'm a certified hypnotist I can "optimize" your team
puffnfresh: via PayPal
Sarkin_dota: SOLD PogChamp
faulpelzz: nice 1
Jewishrambo: didnt work
metasudo: OOOOOF
Klingenwetzer: LUL Jebaited
puffnfresh: just PayPal me $50 and I'll interview with you @georgehotz
shieeeeeeeeet: unhired
Klingenwetzer: Jebaited SCAMMED
blxckghxst: log out?
twiggy_io: Lol
metasudo: HES FIRED
okkessh: will you check my image processing algorithm?
tris790: reload ?
buttez: Jebaited
goto10: Buested
Kriminell00: fired on first day PogChamp
Sarkin_dota: SCAMMAZED
jagger_rsw: @georgehotz it was malware obviously ;)
blxckghxst: Scroll up to usage
johnnyhotlava: GO home
puffnfresh: I'll fix it for $50
ferrahs: Doesn’t work LOL
goto10: busted!
blxckghxst: Log out and back in
Jewishrambo: zzz
tetamusha: you are a shadow in my life, George Hotz
puffnfresh: macOS dude
Klingenwetzer: Not hired BibleThump
jax05_: ResidentSleeper
johnnyhotlava: My github is just coq pics
Kriminell00: LUL
shieeeeeeeeet: @georgehotz do you hire people without githubs? or it's a hard requirement?
Klingenwetzer: lol
joker2k999: lmao
puffnfresh: it did work a while ago
puffnfresh: macOS changed all of its API
TheKoreanZombi: Of course it works!
puffnfresh: of course IT DID
faulpelzz: @puffnfresh u stream?
johnnyhotlava: eggs act lee
jax05_: pretty sure github is a hard req
puffnfresh: yeah mate @faulpelzz
Klingenwetzer: forsenThink damn
twiggy_io: Forked
metasudo: REHIRED
Joy_void_Joy: Sorry if this is off topic, but it was actually simple to prove eqb' -> eqb'' with induction, and then proving true is not false (without any built-in).
Joy_void_Joy: I can share the source somewhere if you want
blazorup: https://github.com/jetstreamin
puffnfresh: REHIRED
tris790: SAVED
searchingforlife: @puffnfresh Jebaited
metasudo: please checkout my github https://github.com/torvalds
puffnfresh: 10 STARS
Klingenwetzer: ten forsenS
buttez: quick star the repo everyone
metasudo: ayyyy
puffnfresh: if you don't have 10 friends
puffnfresh: you're done
Klingenwetzer: LUL
johnnyhotlava: That guys name is sanjay
metasudo: We live in a github society
johnnyhotlava: Image search
Klingenwetzer: BibleThump I got no friends
Nnotm: @puffnfresh I'm sure you could arrange for someone to give you 15 stars for $50
buttez: old pic BTW
Klingenwetzer: 26 PogChamp
blazorup: single responsibility
puffnfresh: I reckon @Nnotm
jagger_rsw: I have 1.6k but it's company's open-sourced thing I'm developing :)
Sznurek066: oldHotz
SKPTCL: the old photo reminds him of his roots lel
joker2k999: that documentation tho....
johnnyhotlava: I develop ways to write paragraphs without saying anything to draw investment from the elderly
johnnyhotlava: We sit
johnnyhotlava: we Chair
johnnyhotlava: It's hot
ZeeZaxean: bang me
dorkmo: good old days
Klingenwetzer: PogChamp
yaus_baus: star georges coq
gunnaren: Streaming tomorrow?
joker2k999: past hotz..
metasudo: gonna follow george's coq
johnnyhotlava: You can do that
johnnyhotlava: STREAM
Klingenwetzer: Twitch partner PogChamp
ZeeZaxean: big money Pog
TheKoreanZombi: Don't tease us with partnering again...
SKPTCL: any plans for next stream?
Klingenwetzer: BlessRNG
lasercatboss: why though
Klingenwetzer: I BELIEVE
yaus_baus: 9 stars
johnnyhotlava: You can invest that money into wechair technology
asaptwice: what is twitchcoq im new ^^
abk467: that purple check mark will look nice
3FXX: sellout
Klingenwetzer: I'm gonna star twitchcoq when I'm back at my pc
buttez: bubi
Nnotm: asaptwice coq reimplemented in python
puffnfresh: $50 for 15 minutes to get your shadows gone
knilecrack: bb
goto10: hs, lots of money
dorkmo: Party1
Klingenwetzer: lowHi bye dad
okkessh: check the gmail
jax05_: byee
Klingenwetzer: DMs Kreygasm
kayos_rl: peeace
TheKoreanZombi: I want mine to be public
asaptwice: @Nnotm ty
UniversalGeneve: would you do code coaching for $80/30 mins?
puffnfresh: $15
johnnyhotlava: God he was so erect today
puffnfresh: I'm on CodeMentor